There
All right
Good morning everybody. Hi, babe
Hi, I just woke up.
Yeah, I woke up at an appropriate time.
How are you?
Good morning, Doug.
Hello.
How are you today?
Good to see you.
I
Know some people have trolls, but I'm not a lot of people have trolls that
members and
our
Think you're my fan. I don't know. You're
Regular
Hi guys. Hi Miley. I'm Mikey. Good morning
If you're having a good morning and wants to come say hi, welcome to you
You are a troll general general but fan of me. It's awesome. I
Think that's pretty much a accomplishment. It's like
If you're trol, if you have trolls that actually are fans
I'm not a fan of my family. I'm a fan of yours, too
You know for my some some things you say or two or not
Yeah, and I got serious
Yeah, I feel good to say though, you know, I got it got a lot of breasts last thing I've kind of like
Really happy drinking as much
Today I have like a
I'm a spiritual bath coming
And sage
Really like I
Think there is you know, you just think divide things into like four cycles just this divide things in a season
in five to a month's, five to a month's seasons,
this is kind of the major cycles of the year, right?
And so, it's good to take care of things
at the end of cycles.
The new cycle can begin.
You don't wanna carry energy through the whole cycle.
You wanna like end cycles.
So it's good to end cycles at the end of the,
Before the equinoxes and the and the salsas is right
Then you don't carry as you can start fresh and not carry all the energy throughout the whole season
Think about it
That's a good time to just like also you can go by the moon cycles too in the moons
waxing, when it's increasing, you can start increasing things, putting energy to things,
and then waning at full moon at the peak of it, then start to cut down on things through
when it's waning, the things you want to end.
So you can work with the moon, there's a book called Moonology.
I'll tell you head over with the moon cycles. A lot of great books on it. The moon is a very powerful
guide and so is the Sun.
Between the summer right now, there's gonna be like a big intensity of a passion.
You know
Coming into, you know, next month is Leo. We're in cancer right now. So we had this emotions then the fire
Cancer has to do with the moon
And changing emotions, then, you know, Leo is moved by the sun, right?
We have the moon and the sun.
So, pretty extreme, extreme polarity in June and July.
Hi, Mikey.
Yeah, I was just like it's been an early morning
Yeah, but think about some things like why is like a people that
Manipulate they tend to like like to brainwash and why would they like to brainwash people what is brainwashing as brainwashing will be you know
There'll be a lot of gas lighting. There will be
There'll be like things said. Let me see
There'll be
Certain kinds of programming there's certain words
words that are gonna be used and
You know words have a lot, you know, you know, we worse have a lot of letters in them
And, you know, there's like a lot of ways to like play with words, and so people can use these little plays on words, these little double entendras, they can just wait for people to treat you.
No, or there's actually a classical cycle of it. Okay. Hey, Dougie
Morning psych. Hi, how are you? Pretty good new good? You wake it up
Yeah, look at those six and I was just gonna go back to bed, but
They had to sleep pretty early. And so I got a lot of sleep. So I'm feeling good
Did I see did I see you slumped over and sleeping yesterday on your stream before I left?
Last night. It was the last night. Maybe yeah, okay. I might have
I don't know sometimes, you know, but uh, I've gotten up dressed now, you know, it's been a little I was partying a little bit
On the weekend
It happens sometimes but and I also you know, like I go pretty hard sometimes on the stream I stream a long time sometimes
As I do smoke pot and that makes me sleepy
But I haven't been I've been drinking as much so I've been having a few drinks that I so I find that when I smoke pot
It might help me sleep, but if I don't smoke pot, I'm more likely to remember my dreams
Yeah, that's true. It's because maybe it's because
marijuana will
suppress the REM sleep and so you won't go into that as deep of that sleep state where you can remember your dreams
That's why people will often not feel very arrested after smoking by the wake-up tires still, right?
You're not getting the full
Arrest I did a couple of gummies once. I think I slept for like 12 hours
Yeah, it's about
well, I love to sleep and
I love to dream and I
Can't get enough of it, but yep
I can sleep so much so that sometimes it can be hard to fall asleep. So
You're gonna have a regular schedule. Hey, GD. Alexa. How are you?
He's the electric here
Hi, good morning. Oh
Yeah, have you ever seen a lecture this is six o'clock?
Yeah, I hope I did
Nine o'clock good morning guys. Yep
Alice I almost wish I had a copy right now, but I might go get one a little bit
Hey, Alexa
Yeah, um, yeah, so I uh, my mom my uh, my mod thing is working because I'm working pretty good, you know, I I
Have a just a just gonna have a few mods like maybe
Between three and five
People I know really well and trust be people who you've known for a long time, right? Yeah
Yeah, I read they're beyond proven of you know that they are supporters and
and so I
It's going pretty well and
I know yesterday I saw I came in and I didn't see you had someone modding. I forgot who yeah
Yeah, maybe Jamie's cat boys and I also have a friend Teresa. I've known them both for about a year
Yeah, Jamie's is probably when I'm like my first my first mod on the show and I probably started last October
When I was just doing lives and she's been there almost, you know, she likes to try to come to almost every show
She's she's very very very
Sweet always reads everybody in the room and everyone likes her
Really cool person. So I
Got some great mods. I'm really happy
Morning thing that is
Got yesterday. I had a you know, I I gifted five memberships and then
Elzo gifted five memberships and so
nice day
the
Increase the memberships. We got a lot more a lot of green in the room
Let's see, let's see, let's see. Increase the membership. How much do you charge for membership? Five dollars, right? Yeah. Wow. Yeah.
You see, that's a lot. I love it. I love it. Some people charge two dollars, one dollar. Yeah. Yeah, I know that's, you know, that's a, that's a good way to do it, too.
I will, you know, I do free chair readings every day, you know, if anyone asks, and for members, I'll give more cards.
And so that can be very valuable. I mean, that can be considered very...
I think the less the membership costs, I think the more likely people will become members. That's what I think.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. Well, well, I think it's been, you know, I think I've had a decent amount of...
of signups, you know, you know, they, YouTube does take like 30%, and so, you know.
YouTube takes 30%, right? Yeah. Yeah. There you go. I give you five
members. Hey, thank you, Doug. Thank you so, thank you so much,
Dougie. That's so kind of you. Oh my god. Thank you so much. Wow, guys. That's a great
way to start the day.
Yeah, and that that really that really does help support the channel so much. I really appreciate that and so awesome
Wow
So how's your week going?
Got some fish yesterday. We weren't fishing. I came on the morning. I told you right yes
Yeah, so I
Posted it in some videos on my channel. We caught we caught some straight bass out in the long-hound sound
Oh cool
We got a total of six stripers and one black bass
Seven fish and caught and I got I got too much son. I was exhausted when I came in but you know, it's fun
Yeah, I mean I haven't been fishing I think I think we went deep sea fishing in Mexico probably know probably years ago
But I live right but right at this period. Oh, so I don't know
Maybe I could like look into
maybe some buying some fishy equipment sometime and
Yeah, but you know, there's people that just sit down there all day. I hear it's pretty slow sometimes
people are sitting there all day without catching fish, but
You know, it's
It's got the prime prime fishing right here though. There's a great little spot for there's all this space for over there. So I
Just don't know. I just thought I need a I need a probably a mentor. I need a teacher. Yeah fishing takes patience
Fishing alone. I mean, I don't know. I used to go out and fish alone
But one reason I don't fish so much anymore instead. I don't have no one to fish with
You know what I mean? I say down. I mean down here to the river
I'm not I'm not but a quarter mile from the Hudson River, you know
But yeah, you know, you know you will you have did you go yesterday with by yourself or with anybody?
No, what we did is this my cousin is in town and he has a buddy he has a buddy with a boat in Connecticut
So we drove over to Stanford Connecticut
Got on my cousin's buddy's boat six of us and went fishing for the day
Nice, I was invited by my cousin
Well, cool, you know, but I would be great to like, I don't know, you know, maybe you can
I don't know if there's any like networking or meetups for fishing or something like that there but the internet
There's there's ways to meet people because it is fun to meet new people
Channels on the internet loads of them is hundreds of people and I think that's what I'm saying about a lot of people
I know on the internet will go fishing alone, but they they livestream it they have this
There's there people with them, you know the yeah
Yeah, I mean I wish I had you know if I had a morning rusty. Oh, I resty. Good morning
Yeah
Rusty, you know, you know rusty you might rusty. Oh, yeah, you know
I'm not rusty for quite some time. Okay. I'd say I've been in YouTube five years. I've known rusty at least four
So yeah, awesome. Oh, yeah, it's you know, it's so interesting like
People all meet that I know other people like everyone's very much networked in you know
I'm pretty much the new the new fish
Right YouTube makes the world smaller you're close to people. Yeah, I'm meeting people from Australia and you know, India and God knows where
And you know, yeah, I would not meet otherwise
Oh, yeah, it's pretty pretty amazing. Yeah, it's great
Because you know, you know or buyer, you know her first name basis, but you know from her from her first
Your name, so
Yeah
You know
About Russia, I think I know I know at least I think six or seven different accounts
Which is fine, I don't bother me listen internet's the place
You know that I'm not I don't know how to explain it, but I'm on the internet that that's what people do
You know what I mean? It's like this and there's all kinds of good reasons for it, too
Right. Yeah
Yeah, well, you know
I pretty much doxed myself when I started the show just by, you know, by sharing a lot.
Yeah, I'm into astrology, so I've shared my birthday with people.
I've been docked for years, right?
I slide stream off of my porch in my house.
It's actually set up right now.
You can see that the street signs across the street.
Anybody who wants to know where I live,
I give them, I'll put my address in the chat,
I'll put my phone number in the chat,
and I put all that information out there
for anyone who wants it.
So that that way,
I'm not vulnerable to being docked right no one could yeah, but I'm not worried about it either. Yeah, I'm not
That someone's gonna come to my house if they do good. I'll invite them in right
The other thing I would say is this and I was listening to the conversation in your chat the other day
You know people docks themselves, right? Yes
Nobody could if you don't put any information out there. Nobody can get it from you
If you know
You know, I know people in chat. I've known for five years. They've been chatting under some name
Don't know who the hell they are. I don't know where they live
I don't know their phone number and yet they're good friends of mine
They've taken precautions to keep all that stuff. The only way you can get docked is if you put the information out there
Yeah, I mean and but sometimes you will like there's there's ways people do things
I don't want to give the way too many of
these tricks these people use,
so people, I don't want people to use them maliciously,
but they will, like, you know,
people could actually like send you a donation
or send you a gift and then get your information,
you know, the people will give their,
people will give, people will meet people like one-on-one
and these people, and also people will be,
if you go to someone's PayPal account,
you get their information.
Well, listen, if you're not soliciting money from people,
nobody's gonna go to your PayPal account.
Yeah.
Well that's true and there's one in particular I could name let's let's say my friend Herman monster, right?
Okay, he's been in chat for years. I've known him for a long time
Herman Munch is not his name. I don't know anything about where he lives or anything
He never puts any of that information out there. He never asked for money. He never goes on a panel
Nobody gives a look, you know, he has never put out any of
How do you dox a guy like that? Yeah, I'm not sure he's a guy or a girl
Yeah
I mean, but there are people that are better when you do develop like personal relationships
Sometimes you will and it's not like you're not like you're giving your information in the chat
You're talking to like who you think is a friend and they can have other other alternative motives
They could be working with groups. They can be they can be one week and not your friend the next. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Yeah, exactly. And if you people just go through the ups and downs the front and so there's but also I would I would say
I was pretty much doxxed just by going on a show and I mean sharing my, I mean I guess I guess I just shared my first life there, but I shared my, this sharing my photo on a show, I think they were able, I don't know if there's facial recognition stuff or people get to take a photo if you share a photo online, and I put it into like.
You know Google and come up with like all the photos of yourself. I mean there's it's getting crazier
There's reverse image searches, too
If you look into you on photos and find out if the photo is even real because people will send fake photos
That's that's very useful for catfishing and stuff to figure out catfishing and
Yeah, but rusty right I think what I've read in chat is your name and your address
Right. I think I've read that in chat
Right you protect your your identity. I mean, I don't think it's been a mystery
right um
I have people in chat who
Put my phone number and my address out there. It was already out there before I've made it public myself
So I just laughed at them, right?
They think they're hurting me and then what really what really is I didn't even get a Christmas card though
You know you think if someone's gonna go to the trouble to have your address
Right, maybe they'd send you a card in the mail. I don't know
Yeah
Yeah, you know
As long as it's not used for nefarious purposes, but what I was doxxed
You know is the it's what you and they call the cops and the blah blah blah you have a bunch of more
Well, the first time I was doxxed
It was actually like because I know I fell asleep on my stream
and then everyone got people were getting very concerned that something happened to me or something like that and
They got they all started talking like I'm sorry worry about it
And they several people called the police like the local local police station
And so the police actually they came to my house and did a wellness check
And then they actually did call my mother.
Like I don't know how they had her information or anything,
but the fleets were calling my mom and stuff.
And so she found out about it.
Also, then I had probably about one day,
I had about seven or eight pizzas sent.
And it's happened a couple of times
since I've had someone knock on the door,
oh, Domino's or whatever.
I set the tell off, hey, is it paid for?
And they're usually like, oh, no.
I'll say okay, it was a prank and then they leave I mean, it's not a big deal
It's not it's not like not scary or anything
But then they but they threatened I've been threatened with like scrappers and they said we're gonna send scrapers
Which were people like looking for metal or simply scrap metal where it says scrappers or?
or uh, we're gonna send who else or to send shipers or prostitutes to your house or
Yeah, or we have been told. Oh, we're gonna have having a thousand pounds of manure delivered to your house. You're dressed or like
Yeah, no
I know exactly that so no one showed up and no one you know really no one's gonna show up
And so, yeah, I pretty much talked myself, but yeah, but someone, you know, I put my name out there
So I did a talk to Elisa Jordana and I've asked her about a lot of stuff, but I couldn't know who Elisa is. Yeah
Yeah, you know
Yeah, that's cool, but yeah, I've seen him on the on her show and then I think Bita is familiar with him
Yeah, yeah, yeah, a lot of people from Elisa remember Todd
Todd was down there I guess about a year and a half ago or something yeah
So I asked Lisa. It's like well, how do you how do you deal with uh
Being doxed and she's like she's like, you know what every every celebrity is is doxed
And you know and these are people with like, you know, the millions of fans celebrity now. What's the matter with that woman?
Well, you know, she has uh, she has she has you know, you have a small following on YouTube. Yeah
It's a small following but still um, like I'm about
You know about seven out of ten people I might might ask about her in my innocent
In my life
Yeah, they have paper or she went viral last year. So a lot of people saw that incident like a lot of people did
Yeah. And people are familiar. You know, DJ Electra in the chat knows Todd really well. Yeah. You know, Electra, Electra actually, you know, you wouldn't...
Yeah, DJ Electra from Todd's chat, I think. I've met with Todd. Todd lives, well, except that he's in Ecuador now. He lived just about a half hour up the road for me.
I used to stream with Todd and go by his place about once a month.
I'm trying to help him get subs now. He's gone ahead and move to Ecuador. I'm not sure what he's on about
He says he's never coming back
Wow, yeah, he has a very interesting, you know with her history of assistant, I think she must have
Have a body count of over like a hundred hundred past assistants or people that she's a lot to her show
There's just a there's a lot of people that enter in her back up
But yeah, but she said you know every celebrity is already doxxed every day, you know, they they are millions of fans
Other information that they all have a you know all their names are fake usually bill
Not hard to find
Hi, those addresses are out there and everything and
But I mean, did you have more security? Hey, yeah, hey, uh, I'm beer in Gapow
Yeah, hey, Leah. How are you? Are sending people on wild goose? Yeah, you can always like put out, you know
false information to you know, and that will
People will think that they have this this correct information and they're going a wild goose taste. They're like, okay. Well
That's not the right person, you know, so it's crazy like there's not really except for the case I heard this year
You've heard this case. There's a YouTube streamer
And he was getting harassed by this other YouTube streamer to the point where he got his channel taken down
This guy had a pretty big channel and a lot of memberships and it was making all his money from YouTube
and the guy ended up like
just snapping going down to Vegas, I think,
and then unaliving the kind as wife.
You heard that story?
I heard that.
People with mental illness probably take you to,
I can see how it can be bad for a person, right?
Some people think I may actually think it like it's real like it's it's all important and it makes a difference in their lives or something
I don't think it does
YouTube is it's a thing I do for fun
Yeah, it's a thing I do for fun. Hey, I'm not monetized. I'm not trying to make money
I'm not I'm not I'm not live on YouTube. I'm not trying to live my life on YouTube. You know, yeah
And that's a that is a great way to do it and some people have different circumstances
I mean it's like you know, but you know some people do make a living from YouTube like this particular person
I think he had I think he I heard he was making a hundred grand or something a month
And I think he had like at that over a thousand memberships that were $10 or something like that
so
Which should be I don't know
It's quite a lot, it's making quite a lot and then to, you know, people will just mess
with people, they're trying to strike down their channel and, you know, and unfortunately
sometimes, you know, people do and it's, it can be very devastating for some people.
To
Yeah, I'm not sure those people, you know, I mean you want to be you want to be careful
You know how much you invest in the YouTube?
Yeah, as a creator. You gotta know, right? I've had people call and report my channel. Yeah
Yeah, you got to understand when you go into it that this could happen and then the whole thing could you know
You can have people really fuck with you on your channel
Yeah, yeah, I had somebody come up and trying to pour bomb me like three times in the same night
Oh, yeah
Ilya let me just say about Ilya I remember that guy Ilya came on my panel
About a month ago. He or maybe three weeks ago
He came up and I asked him about I said why are you wearing a wig and he got mad at me
It said what do you care and so I threw him off
Oh, that's it remember Ilya was up here with the kill. Yeah. Well, he was yeah, he was up here and then
You know, unfortunately, I I did fall asleep
I mean, I got so lucky because he was you know
He's been on two other times and he porn bought me both times
You know, he like he moved me the first time then he showed his penis the second time when he peed on on stream and then
Then the third time he was in the kill and he wasn't wearing anything under the kilt and he kept
pulling it up, and I was like, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And he kept in, and he was like sitting up on a chair.
And, but somehow I passed out and left him on all alone.
And then I woke up the next day,
and I was like, what happened?
And they're like, well,
He just took off his wig and then, and then they said somehow they thought,
they someone thought I kicked him off or something like that. I don't remember if I woke up
he kicked him off or he just left, but I think I'm very lucky that nothing happened because
I heard about my panel a few weeks ago and he was acting weird, like weird.
And I asked him why you're wearing a wig and he said why are you making fun of people wearing wigs?
I just threw him off for that. I said, you know, you're not gonna answer my question. Fuck you. That's the way it is, you know
Yeah
Well, I think I'm a little more. I'm a little quicker to trust people than you
Yeah, which is fine. Anybody's different, but you know, um
Yeah, I he was on my panel for about a minute before I threw him off
Yeah, uh-huh. Well, how about he's acting weird and not only that but
He seemed to me as if he was trying to be intentionally provocative. Yeah, uh-huh. Yeah
That's fine do that somewhere else. You're not gonna do that shit on my panel
Oh, he guys he adjusted his camera and he accidentally booted himself guys
If he would have been left on if he didn't accidentally boot himself
Adjusting his camera that little like little that's like divine intervention really because he he would he would have done something
And then because I know this guy. Well, there's a guy named good times
I don't know if you heard good times and he had a channel and he's just
Kind of late like a laid-back kind of hick or country kind of guy
Yeah, yeah
And so he had a channel. It wasn't monetized, but it was a big, big channel. And, you know, a lot of probably, you know, decent amount of followers. And, and then he got formed by Aldi, this guy Aldi, 5k or something.
Um showed his balls or whatever pulled out his pants and then good times were just sitting there staring
I think he was on maybe some
Pain killers or something like that, but he was gonna mess up
He was just staring he just waited too long and then his channel was deleted because it's like it was just like you have to
Yeah, you have to get those porn bombs really fast, you know
Yeah, good times
Yeah, have a mr. Big Piper you're familiar with this for big pipes now mr. Big pipes. I've known for quite a while
Yeah, I've been in his live stream. I've been in his chat
Yeah, he's uh, he's another one. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know quite what to say except that you want to be a little careful
That's all you know what I mean. I think he's an old guy. I think big pipes is all right
You know, well, he was he was on the other night and he comes on and he kind of like
He talks to me really weird like he keeps saying the same catchphrase over and over
Which is really annoying and I imitate it
But I think he's trying to like say I think he's saying it so weird because he's like a California accent. He goes
I'm just trying to chill. He goes
Don't be sedge yet. Okay, it's really I mean it's like it doesn't that's didn't talk like that
normally, but then then he kept like
You know, he's very temperamental musician and he's very he's very drunk and he's like and then
He'll like say you want to play a song. I'll take him like
45 minutes to even start and then he'll like that do like 10 shots between then and then so start hitting on
me start hitting on on a woman and then those are really
Really sexual with me and I mean, it's it's just
Like I said, he seems like a nice enough guy
To me however, I've heard I've heard stories about him and you know, he does get a little bit
Um, I don't know what's the word but it is chat like after a little while of being there talking with him
I was like, yeah, okay. I'm gonna go somewhere else now
Yeah, yeah
That's why I constantly feel like we're somewhere else when you've never but
Also, I get like this message. Oh, this is a this account and it's called nightmare. I think it's called and it says
This is like mr. They're like mr. Bigpipes the panel there the channel or the
Livestream killer or whatever and it's like every time you have mr. Big Cops on we're to do your name
minus minus 15 likes and I was and then I was like
And then it would do that and I was and I had like a big negative place and then it's like I did only all my legs are gone and
It's not a big deal. It's like if people give you thumbs down
Yeah, you could go on your analytics and go on the page and go look and see
Otherwise, you don't see it, right? You only know that you got them if you go and look on your and have to find them
I'm not sure content
You go to your content on the left
Right, and you and you'll see you and you can go to your live stream that you can go and look and they'll tell you
How many thumbs down you got but unless you do that?
You don't know how many you know. Yeah. Well, okay. Well, it was interesting also was was weird is that
You know, he was he was using an avatars or an avatar instead of going on camera for the past like, you know
Maybe a week. He's been using this avatar. I thought it was like
some kind of avatar for
Like the computer logo or something I like it just like a version that kind of like second this bright green
kind of triangle avatar thing and so
Okay, so anyway, so someone told me, oh, that's a chaos magic sigil and I was like, oh, really?
Because I've studied like, you know, magic and I know about chaos magic and the sigils
and like that.
This kind of thing.
So I was like, okay, well, why is it so he's putting this big sigil up?
And then it was just, that was kind of weird.
On the streamer, but but but he was when he went to my back my back chat and he is like started going off and he's like
I'm he's like your hex six six six, you know, and it's like and so
He's the it is along those lines of like
Using sigils that I so I don't know what he's up to it. Just like yeah
I was getting uncomfortable feelings and I have to go with my gut on that and I was I just I just
Okay, I'm gonna have to go a couple of things. Okay. Okay. Thank you, Dougie and second of all
I think my life came on my porch overheated. I gotta go. Okay. All right
Okay
Thank you for coming Doug. Thanks for having me up. Thank you for the membership. Thank you for being here. We're talking to you
Okay, love you. Yeah, okay
Hey, lecture, I'm not, hopefully, everyone's getting along.
I'm not sure about everybody's, you know, relationship, but it is good to, like...
The symbol of civil shit was tripping me out to the guy with the head of Avatar 2. Yes
So Ziggy is his avatar is from the Goetia. It's a king saw the keys of Solomon. It's uh, you know
It's a little grimmery. You're getting along good. Yeah
That's I don't
See, I'm not sure of everyone's relationship or everything, but you know, I want everyone to get along
Yeah, so yeah, you recognize that to Marcy. Yeah, and it's like, you know
Sometimes you can put out, you know, a film puts like a, you know, even a star is a magical symbol, you know, or it's a
It's a symbol, right alchemy. Yeah, but it's like alchemy. It's just okay
So, you know, the goatia symbol is going to be a it's a demonic sigil and there's a lot of
Yeah, stuff can happen except I mean these
They can affect the subconscious and so they can be very working a very powerful way. Yeah
I mean think about we in that and we go to geometry. We've been like, you know elementary school
we'd make stars and learn circles and triangles and
But you know these shapes can be used other ways and stuff. It's always like yeah, we're surrounded by all these shapes all the time, but there are
Magical sigils that can have other effects that affect your own subconscious level
And the alchemy, you know, alchemy is like, should be, you know, it's also from the D-Man
eye post.
Yes.
Eye post and eye post is also known as sometimes the newbis.
I think there's different thoughts on the correspondences.
He definitely does understand it because I was asking about it.
I was telling him, oh, this is your D-Man's eye post and he's like, oh, it's actually,
You'd have to very much study study the demons. You know, he always plays dumb. He's he actually he doesn't know
What it is interesting
Yeah, it is it's like it's not something you just want to like put as your avatar, you know, it's like
Because that also I mean the internet is like the dream of the chaos magician because it all of a sudden it's like you're able to
Put the symbol everywhere. All of a sudden you multiply things very fast, right? And
You know, it's other people's minds and it was really really steps up the magic and so
They give me scary. So they would just watch out for
People that and they get an even visitor because of sitting backstage that that sigils on my screen and that's like, I don't
That's the point is it's like not something that I've studied and I want to and I'm you know, I say, oh this is this
Corresponds of what I want to be putting into my subconscious if somebody else doing it
Totally unrelated, you know, that's what it is. You have listened to him talk about a subject several times
Yeah, I mean I've tried to talk about it and he's like he just is like, oh
He told me that they're like an alternative name. Oh, that's just this first one
Then I went through I read the entire entire description of it
And then he just didn't kind of react so it's I don't know it's like when people are just playing dumb
I mean you it's a very niche kind of study that you know
I will recognize but the Goetia symbols are very extremely recognizable even if I even if I didn't remember the exact
Sigill if I saw if I saw any of the Goetia symbols, I would know it's a Goetia symbol. There's very
usually in a circle with the name around it and this yeah so yeah if you want to
if you are interested in like looking at them but it is like you know hey what's
up boo yeah it's very niche yeah I so I you know I'm actually I've I've I've been
Study on my own right and and you actually
Put a lot of time into study. I get it like a very
Three years, you know years dance. Yeah devilize. Hey, what's up? So I have a I've done extensive
studies and different, you know that the
Traditional method it can be very complicated
You know, it's kind of like kind of like to discourage discourage dabbling
But that's the whole thing. It's like this whole this whole centuries has been dabbling Alistair Crowley
Kind of brought everything out
But it inserted into the culture into the music into the movies
It's I mean, it's all if you see the movie hereditary movie hereditary
that's
All about the Goetia Demon called Paimon PAIMON
They kind of, you know, they take a little, take a little creative
liberties with it, but it is
pretty much
very accurate.
Other than all this, you know, some of the, some of the crazy paranormal stuff that happens, I
might be just a little bit Hollywood, but
Some of it's very correct. Hey guys. Hello for you. Yeah. Hey, say everybody. How's everyone doing?
Yeah
so
But yeah, the cult is not I mean there's certain personalities that are just like
There's boring for the occult, right? There's
Not you if it can be either born into it or they're just
they're pre-wired their spirit is or
There's going to be a lot of dabblers and
A lot of people that are not
Men for it and unfortunately it can be very
Dangerous for them. It can be very dangerous in that
A lot of people go insane a lot of people will go insane they can become
Obsessed
It's hard to explain it to most as most people won't be able to wrap their head around but it is what it is
I'm glad you're aware of those things. Yeah, and I know I'm a like maybe I
know I'm not saying I'm
so advanced but
I'm one of the people that's kind of like was
Kind of like always
Been in my mind in my my interests and always
Always like trying to
Uncover the darkness even especially my side myself, and it's you know, it's uh
That's like there was shadow work is because we all have a shadow and then
Especially these days. It's turned into a lot about
Let's go find this place. Let's go hunt down somebody else's shadow. It's a
Save the world. We're always looking at other people's shadows like we're always
You know, we always want to be in the hero position and then
Outside of us is the evil right?
but
Inside I said all of us in the shadow we all have it and we all have to deal with our own shadow and
Until we do their own shadow
We should not be trying to mess with other people's shadows. It's like
Because a lot of people just want to
They think everyone thinks the problem is always outside of themselves
No, and it's like this part of the human is like we're like, you know, you like to have a good self image of ourselves sometimes
But
It's
against it's weird when we think of we think of ourselves as perfect or some people think of themselves as gods and
infallible your gods and then this and then of course in order to be that position they have to look at other people as a
barnyard animals or
seeper
cows or
so
I'm always very
Rather than looking at people as gods or demons
We should I look at people as human human beings all that's where the all men are created equal all men and women are created equal
That's human beings. We're all
We're all equally
Perfectly imperfect, right? Hi, baby
Mr. Tricks good morning, yeah, but if anybody is you know
I do wonder about if there's, you know, tarot, you'll attract people in tarot that are, you know, in the occult, they'll attract people that are just spiritual, open-minded, or intuitive, or interested in divination, and there's all the, and even skeptics will be still kind of intrigued or interested.
I think that the light from your spirit shines so bright the darkness wants to take that time for itself.
I hear you. I hear you. And then I feel like that really, it's like that. I think we all have, we can all have that light and, you know, and the, the brighter you shine, the darker it will get around you.
Yeah, when you shine bright, you know, when you shine your light lights attract they can attract attention, right?
In the dark, you know
Don't know I can really see it. You'll you can be hidden, right?
So think about being a light that you're gonna be
Out there. Just that's just like a like just like and a corresponds to
you're out there on YouTube if you're out if you're
You're shining your light. You're you know, just being being out here and showing myself and talking you're pretty you're putting your light out there. And so
People will be attracted to you, but all kinds of things will be attracted to you from especially especially maybe
the darkness sometimes sometimes so
But just be a son be a son
You'll be too hot for anything to get too close to, right?
Yeah, but I would be interested in like, you know
People are interested in the occult and things like that. I have a lot of lot a lot of books and
You know, I will be just and I will be discussing a lot of
Occult things on the show that mainly focus on tarot astrology
But there's a lot there's there's a lot of interesting things. It's definitely in lifetimes of studies
So every day I can present in this lifetime
I'm gonna show it will just be like a
little little piece of it, but
If you guys have topics to suggest or with our questions or anything
Pretty much I have a I do have a pretty much wide variety of knowledge. I've studied a lot of things, you know
I know a lot of, as I said, a lot of world history, you know, a lot about, kind of, more esoteric, esoteric things, so, yeah, more, yeah, oh, you're welcome.
Ooh
Yeah, so yeah 15 people six forty a um, I don't know. It's yeah, it's like a
It's been a great
Great time on YouTube
Modestizations been going pretty well, you know, it's slowed down a little bit and
You know a lot of people come in and out but and you have so many loyal people
You know there's so much that's happened. There's been a lot of controversy a lot of people a lot of people left
You know it's like the right people are gonna come the right people are gonna leave it's gonna be it's just a
Still building a nice over probably almost 2,600 subscribers
you know I
Have been kind of controversial those people that you know
There's been a lot of things. There's I've had a lot of haters. I
Have my supporters
I've got there's people
They think of me a little bit little bit. No, I don't say oh, I'm somebody with gel stuff
I'm just a little little tiny little streamer. Hey time. How are you?
so
that I
Know I have
Have built my channel pretty fast and people see me and they're like, well, what's the special about him?
That's like really nothing special about me. It's like I
Think that I'm just I sit here and
share my
Share my share about myself talk, you know, I do it every day. I'm
You know, I've been around
Networking communities and met so many great people and it's not
It's not you know, and it's not easy for people. I know there's people with channels for years
so people with channels for years
that have you know, they've just grown up from organically and
They've done their best and it's like in the sometimes they don't have anybody in their chats. They don't have
Some of them don't even have a thousand subscribers and they've been doing it for years now
I've been doing it for six or seven months
It's and but it's there's the thing they're gonna people that
Get a million subscribers in a day practice or 100,000 subscribers a day
Or you know, there's some channels that haven't been able to do that and just took off overnight, so I'm not special. I'm just a little
And so for people to target me it's like
It's like there's
It's like there's like sharks out there chasing the guppies. How about that, you know, I'm not a meal for anybody
But luckily I'm a little
I'm a fast swimmer. Bye, Marcy. Love you. Much love. Yeah, so it's, I mean, it's very early.
We're having a little morning hangout. I'll put up my, uh, my, uh, hey Doug.
My phone on let me see my phone's always dying. It's not uh, it's live
You got the answer the mystery
Will
Okay
Move
Hi, Tracy. Good morning. Good to see ya. Sorry, Tracy.
Tracy, yesterday, yesterday, I just woke it up and I didn't know my chat was still on,
and so I saw my face in the camera, and then I was like, oh my god.
It was on, and then you were like, are you okay? It was so funny. I was okay.
Let's add a little bit of a funny face.
Let's say hi to Tracy.
Let's say hi to Trix.
Let's say hi to Ms. Tracy.
Hi.
Jesus.
It's Perrin.
Morning, everybody.
Yeah, is it gonna be a,
a, I think it'll be a copy this morning.
What do you say?
I don't know.
I'm gonna hit a pot.
Hey, it's okay. Don't be concerned. I was
Guys you should see the face that you should see the face that I make when when I'm not on camera
I don't deal on camera
I'm a little bit of a I
Think I might have my old the mild Tourette's
So
Hello, but looking for the channel for it's okay. Yeah, look kitty cats. It's just
Shakespeare's is here as Rudy over there every river there
Yeah, we'll be forward, you know, I
Like, you know, it's a hard balance. It's like, you know
Because now I guess now people think
Because I unmodded everybody that I
You know that it's actually like, you know drama free or something that wasn't all the drama like there's a lot
There's a lot of drama
Like a lot of the drama
Hey, Christine good morning a lot of the drama was
It's when certain personalities get together
I just like there can still be drama on the channel. It could be people like that don't like each other can still like
No, you have a kind of fight in the bait. It's like it's when it gets to like levels of making threats
Doxing and
Racism I mean
Transphobic there's there's ways to like
Have a debate or to fight or to talk and to you know, even if you don't like the person you can even like you know
This and without calling them names
That's how we saw the drama then from yeah, I think the mod yeah, that's not what I mean it was
love the mod stuff was like
That's why people would be getting us that's why this is a drama I saw because
It was like whenever people would get timed out
People would untimely them out and it's like and then people started getting
Like like getting mad and and think oh well
They're saying this why can't I do this and I was talking to JT for hours about it
Like it was basically and like him saying well
I I need a mod because I have your mods attacking me and then and you let them talk about me
But I can't say anything about them
Good morning. Good morning. So, I thought about this long and hard yesterday. Long and hard.
And I kept hearing you say it was and you did say the drama in here was from the mods.
That's what you said numerous times. That's not what I saw. I think you used the mods
came from drunks,
came from people who didn't sleep,
came from people who should never have been on this panel
to begin with because you give chance after chance
after chance.
And I don't think you wanted to realize that.
And if we're gonna be honest,
I'm going to be honest with you.
Oh yeah, and I didn't mean to like,
I didn't mean to,
I was just saying, the mods brought the drama, I'm saying it was the drama over the wrenches,
it was drama over the wrenches.
How can you tell me?
Alex and Flirty Diamonds issue were over a wrench.
Well, Alex was a little bit...
And Bad Pipes, his drama was because he didn't have a wrench and felt inferior.
Well, he did at one point, but then he started misusing it, and so I had to unrench him.
Well...
I don't know. I've left numerous times yesterday because no, it's not funny
Because
It's the fact that nobody's controlling and people think it's a free-for-all and can be nasty to other individuals
I won't stay in a chat like that
Oh, so yesterday's oh the chat. Yeah. Yeah, I won't stay in a chat like that
Well, yeah, the mod the two mods you have
Jamie is too kind and
She doesn't know. Well, should I shit nice? Should I should I can't just remove it?
And if you know and do a progressive she doesn't she doesn't do that Jamie's too kind
I mean, she's very kind and and Jamie is a very fair one. I don't get me wrong. I love Jamie
But she's very very kind
But when you've got a group of people and like you had yesterday going after one or two people
In a nasty tone when nobody's correcting it
It's okay, and I love I said forget it
There are plenty of other places to go to a little
plenty of other places
Christine
Like I wanted to say
Can I mod you would you be a model? No, no, no, no only only because I think you mean a
Bigger issue about wrenching than what should have been made versus focusing on the behaviors of
People coming up on your panel. Mm-hmm
That's why I need people that's why I need like a good mod like I know I need like I'm I can't okay
But I need like because I had so many people modded
And it was like I know I think a lot of yeah, it was causing so many too many problems if I had if I had just a few people
that I didn't that I know are
I think you need to really address the the real problem
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I know I understand but it's like, you know, I just you know, I just know you're like you always don't you're always the
got my back but
But I I mean the tech doesn't go kind of I mean it's hard to run a chat and run the panel
Because it's like you know, oh
There's a comment. I don't like it. I have to like just stop get scroll to get on the phone and like
You know, so they're getting it's hard. It is distracting trying to moderate when I'm trying to focus on the show
That's that's you know
the
It it is very hard, but I think and this is and I'm not and I'm doing this as constructive
I'm not trying to be mean or nasty about it. Hope you understand that
But I think that you focus so hard on the problem is with the wrenches and
You gave a few people
in their mind that ha
There's no wrenches now. I can say what I want to who I want and nobody's going to do anything about it
So yeah, so as long as I don't call them an F word or as long as I don't say a foul word I
Can go in and say whatever what I've never had a block list
so big
Other than when I came in here yesterday. Mmm. Yeah, I've never blocked that many people ever
and that's why I had to get off the StreamYard.
Because I like reading StreamYard and adding comments from the chat,
because chat's just as important as your panelists.
They really are.
And if your your chat loses interest because there's so much attention paid to the panel
Then you end up losing your chat and you have to have both because you are always going to have the majority of people that are in chat
not panel people
But I know but I really think that you focus too hard on
The mods the wrenches and I shouldn't say the mods because it's not the people and I'll be honest and
Talk to Jamie because I watched and and I kept giving little hints that when when I'm modding
I don't just automatically time people up. I just remove comments remove comments and then it's a progressive one
I start out with a 10 second. I'll do that once or twice and then I'll go to a minute
And then if they don't get the hint in a minute, then they do get a 5 or 10 minute and I and Jamie has never hidden anyone unless it was specifically told by you or they came in doxing because my thought process it is better to hide them and let you undo them when they're actually doxing.
It's a it's just a portion like the people
Tracy's agreeing with me if you read that she agrees that you concentrate it too much on the wrenches versus the real problems
Yeah, and you know you get you you remove off panel like
Ilje yesterday. I mean Ilje you had to watch him so closely. Nobody had to have fun
Yeah, I know you fell asleep and he had the panel to himself
And he accidentally he
He does he but he just did his camera and he turned off and it turned off the camera
That's what that's why that's why he left the show. I got so lucky
You got very lucky, but see the thing is though he was given numerous numerous times
Asked not to do that not to do that and and he was tormenting you
You shouldn't have to deal with the torment. I bet if you were removed him up panel left him up panel for a little bit
And said if you're coming up
Show the camera on your face not on your private parts
Yeah, that might have stopped the problem
You know bad pipes his threats yesterday, and I know they're idle threads. I get it
But who does he think he is coming and threatening a channel owner?
You need to take control over things like that
Yeah, well, yeah, it means like he's he was just
when you're when you're when you're reading or you know drawing or
concentrating on something else and and it seems to be you may need to get some
glasses to be able to see a little bit better you know you're losing people
because you've got somebody tormenting somebody about oh see and here we go
yeah positively possum you know I'm not lecturing site we're having a
because it may you may feel it's about you then I'm sorry but um but you know
you lost several people yesterday and people shouldn't have to keep blocking
everybody but you lost several because you had a few people in here going after
them personally uh-huh well yeah and there was nobody to stop that yeah well
That's why I need you to probably, I guess, like at least a few moderators, but, you know,
because I can't, I can't watch the chat all the time, like sometimes, you know, you know,
you know, you know, I agree, and I think the, I think the two people that you put are very
good people, but I will also say that I think you put them in a little bit of a predicament
Eldo is the mod now too. Oh great
That's pleasant
Eldo is the Eldo's the big supporter of the show
Pardon me. Well, but he's a big because okay, so
He's a big supporter and and I want you to think this a
Big supporter as in how?
Oh, he's just uh, you know, he's always on the panel. He's I don't think he was you know, no one ever complained about him in the mod
He didn't like this uses
Yeah, you know, do you know that do you know the people complaining about who the mod about modding were a
People that didn't have mom a rent and they had no clue who was doing any timeout
Not if you are if you do not have a rent you have no clue who?
It's timing who? Well, you know that, right? There was one day where nobody was being timed out,
nobody, but you had two people in here saying, oh, so and so is timing everybody out. Oh, so
and so is timing. Nobody was timing anybody out. They were playing you.
And somebody even said something and then I piped in and said, you know,
Um, so I can go back and look at the history and see who timed who out and you'll see nobody timed anybody up
Did you know that that there was two days like that
Yeah
When nobody was being timed out
But you had a couple of people in here. Oh, so on so Simon up. Well, first of all, they didn't have wrenches
So they didn't know who was tying me now
And I will tell you, I was in a chat last night and somebody, the channel owner said hides are put such and such in a 24 hour time out.
Hey, Tracy, you have a beautiful day too, honey.
the channel owner said put so-and-so in a 24-time-out.
Well, the mod went and put it in a 24-time-out.
And then another mod apparently did not hear the channel owner
or was showing a power issue,
untimed that person out to only 10 seconds.
And then a channel owner state had to come down,
had to go in and put them in a 24-hour time-out.
In platform boots. I'm not yeah, I'm not I'm not saying that but and I'm not saying he had too many wrenches
Please don't get me wrong. I agree. You had too many wrenches
Um, I just think that you weren't you're not addressing the real problem
That has been happening. That's what I think
And don't get me wrong. I'm not saying some people had wrenches wasn't a problem but
of the
people who didn't have branches there was a problem
yep
well
nearly Joe how are you sweetheart
hopefully you'll get better
I mean, you know, as well as I do, trial and errors go with channels and channel owners
all the time.
You think something's going to work and it doesn't.
So you have to try something different.
And then you as a channel owner grows and you have a different vision of what your channel
So, yeah, it will, you know, it will always be changing and if you don't, if your channel doesn't always change and become stagnant,
well, then you'll never reach your full potential.
Yep, just got to keep going and
you know.
I mean, we've all been around these YouTube streets for a while. I mean, we've all had channels. We've all had channels fail
We've all had channels taken away, you know
We all go through the trials and errors and it is what it is and you know to be honest your real supporters
Will still be here
And and I think somebody who truly cares and I I feel I'm one of them not lecturing
I'm I'm giving an observation and that's what you want is a open communication, right?
Or I mean you can say Christine just shut up
No, I love talking
You're you give great advice and uh, you know, if I do your opinion a smash these matches a member
It's hard work, isn't it, Sike?
Yeah, it is.
You know, and especially if you stay live longer than two hours.
Yeah.
But you know, I'll share something.
You talked about elbow getting up, getting a wrench.
You know, and you're okay with him coming over here.
and
Winding that he's going to call somebody's family member because he was but hurt he couldn't get on the panel
come on
No, he's saying I mean I say I'm
A lot of people say wild things. I don't know. I missed it
Well, no, you were having a conversation with them. Oh
And he's talking about somebody who was live yesterday and they and he tried to get on their panel and
They let him and then he came over here, it's crying to you saying,
why are you going to call their uncle or their brother?
And I'm like, who the hell do you think you are?
This is an adult threatening to call another adult family member because
you got butt hurt, get out of here.
Yeah
That's when I asked him I said so if you don't like if you don't like what I say up there on chatter
Unchannel that you're going to go ahead and call find a family member and call them on me with the house wrong with you
That was just weird
Yeah
It was just weird, but anyway, I how's your morning?
Other morning. Yeah, it's pretty good. I just woke up at like six
And so it's like I've been on for about an hour
Yeah, it was kind of with the cute look at and I get really good sleep and I'm just considering
You look good. Thank you. You look well rested. I like that
Yes
Yeah, I don't really have my bags are kind of going away. I had these big bags on my eyes recently, but
Yeah, I've been
Been doing you're taking
You know more time to sleep and take care of myself, and you don't have any houses clean. I feel pretty good
Yeah, you gotta sleep
When you don't think you've become a little psychotic
And then yeah, and then you look worn out in bags and pale skin and weight loss and then hair laws that
Yeah
I'm here to turn in gray though. I'm uh, you know
Really feeling this the feeling my age. So yeah, well, you gotta find some friends and get out in real life
I had a sleep stream. There is a real life out there, you know
Yeah
There is a you know, I'm um
But I'm living it. I'm I'm doing my best. I you know, I have a I have a different kind of life, but I
love my life and
You know we all have a different type of life and just because your life fits you doesn't mean it'll fit me
But guess what you're my life isn't gonna fit you either if we if we all the same life
You know boring that would be oh my god, could you imagine you all had to live my life?
You can imagine having to live my life like oh my gosh
Mom yeah, my life is pretty crazy to you
That's what that's what life's about. We all lead a different life and sometimes we we find
people that intrigue us. We want to walk that life with them.
That's the fun parts of life when you find somebody, you know, and opposites do attract.
you know, you find that you find your yin to your yang and and you walk that life trail together and
sometimes that life trail ends because one of you
Take that detour and it's just not the other person's detour and that's okay, too
This way I've got life life is like a box of chocolate. You never know what's on the inside
I can't fight into it. It's like, oh, no. Oh, that was good. You know
there is a true saying to that life is like a
box of chocolates
Well, thank you, Doug. I
Appreciate that
Doug apologized for his behavior yesterday and done, you know, I don't take words
Tough, you know, I mean the words are words
But I will share and yeah, come at me regarding my profession
That's one thing I don't do well, and I and I I'm glad you thank you for apologizing
Because that did upset me
And you can ask Jamie I've never hit anybody I've never timed anybody out 24 hours
unless you have said so
or I paid for it.
I think there's a couple of good mods. There was one or two, I felt they modded too rough, too hard, they were too quick.
Just a couple.
Money, money, money.
You're listening. Yeah, we're having a nice morning with pristine
sitting here
with tricks
Hi
Yeah, so it's pretty calm. I hear yeah, maybe I don't know if people have been other places. I hear
Once it beat is
I listen to beat is all night couple times it was I they woke me up and I had to watch you giggle
I had to watch and giggle
And I watched Kate's lesson for a while.
She makes me giggle too.
Yeah, they've been streaming a lot more,
like that's really good.
But yeah, it is good for them, you know?
And the sad thing is, Bita lost her channel,
you know, so she needs to build it up,
but she's having fun.
And you know, when you're at home on a channel having fun,
you're kinda staying out of trouble, you know what I mean?
No popo's gonna put those silver cuffs on you when you're at home
That's the way I look at it. Nobody's coming for me. I'm home. I didn't do it. I have a good alibi 50 people in the chat
right
Yep
Hey, stay. How are you this morning, sweetheart? Oh
Stop calling people old hats, you know, I am an old hat. I'm okay with that. I'm okay with that roofie
It's not a big deal. See I take it with a grain of salt.
Daisy, don't start on me sweetheart.
You got right smash. No, I haven't.
You got this though. Like just keep those that have your best interest versus theirs close to you.
That's all you got.
You know and you got quite a few of those that have your best interests that aren't
You know out there to say something for personal
Yeah
Well seems like I got a good chat going
In the room a lot of familiar people. Hey everybody good to see you guys
Say I'm good too, honey
You missed the interaction. You missed those. He's talking about there's somebody who who
and you know I'm a nurse. Everybody knows that and you have somebody else who claimed she's a nurse
and this is the most delusional person there is in the entire world that I have met. I promise you.
And yeah, her and I would go round and round.
She'd call me names and I would just say mm-hmm.
Well, no, that's not nice.
No, is it?
But I did have to verify through her state
she wasn't in the medical field.
Hi, Peta.
Peta, how are you, sweetheart?
Peta, my reason I scream more is because I don't.
Well, you know, and that's why I said I told him I was entertained all evening by you all night. I'd fall asleep and I'd hear something. I'd roll over and I'd look and I'd giggle.
You guys were having a good time. I just absolutely a lot. It was funny. It was a good stream last night, Bita. And then this morning, I don't know if it was a fake cry or a real cry, but it woke me up. It was funny.
Oh my god, it was funny. Yeah
Well, you know, I relate to be there because you know, I was when I was M. I was Emma's mom and
I'm a little biotin and I would be there all the time like, you know hours and hours and hours
For and like, you know for like the six months. I was the mod. I was there almost every night with her and
and then when you know
I'm not a good woman. He does a very good. Yes. He is just a beautiful person inside and out
Yes, he's wonderful
Yeah, she when you like but I bet once I but once I like stops, you know modding for like Emma that I had like a lot more
Time and that's when I really started streaming a lot
are starting streaming so, you know, it's like, you know,
we do invest a lot of time in other people's shows
and, you know, we should all, you know, start just,
It is a much seminar shows, right? Oh, absolutely. And that's why the things I'm telling you it's not
to to control or to lecture. It's just trying to help. I think, you know, sometimes handle owners
need a little outside, especially when you've been streaming these 24 sevens and people are
coming at you at all directions. You don't know who's who, what, what, and are they are they
But you know and she's like, Kate, I enjoy Kate too. You know, I don't get in the bullshit. I like going in having fun. I did listen to Sam and the other night though. Well, overnight, nobody else was on and I needed to catch up. But you know, you got to remember, you all are intertwined, every one of you.
each one of you bring something to the table.
And I find something in all of you
that you all bring to the table.
Yep, greed is bad, yeah.
KZ, someone seemed on edge.
Imagine coming online and trying to act better than others.
That's funny.
I needed to laugh.
Who's coming in here to look better than others?
Absolutely. Always check on those people, Beto.
100% is kind of why I'm here this morning.
Just checking in on him because yesterday was a little frustrating.
Yeah.
It was, you know, and you take control.
Like, Ilja, for example, yesterday you should have told him, Ilja.
It's one time, Elja, if you do not want to face your camera towards your face instead of your crotch and keep being so agitated
I'm going to take you off panel. One time
I'll be I love you. Is Scotty still going?
That was funny. Oh my god, but you know one time. That's all it should have taken from you
And if he didn't you remove him and then you bring him back and say, okay, are we gonna do it my way?
Because he was he was trying he was so itching yesterday to porn bomb you
Yeah, and I'll be honest if I wouldn't have come up when you asked me to he probably would have but I called him out
And he didn't like it when I told him get off the back of that chair and sit your butt on that chair
What he did it didn't he?
Yep
So he did
Hey, thank you. I'm just hanging with site. That's all
Casey you're welcome to come up since you think that
That's what people are talking about that. They're better than you and I have no clue why you think that
That was not intended for anything
He did Doug. You were right. He did have that perfect opportunity
And I think if he wouldn't have turned his camera off by accidents
He probably would have but I think he was adjusting his camera
That's just my opinion, but he was that itching Doug you saw that how he kept
Showing his thigh and bringing that up higher and higher
Maya you want to come up. Can you drop the link? I don't think it's been done. My old one may come up
He's asking for link
He I'm sorry Maya. Yeah, I don't think you're your links and I could be wrong. I
Can't see it on this end easy you're welcome to come up on
Oh, okay, Maya, thanks.
Yeah, I can't, when you're on stream,
you can't see if the links pinned or not.
You have to go into YouTube and look.
That's the sucky thing about it.
So I'm gonna go get a haircut today
since you didn't yesterday.
Hi, Maya.
Oh, and you know what, I ordered some sage
and some spiritual bath
So I'll take it. Oh, they're probably coming today. I think I come each day or maybe maybe Monday, but
Yeah, no bath tub streams though, okay, yeah
Oh, yeah, okay
Streams
Yeah
I'll see exactly what Reggie Deema put in there should be removed 100% that comment should be removed Reggie Deema
I demon I love you, but
Don't do that
You see that comment oh I'd be the
Okay, I will delete that comment
Hi, baby
Yeah, here's Trixie tricks
Let's see. Oh, it's the sweetest sweet cat
Don't get mad at me for saying it needed to be removed, but you know as well as I do that it needs to
She's live. I think
Go address her
Yeah, I know
No stuff like that would
can hurt you. That's what I'm talking about. Learning what hurts and when you're not paying
attention you have to have somebody in there. Oh god, here he goes again.
Wait, I'm sorry. It was a very nice fit.
I'm sorry, people are...
I'm sorry.
I am going to do something, say, open in a second.
Would you, only you and I?
to go to my subscriptions, okay.
I know, I'm gonna, I'll delete it,
but hold on, I'm just trying to get the tricks right.
Hold on.
Hold on a second, too.
Okay, it's removed.
OK, look what I put in back.
Do not say it out loud because others do not know that most people do not know.
Very few.
OK, because because I that that does it a lot as a ghost.
Just enough my eye and then nobody gets play.
OK, you see what I'm saying?
Yes.
it's funny because the person never types, but they remove comments.
Okay.
Done.
You like that.
Yeah, I like that.
Yeah.
You talked about it yesterday.
I said to him, I should probably tell him what I got, what I do.
But now I'm gonna tell you some very far and few between people know about that. Okay
Yeah, I'm I'm I'm removing some of these comments. I did I'm removing it's okay
That's what I said
Hi Miguel
And see like Miguel
It's it's getting to be a better channel that you'll be able to come up and talk to site
Right
Yeah, yeah, he's been on again
Good. I'm glad to hear that because he likes that
Yeah, you know, he's knowing people
Yeah
Yeah, he's a good guy always like to talk to him
And those comments and those comments don't worry about it. They're taking care. Okay
Just know when you got the people in here that they still show up on StreamYard
Yeah, well if you know all the comments show up on the StreamYard
But not, but I have to turn on all comments and I'm in the chat because like a lot of the comments get filtered with like, they're spamming early.
So, hope everyone's doing good in the chat. Good morning, guys.
It's 7.24 a.m., so we're all up early this morning.
Yes, it's 10.24. Hey, Amanda, did you send me that email? I haven't looked at my email, so did you send me that email on the Medicare and Medicaid things?
Hi Miguel
Hello
Good morning
Me hot day it's hot New York Miguel does your mom?
Do you have an air conditioner for your mom?
It's okay Tommy Jones
I'm sorry
More how much today 110 today Wow
Tommy come on
See you money hate money stay cool
Hi, guys. Oh, we have a pretty active chat this morning. 37 people. We do have money for it, Sonny.
So, Miguel, you do have an air conditioner, hun? Mm-hmm. Okay, make sure mom's drinking water. Okay.
You know how I gotta take care of mom
Yeah
Amanda stay cool today, I know it's hot over there too. I'm used to this heat and humidity. That's that's normal for me
No, you're better off. Apparently, there's a little few problems going on.
So anyway, what else is going on today?
Well, we're going to copy.
Oh, there you go.
Are they delivering it to you or are you coming to going to get it?
They're delivering it, but it's $3 off.
Oh, well, I would do that too.
Yeah.
You're saying?
Oh miss beta you never alone, baby girl never ever ever
Perfect fortunately
This would be pretty much the exact same as if I was to get myself
Yeah, three dollars off is pretty good
It's impressive.
Of course, God, he's under a Persian spell.
Oh my God.
Vita, I don't know how you were sitting there.
He was so cute.
What's funny?
Boys and Frog, how you doing this morning, Zedart?
Okay, so that's on his way.
So maybe that'll give me some energy.
Well, I didn't even finish my beer last night.
Even after, even after a sleep stream?
No, I didn't finish, no, I didn't.
Oh well, right? Oh, it was really, oh really?
It's, it's 8 a.m.
Morning.
Good morning.
How are you this morning?
My bad for what I wrote in the chat, but it's got to be said. All right. I'm not it's not no trouble
I'm just here to defend my own name because I'm okay
I've got called faggot and none of you motherfuckers did anything to stop the people from talking shit on my name
So for that, I thank you so much because you Americans are so fake and your race is towards me
Yeah, if I was American you defend me, but you know what it's all good. Have a great day
Fuck your channels. Yeah, let's see if your channel stays up yours and be as in everyone else's
Let's see how long your channel stay up for but thank you very much for letting me out
Thank you. Have a wonderful day and be a fuck your dad. Your dad is gay. Yeah, thank you whole family
Thank you psych
Reggie, it's okay, huh?
Whoa, whoa
I don't think it was Bita that said that. I think it was somebody else
Well, he's not even I said though, it's not too early for him
Sorry Bita, oh Miguel dropped off. Oh Miguel. Well, you know, and he doesn't like conflict either
Yeah
Oh gosh
Care cake oatmeal platform that sounds really good
Carrot cake oatmeal I love carrot cake that is like my most favorite
favorite
cake there is
Oh my gosh. Yeah, it's a little drama apparently
I remember you always see it in
Okay, my channel I'm gonna pin by link
Yes, anybody else like to come up
We're just hanging today
Okay, let's see
I
Think it's going down
You way I think he's all it keeps up. It's not it's not on the
I got a pin now. Yeah
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, let's start the day out fresh. Good morning
Morning, morning, morning, Doug
Morning raging
Good morning
Everyone
Yes, morning everyone
How's everyone doing today? Let's see. Life is too short for a nonsense.
Say sorry quickly. Forget people who matter the most to you and fuck creators. Yeah.
Yeah. That's what you do. You know, sometimes you just need time out from people's.
Walk away. Yeah. Right.
Also, I've been seeing like the topic of like worms and stuff like that people you know, you know
You know, you know, I mean people like to talk about talk about worms, you know, they're talking about
Why did you think that? Oh, they're like, you know, there's things called
Earworms, and you know, you know earworm is yeah, they're yeah, they're here with yeah
The earworm is a brain
Yeah, they get into the brain. Yeah, there is a day of JFK has had one. You know that, right?
Well, I mean you're thinking about like literal earworms, but I'm talking about an earworm is like
Some say few things people will say that they try to get into your ear that they want you to like obsess over and
So it's people say they'll get into your head that you start obsessing over like, you know, so a lot of people will
But the sad thing about that the sad thing about that because you know
And it's it's true
It'd be human person if you tell them a lie ten times
They start to believe it if you tell yourself a lie ten times you start to believe it
And I think people who have a conscience that that those are the ones it bothers more
Mm-hmm because those types of people always go back and evaluate their day or their life
And then it bothers them
Yep
I'm just saying that so that ours our studio is
Reggie's human it's yeah, it's like I said, it's good. You'll see it on on stream yard
And as a fake mermaid
Yeah, we are like people people imitate other people
But you know imitation is the biggest flatter you can give towards somebody
What do you think about how many fake fake fake people that are first in any people in shafts, you know
Here's Miguel's back
What do I think about what I'm sorry people that try to imitate other people in the chat like you know
Well, I look at it that you know
And I told Jamie this yesterday. When they do it to me, at least they're leaving anybody else alone who can't handle it. Not everybody can handle it.
Welcome back, Miguel.
Yeah, I can't bag. That's pretty hot.
Yeah. Well, even your phones are probably going to get hot today.
No, I see everyone
My cop copies on the way already he says you're gonna say shit about me
The Richard on piano
Don't read something
And I really, I know you talk about that time, but then, you know, they're back.
Oh, oh, my God, I'm sorry.
You know, I kind of thought that time because
he apologized to me this morning, but you know something?
It's the right, Doug, and he's being sincere, and I appreciated that.
I did. I mean, I will call out when you're a nasty person, but I will definitely call out
when you're kind to somebody.
100% because not a lot of people can actually apologize. You know, say, I am sorry or what
that and I love you are the three hardest. Those are the six hardest words to say in
the American language. Did you know that? I am sorry and I love you. I just find that
Aw, Doug, that's so sweet.
I think if we all would mimic Doug,
Doug's going to spread positivity for the next 48 hours.
But it's subject to change.
But that's okay.
You know, you gotta at least try.
Morning, olden, how are you this morning, sweetheart?
Hi, time.
I want it to be positive.
And instead of you know, you might be like, you know people fight a little bit, but um, you know, we're always gonna roast people are always gonna roast
That's human nature, but you can roast in a different way
Yeah
Then there's you can be kind about it or you can be cruel about it
I think
Just be kind. Oh
Lurdy shouldn't be like
I hope you guys can get lost.
Sit down, sit down.
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
Real friends can get in fights, right?
Oh my gosh.
So what else is on the agenda?
What's, when's your coffee coming?
It's on its way.
Oh come on
These are cast they say I'm so positive. I try to be positive. I do want to be positive guys
I do want people to work out their stuff, but it's like they're people are gonna fight like it's like I can't
You know, I can't you can't referee at all, but you know
Take it elsewhere to fight, you know, it's there's nothing and everything you're talking about didn't happen here
Didn't happen here. Keep it moving
We're all going to follow Doug today
Doug is our role model for the day. I bet Doug never thought I'd say that
I
Yeah, I want to go
You're not going out though, right?
Mmm. No, yeah, I'm going out
Okay, because it's awfully hot for you to be out there today
That he can overtake you really easy
And you up it you guys up in New York aren't used to this my son's up there, and he's like mom
I'm dying. I like well you're heading down this way
I'll be he'll be down here this weekend my son and granddaughter
From New York to spend the summer with me
As I said yesterday, I'm trying to find a nice small little trip to do
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
Like you can't control other people's behavior. No, you can't. Well, you can't hear
Right, you can't hear
Yeah
Yeah, so pretty exciting
Dougie Doug donated five memberships this morning and then
We got ten we I donated five yesterday. I'll go to donate five yesterday and
So
Have some more members coming into you. Thank you to all the members. I
Um had my bank
money stolen out of it
Almost a little a little over a little over 10k. Oh my god. I know so I've had to close everything
started all over again, so I don't have anything connected to my phone at this
time. Nothing, because I'm so afraid. Yeah, I know that sounds terrible. And
imagine if that was the last penny I had to pay bills. Yeah, I mean it took me two
weeks to get it back from the bank. Two weeks.
Hey
We're hanging out this morning with Christine. We got Miguel here. I got my coffee on the way
Waking up a little bit
It's awesome
Links pinned
He ordered his coffee because he got three dollars off. So he doesn't have to go get it today. I
Haven't I am in iced coffee this morning
My son took part in most of my iced coffee. I'm like on his way to work. I'm like, wait a minute
You're going out and about just stop and get your coffee because no, I like yours better. Okay, bye
Right that's funny. Oh truth zone. Are you in back?
Sorry truth that's all good
Good morning, it's been hot it's been hot as a fish grease to pass four days man. It's been crazy hot
Well, it's been pretty pretty like you know normal, right? It's a little bit warm, but yeah a little bit on the warmer side
the
which downstairs and set at 78 the upstairs is set at 76, you know, cuz heat rises, but
It's keeping the humidity out. That's what we're dealing with
One and all day
Your thermostat is still it is still if it's a hundred some degrees outside. It'll read it at like 78 77
Yeah, well, and I got it 70 but they say because you know I have two air conditioners and upstairs and a downstairs one
They say that when they run non-stop if you set it lower and they're running on stop it burns your air conditioners out
And trust me I did my air conditioners are newer and I surely can't live without one for the summer here in Florida
Right, right they heat down there's a trochan, right? Yeah, it's horrible. It's future
Horrible
Man salute to the chest. Shout out to everybody. You know, I rarely come up here. So, you know, I had to come up here
Chopper I see you here. So I'm thinking I come up for a little bit
Yeah, I'm not gonna lie here
Do you have a topic today? Yeah, I always got a top, you know, listen, I got a top
About one so I can go live every day with a different topic with a different topic
Huh you always stay on topic your your stream always stays on topic. I just find that so funny because most
You know when contention arises between you know some of my panelists some of the guests on my panel
You know the topic can you know straight away from you know because they get up there get the argument with each other
So it can at times like my topic yesterday the other day my last one was World War three
And somehow we just ventured off and start talking about other things but that you know, that's understandable. I get it
Yeah
When you start talking about something like that here now, you know
People kind of want to block that out and that's where they go into other topic
Yeah, right, you know contention arises because a lot of people they be having problems with each other just like over here
Nowhere else
Once you start the most I might get to call somebody man. You a dumb mother mother
I don't fucking cuss over him. Somebody says I say a man. You won dumb motherfuckers
That's when the whole topic you just put it in the trash can it's over with
Yeah, pretty nice
But it's okay. Oh job wasn't in chat, but never came up. I don't know what's up with that
Maybe he's changing into his guilt
So man somebody Doug be asked where I was from. Yeah
I'm from Lowell, Kentucky man the same place a summer Dickerson is from shout the summer
No shout out summer shout out to the Midwest and you know salute to the Midwest
Yeah
We I had a great talks with you, so we talked about some
Interesting as I know my main thing with conspiracy is I think that there's like a
The media is very like, you know, if you watch anything like especially like the news state the regular news, you know, it's just so
It's oh you took off, but
It's a yeah, it's pretty I think there's a lot of psyops and there's a lot of like mind control and
trying to social engineer things through
The the media which they've been, you know, it's pretty obvious that they've been doing that
Get to realize there are the cultures like a lot of results of a lot of the media as a
Question is like do we the media like
Cop like copy humans, or do we copy them copy the media?
You would do we do gotta have that dialogue because we talked about it a long time ago
I think on summer's panel, but I was like it was like what out busy today working that day
So I really couldn't indulge in the dialogue with you man. I really couldn't
But yeah, you say we say conspiracy theories
You take a somebody to where the tin foil had me. I don't really look at a conspiracy theory is it's just common sense
You know, you go you have to question everything and you know
That's just what it is. You know, we've been programmed
You can say I don't say I hate y'all well
We've been indoctrinated, you know until like just following the narratives about everything
They tell you the skies if they tell you skies perp
We have to go with it if they tell you that God in the Bible exists
You have to go with it instead of instead of just thinking for yourself and questioning everything
Who remember that movie the bugs life?
Little smart at one little small and started questioning everything. I mean, what the hell am I why am I here serving this queen at all my life?
You see what I'm saying?
So the same goes for us. It's you got a question everything man. Yeah. Yeah, it's like because
We're presented with a lot of stories and it's like a lot of stories are like, you know
And it gets into like, you know stuff that happens
We don't we don't even get say too much of the all these cohorts like, you know school
You know this happens at schools with people come in with their guns and stuff like that
Those you can't question any of the narrative of those stories and so
Because it's like, oh, how you know, I think it's like you're insulting the families, you know
Yeah, but if you look into that big famous one
SA and DUI HO ok
If you look into that one like a lot of these families they were their actors and you know
So you get it a lot of those you know those
So-called mass shootings like the sandy hook that was clear as day crisis actor
Side-up operation. You can just see clear as day. Yeah, that happens. Yeah for sure
Do I say this all the time? Why wouldn't they spend this? You know, they control the media. We don't control none of these
Mainstream media outlets such as CNN Fox, MSNBC and etc. We don't you gotta think they they invest over
Almost a trillion dollars a year
Towards a propaganda
So they have the resources, you know to pull off anything they wanted in a given time because it's their shit
It's not ours. You look at it from them
Somebody asked me the other day a truce on why would they lie to us? I say why would they lie to you, bro? This is their shit
Why would they lie to you man?
No, that's what they that's what they do, but you know, we're never gonna change it
They've been doing it for decades. The only thing is that the world is waking up. I hope
Rafael you're not hidden we see you hun
Yep. No, I don't see I don't see too many people waking up
It's not even it's not even about being a walk or being conscious
It's just about using your discernment being able to use discernment and you know think logically and think for yourself
That doesn't exist too much in this world because you have too many
I don't want to go there on this channel you got to me man. You got peace
You got so many people that just they let the TV
The TV thing throws all that thinking for it for them man. They have a phone in their hand smart phones
The fucking phone is smarter than them. Oh trust me my phone's smarter than me
I'll be the first to admit it
But then I've also learned that my phone's only as smart as I've learned to do with it because there are things
It's like why can't I do this? I know I can do this
But I won't do it because I don't know how to do it
Yes, I might call me a crisis actor
I'm sure I'm sure not getting paid for it man. I think give me the money. Give me the money show me the money
Listen, listen, they got they give me a $10,000 check. I go out there and put on a whole charade
I put on a whole show. I'll turn into I'll turn into a soap opera man
My dog gets my cat gets stuck in the tree. Oh, man, they did dog mouths. I swear
Morning taco show
Yeah
Okay, I'm sorry Katrina. Yeah, I mean, I don't know. I just thought I saw you know a few of them or though
I mean, I'm sure listen listen my ass sandy something in the chat. Listen listen to me
And everyone can it can kind of agree
That the moon landing was fake you can just look at it and tell a man they shot this in the studio
If I would have been alive back in 1968 and seen them with my with the discernment
I have now and seen them, you know orchestrating this fake ass
Folklore move the moon landing I'd have been like back then a man this shit look like what what studio they shoot that in
They don't even look real. How's their wind on the fucking moon?
So we can agree that you know the moon landing was staged, right?
So why wouldn't they stage why wouldn't they stage anything else think about it like that?
That's how you gotta look at it, right? Yeah, that's it. Thanks. Yeah
Yeah, and if you but it also choose don't have you notice like because I I always watched I watched a lot and study like a lot of
the news and I would notice a lot of a
Lot of code words a lot of they would wear like I see like Tiffany blue and and they didn't purple
They would wear a lot and like different
like different like certain colors they would wear like symbology it's called symbology yeah
they might wear red they might wear blue because red represents you know red house blue house politics
purple is a royal color so yeah they and they'll put 33 32 7 11 different numerical codes inside
it yeah you know i'm talking about yeah yeah for sure yeah 32 32 uh personified skull and bones
so if you able to catch that you know what i'm talking about bro yeah so yeah
Yeah, they'll be number y'all numbers, too
There'll be certain numbers again and certain things
Certain cases will be very orchestrated. I think some of the most obvious ones was remember when that submarine there was like these guys
They took one of those submarines down. It was like this and I think a little
Little cool be underwater vehicle and they went to like look at the Titanic or something like that and they all and they
You know, they died, you know, and if you look at their names their names are all like
But like Kingfisher, I mean there's just like there's just like certain names like or they use presidents that you'll see
There's sort of Masonic names, too
Like there's some
Right, right
And you mentioned, you just mentioned the red and blue, the red and blue is for the red, is red house, blue house, Masonic lodges, too
Yeah
And also you look for like the checkerboard like the black and white checkerboard
Yeah, it's all it's all basic
What does the checkerboard represent? It represents Freemasonry
Oh, no, no, it's like they they they also like take like games like chess very seriously and
Also, like it's like the black and the white and so it's like this
Yeah, the black and the white night and day
It represents polarity and then yeah, and then think about it like this
They have black and white people always, you know in the eyes it gets one another
So they were used as a chess piece on the chessboard to yes
Exactly. It's like yeah, there's always like that's always like they're always putting very divisive
racially divisive news stories up, you know, like, you know, we're in it for things like the George Floyd case were
You know that
But what they're doing is not a new tactic man the Roman Empire did it divide and conquer bread and circus
That's all it is. It's the same
Concept of ideology, you know being regurgitated on different civilizations in different time periods
So what they're doing now with the whole divide and conquer with these with these racial division division of
Psydups, it's just it's yeah, it's basic
I look at it like man if I was if I had a world that had eight billion people in it
Well, 300 something million people in this country per se if I had that many people on one geographical landmass, and I wanted to control them
I would easily just use the news media think about what Hitler did. It's the same shit. His media is propaganda man
Yeah, it's already it's so basic
So someone doesn't he's a conspiracy theory. He's correct. This is basic man simple
You know that goes back to me saying that if you tell yourself a lie 10 times you can convince yourself
It's the truth
That's why it's like it's that's why they like to get these ideas in our head or like or lies and like, you know
How then they get out of it repeated often enough everyone believes them, you know
It's just it's it's also that there's like the 100 monkeys where it's like once a hundred people figure out something like pretty much
Everyone figures it out. Well, it's like
But also I think look at look at like a case like the OJ case like um, think about how
How interesting it was but also how how how much it divided the races and things like that because here he is like a black man
He's expert it. He's an actor
He's famous and football player and then a white what it's a beautiful white woman
and there is a Jewish guy too and so and then
Think about how racially divisive that was at the time and I kind of
Let me ask everybody a question over the past 20 odd years right for the past 10 years
You really don't see those are Siberians were the Native Americans they really Siberians, but that's besides the point you don't see them
Being utilized in the news media, you know, but you will never see a Native American telling that Chinese person in the news all this major
News organization spending it 24-7 all day every day. That just never happens
There's always a so-called black person and a white person
You know killing one another doing something detrimental to one another and the news media is using it as
Is utilizing it as a
division tactic
To the father keep the the keep the division going but you never see nobody else
No other ethnicity of people doing it to each other, right? And it's I'm trying to say
We've never seen a Native American George Floyd never right. We never seen a Native American being choked out on camera
And it being you know
Celebrities coming out being in support of it the news media say hey, this is a this is a tracities
These tracities don't need to keep happening. We need it. We need to change things
We need to we need to put new laws in place. We need a you said I'm trying to say yeah
Well, that's the problem reaction solution. It's like you they create the problem to get this reaction that they
Used to bring in a solution which they had planned by creating the problem in the first place
The solution was already planned out. But they gave the problem
It's like, you know, you're good, bro. That's why I'm so damn, you know, you're shit, bro. Damn. I like that respect, bro
It's because yes, you it's funny. You mentioned that it's called hingillian dialect principalities. Yeah
Order about chaos because that's a double-headed eagle and freemasonry
Yep already about chaos. We bring it. They bring in the chaos and then what comes later order the same thing during the 2020 epidemic
What came and what happened in the infancy of the epidemic period chaos?
What came towards the back end order the order was the annihilation, right?
Hey, go take this go take this annihilation things to go back to normal
So that's order the chaos is everybody being confused going into these stores
Bout of all the toilet paper people are people are can confound it people losing their minds and then they bring the order
It's it's it's simple man. It's simplistic
yep, and
Yeah, that's how the world
Really works, and that's even like the political parties that are like two two wings on one bird
You know, they that's why there's two and it can't that's also like, you know, they have the two the red and blue
Democrats Republicans, you know, so that's kind of like the black and the white every mistake they
It's just they use dualities, they just play, we play on each other and there's a lot of them.
Katrina and I, in summer, made tin foil hats one time.
We did, didn't we, Katrina?
All right, so I'm sad, I hate to get up here and sing, but you know, to me, man, I don't go for the old
10 for somebody there's a 10 for had word be like a man. We got the aliens and reptilians and
That's all spooky shit. I ain't I ain't trying to hear all this spooky shit
Yeah, saying that the earth with that. That's all spookism. But like far as like just people just gotta learn how to use common
Sense man. Don't take everything
Somebody said especially somebody with a suit and tie
Yeah
Especially somebody with a fucking suit and tie on the damn ties and noose go hang yourself with that motherfucker
Hmm
Think about it what what?
Somebody that's ultra rich
There's never had to struggle up even rake of fucking
Some some leaves a cut of string of fucking grass before in their life
How would they be able to resonate with somebody that works?
80 hours in two weeks and they're ultra rich. The only thing they know is the high life
How can they resonate with you think about it like that?
Yeah, I mean
You know, but we know we do coexist and it's like, you know, we do have even a pretty good standard of living in America and
You know, I don't know people you know, but yeah, there's different worlds. Really. It's like there's different worlds
Now I've always thought for myself, man
I you know, I've always considered myself to be an intelligent man even when I was younger
You know, I always question everything even in school. I always just
All this shit that would feel right to me. I'm thinking myself then why we gotta go to school all day to learn a bunch of learn about a bunch of nothing
It's like we're being sent away put on a bus
Sent to us sent to this place where a bunch of strangers is just is beat me over the head
With their with their ideologies that I really can't align with it
Like you know, yeah, even with the whole church thing
believing in a Jesus of Messiah and stuff like that
Yeah
I mean, that's like, I mean, religion is like, you know, programming and, and, uh, you know, even the early education is programming.
And it's basically, you know, thinking, you know, the textbooks, they basically, they teach the mythology of history to the youngest people and like, you know,
you learn about George Washington, the cherry tree and Washington's teeth were made of, made of wood.
And it turns out that you know, it's darker and darker every year this week
You know most of our history is folklore it's folk. Yeah, it's his stories. It's not yours, man
We gotta go learn about George Washington and Andrew Jackson. Who the hell are these people man these we gotta go learn about pirates
To be already all the way Frank. Yeah, these were number pirates
So I'm we have to go learn about a bunch of pirates and losers. They were undesirables George Washington
Todd all the more undesirables man. They were all fucking undesirables from Europe. There was the fled persecution
Pieces of shit
Well, yeah, I think there was I know many were many were and
I mean, all the founding fathers, you know, I think that that's the secret kind of religion of the country
Right. So I'm not saying we go to school to learn
I feel like the basic things that we go to school for is to read and write all the other stuff
It can you consider a mythicism a folklore the basic things is just being able to comprehend
Read and write. That's it
Like learned about the moon landing and learned about we spent on a fucking ball at a hundred thousand miles of power
Oh, that's mythicism, man. Who can prove it? How the hell are we spending on a ball through the abyss of space?
That's physically impossible
Stand up right now spending the circle for a minute straight
You're gonna be dizzy and throwing up so how the fuck are we spending on a rock further into the abyss of space? Come on, man
Well, yeah, well, yeah, it's too big. I mean, it sounds like Maracas. I mean
Is that Apollo Apollo? I bet you won't hit that link
Yeah, now I think but I think the bridge really weird stuff is like the all these drones and stuff like that and now they're
You know, have you seen music in there? No, it's kind of with this
I don't want to give you some of these projects name on my on my show, but it's something it's about a
Kind of an alien invasion, and they've kind of tested it on us a few times to see how we react
It's not a real one. It's a
They said what made you what made you start started?
To question everything what like something stuff that you talk about man, you know, I heard I've been hearing over the past
15 years so what made you
Oh, well, I've just been, you know, very interested in, like, you know, different conspiracy theories interested in, you know, the occult and secret societies and so, you know, and I've just always, you know,
learned a question, you know, I've just always questioned things. I've always questioned things and I've always been able to, like, see kind of
Beyond things that I recognize patterns. I'm really into recognizing patterns and like so and also really into
Numerology and so yeah, I'll recognize like the
Different like numerology and that different like serial killer cases or things like that like a gosh like a John Wayne case
He had like 33 victims
And then if you like watch that they have a video of them taking the body that a John Wayne case his house
And it's like a bunch of guys in sports jerseys. They all have numbers on them
And so then there's like and always like some kind of numerology
Numerological significance and it just seems like it was like some of these cases is made to have make you appear like serial killers
And like that's a kind of scare people and
But I think some of these serial killers cases are like just so
There's so many things to them that this seems like they're they're not
Yeah, connecting dots there definitely because there's there the art that you put like little tells in for people that have eyes to see
That they want to like think they like to leave like little signals and stuff in stuff to like so people can recognize it like
It's easy to pick up on somebody says spin a Disney from the Earth spinning. Yeah, that's physically impossible
That's pseudo science their own science is a theoretical concept
These are just theoretical time
These are just theoretical concepts that they come up with and people take it and they take it in strides
So that's what I'm saying like if you went to a amusement park right now and got on one of those goddamn rides
The word spins in a circle and you get off that motherfucker. You're dizzy
It's the same thing they're saying that the earth is spinning that how fast
23,000 miles per hour. So how the hell we will be able to fill it then if it was spinning, we will be able to
We will be able to fill it. So they're defying that they're defying their own idealism. So that in return, I would call it pseudo science
pseudo means fake
Approval so to me it's pseudo science. Like how you telling me that we're spending come on bogey. Come on, man
Listen, man
Yeah, I mean
Gravity is a theory to gravity is a very good gravity hasn't been proven
The concept of gravity came out in the late 1800s. You can go look it up
Look it up right now. Gravity is a theory a theory hasn't been proven, right?
Well, right
Right, so that's what grab the look of gravity. It's just a it's a scientific theory. It hasn't been proven
Yep
Right. Yeah. Well, also, you know, even if you even like, you know, physics, like the first thing my physics teacher said to us on like the first day was like, well, physics is bullshit. You know, he's like, this is all.
Mine told me that too.
They did.
I'm like, well, then why am I paying for this class?
That's great.
Yeah, but I guess it, but it is true because it's like they all, it's just all.
Man made sick man sick man's concept. Well, so much so much is man's concept. Like we're the only people that you know have
These sciences like you know, we're the one that's considered these groups
Name anything my bae
If I took you and grabbed you by your arms right now and spend it's fun to around for two minutes straight, bro
You will be dizzy. It's shit. You wouldn't be able to stand up, right?
so
If we're spinning on a ball, and how fast they say, what,
10, 20,000, however fast they say we're spinning,
we wouldn't be able to live here.
That would be physically impossible.
So at that point, with that statement,
with that theoretical concept, that would be pseudoscience.
That would be considered pseudoscience.
Yep.
I mean, and then, you know,
pseudoscience is gonna be dangerous, you know, or...
Love love people do it love unhealthy medical experimenting on themselves. Thanks gravity is fake. Oh, it's a theory, bro
Not a fake homo. Give me a second very back
You know, yeah, we got into his his little realm of what he likes
Yeah
Yeah, and it's a very interesting channel
Yeah, take out shoes on channel
It's very interesting. I go there sometimes.
It's slightly bigger than...
Here you are.
Yeah. Well, I think, you know, it's interesting about...
You've watched the movie Cabin in the Woods.
Like Cabin in the Woods is like an interesting movie about...
It has kind of a conspiracy twist to it.
But at one point he tries to come out of the...
He tries to like get out of the area and he crashes into this dome.
I think there's like a firmament, kind of a dome over us.
I don't know if we're spinning around,
but I don't know if we're spinning around.
I don't know if the earth is flat,
because I think we can see an airplane going around.
We've been on an airplane.
We know if we keep flying the airplane around,
we're actually gonna get back to the beginning.
So it's not like we could fall.
It's not like we'd fall off the edge of the earth.
Well, I don't know because I was dizzy yesterday and then this morning just just now
You kind of moved too fast. I think I have an inner ear infection
But I felt dizzy and and I always connect dizzy where I need to eat a piece of toast
In my money
But I would but but I was you know
I was programmed that way. I guess when I was little and I didn't feel well or I felt dizzy or I had a headache
My mom would always feed me a piece of toast. So I was programmed that way
Put me on the big screen
Come on, put me on the big screen
It's a pseudo. Yeah, it's pseudo signs. Well, look up pseudo
It says right here gravity is considered a theory. Now, hold on. Let's look up. Let's look at what what what the three means
So gravity hasn't been proven, right? So it's just an idea. So it's a theoretical. It's a theoretical concept, right?
So let's look up where on the way it says right here
Let's look at what theory means
God damn
It says right here
Theory not strong I says theories never became facts. So a theory is not a fact, bro. It's not factual
Yeah, right here go ahead. I got the right one here
It says right here
Damn, it's the wrong goddamn
Okay, well really it's like, you know
Right here says theories never became facts so a theory it hasn't been proven man
It's just an ideal or a concept
So that's why gravity hasn't been proven. It's just a fucking theory, bro. That's all it is man
but that's what's all I wanted to say
Okay, but it's like approving gravity is like
Proving like, you know
There's magic exists or like those certain things. You think that's telepathy. It's like there's it's like really
It can be maybe it has made for it and no experiments made, but I don't think we can ever really solve exactly
And a truth about it. It's like, you know, we can just unprovable this is it's met
It's why it's called metaphysics and you know and physics and you know, it's like this is that we really can't
There's some things we'll never understand
It says it says it's based off of somebody else's hypothesis and assumed somebody the guy name is so what's his name Gabriel Newton?
He assumed that gravity was keeping us, you know grounded on this ground. It was an assumption
I couldn't make it as I can make an assumption right now about Christine. Does that make it does that make it?
Does it have any validity to it? No, I can say a Christine Christine. Um, she can fly
That's an assumption that would be that would be a theoretical concept a theory of minds about her
But that doesn't give it any validity. That doesn't mean it's correct. It's just a fucking assumption a theory
right
Yeah, and you know scientists for for centuries decades have been trying to figure this out to show proof
Because we are the type of people there's two types of people there's people that okay
I'll believe you because I don't know how to get to from point a to point z the way you are
So I'm just going to believe you because
You made it sound believable because this is what happens and then you got people like truth don't tell me
Well, you know, you can tell me to your blue in the face, but until you prove it to me
I'm not it's about to be a headshot somebody said a theory in a scientific in a scientific theory is different
But a scientific theory is not a fact bro headshot. Hold on headshot
You just killed yourself. Oh
It says right no a scientific theory is not a fact man. That's what it says right here, bro
Yeah, and that theory has been confirmed I don't think it's based on facts, so
But you know when you sit there and start thinking about things you really wonder those are the things that make you go hmm
They are
They're making their their things that make you go hmm
Yeah, that's right mojo Joe
Don't you don't feel it you don't feel it go yeah exactly you don't you don't feel it going fast
But maybe if you're outside you're you know if you put when you're inside you
But if you were outside on top of the plane you would you would feel it going fast, huh?
Man, I don't need listen man. He's just common sense to me like they tell me they were they were spent
What's up
Yeah, but if there is a matrix that means the matrix can be hacked right and so and there are probably like different hacks
We keep that would be there's things little things we could do to make things easier in here
Maybe change things in our favor
There was it there was it doesn't want
Yeah, remember that we are having
About that they say the earth is spinning at a thousand miles per hour, bro
Thank about if you got in your car right now your car spent at a thousand miles per hour
You wouldn't be able to live you wouldn't be able to sit in your car. You would be dead
Yep, you can feel when your cars go you can feel when you go in a hundred miles per hour down the highway
Imagine being in your car and your car is spinning at a thousand miles per hour
You would be you would physically be able to feel that right right around
the
That we're spinning at a thousand miles per hour on a fucking ball, bro
You know, you don't even want to get on the flat earth
I don't I don't these are just these are two different religions gold earth flat earth is just a it's out of allergy
Man, it's a fucking religion, bro. I don't buy that to me. I'm saying me personally
Somebody else might give validity to it, but me my own personal perspective on it is pseudo science to me, bro
Yeah, you know, I have
But that's my own personal perspective on it. It's little signs. Yeah
Well, you know, they're like a lot in the in this
In this realm of
The physics and metaphysics there are there is a lot of pseudoscience and there's your name
There's gonna be a lot of things that well, I don't make sense
Hold on a time can you prove without using somebody else's synopsis a hypothesis that we're spinning physically when it comes to physics
Can you prove that we're spinning on a fucking ball at a thousand miles problem, bro?
Respectfully, can you prove that without going off masses hypothesis, bro?
Can you prove it? I bet you can't
You would you would have to reference what they say, bro
We're going my bed
Yeah, well
Everyone's doing good in chat. I see that you know a lot of people here
Yeah, but it's like at the end of the days. It's like it's just like space travel. It's like
People have called them
Faking that shit in front of a green square in front of a green screen with strings connected to him, bro
It's out of a student. Oh, they have been busted
Calls of times
Faking it fake go on a spate, bro. They have been busted. So why would it be out of the imagine any?
Any stretch of the imagination from the fake all that shit, bro? Why wouldn't it? Yeah
I know, well, it's because, you know, but think about billions of dollars that goes to these, these agencies, you know,
like, and, you know, billions of dollars goes to space travel. And even if we can go to space, if there's nothing on any of the planets,
like what we can, like, you know, do scientific experiments and like, there's nothing like,
is there anything that can, like, help, there's no information I think we've ever gotten from space travel that has given us anything interesting.
That it could be used to help us. It's just like, you know, it's basically fantasy fantasy and stuff, you know
Amazon yesterday went up and put some satellites up there. I think Amazon's gonna start their own internet service
There this is twice now. They've done that
Nice
Yeah, it's like, uh, that'd be, you know, Amazon's pretty much taken over. There's, you know, there's a few
huge companies in the world and you know, you know, Amazon is like the number one for internet shopping and
Yeah, oh my gosh. I get I get Amazon delivery every day
and my granddaughter gets so excited and if I don't get it, she's like,
grandma, what happened? We didn't get a package today.
So I purposely got to make sure I send a little...
Apollo, you can't even speak English fluently.
You have broken English. You sound like a fucking...
You sound like an AI machine. You sound like a fucking robot.
You can barely talk. Shut your ass up.
Let alone barely think for yourself.
Yeah, that's...
You was great and was so broke.
That name was made yesterday
You don't understand that now you don't you don't even understand anything. I've been saying bro
They told you to spell physicians over there on our TPP's panel. You couldn't even spell that bro
You don't even know what that mean true. So that name was made yesterday. I'm not sure it's a man
Office. Oh, yeah pause but again. Oh, man. All right come up. I'm sorry Christine. Go ahead. Oh, it's okay
I just want to let you know that I don't think it's saying I mean it may be they might have made a new
I'm not gonna
Everybody thinks for themselves man
I'm not I'm not gonna force somebody to think like me and
Somebody else shouldn't force me to think like them. I have my own my own opinions. You know, I uh
I come up with my own hypothesis on things man. I just think for myself
I've been and I feel like that's the best way for everybody to think just think for yourself man
Don't take my word for it. Don't take nasa's word for it. Don't take the government's word for it
Don't take your school teachers word for it if it doesn't if it doesn't align with your intuition
You know, if it doesn't align what you would consider just logical thinking man, throw it in the trash man
Thank you. That's all I that's all I'm saying when you think for yourself, man
That's what you have your own brain in your head for everybody has their own fucking brain in their head
That way you can think for yourself
Don't be high-minded. Don't go along to get along. What's that old saying if everybody jumps off the bridge
You're gonna jump to don't be a don't be a follower be a leader man
my son my son's the leader of jumping off bridges trust me I saw it one day myself
Like you down off that bridge there's alligators in that water. What is wrong with you people?
Yeah, oh my god, let's say that's what he did they were jumping off the bridge into the river a river filled with
Alligators and his friends wouldn't do it. He goes just watch it's easy. I'll do it and show you I'm like, oh my god
Of course, it's my kid
He was leading the stupidity
Time you can you can hit the link you can have a dialogue bro. We can have civilized dialogue, bro
You ain't got to talk to me in the check
Everybody not everybody panels, you know, there's a few that just don't that's okay. You know why they don't you know
Why they don't panel because they're gonna sound retarded. That's why
He's gonna be gonna sound stupid. That's what's gonna happen. He knows it
Mm-hmm. I used to know how to handle now I become that hand
My beat up is logic. I'm gonna beat him up. I'm not talking about physically beating him up. I'm gonna beat up his logic
You're gonna get her stunk fuck with me I
Ain't the smartest man walking but I know I'm surrounded by a bunch of fucking idiots that can't think for themselves
And I know a bunch of zombies can't fuck with me
If there's always a thousand zombies chasing two niggas that can think for themselves in the movie, right?
Those two people that's that they're being chased by a thousand zombies. Those are the two people that can think for themselves
There's always a fucking fuck a flock of two thousand zombies this brain did
They don't think
I'll be right back. Okay
Well, you know very of what's very true that there's a
Seems to be like a lot of followers and like a few leaders, right? Or else they're just be like, but I think if there's a
Lot of leaders like I don't know. I'd like to create leaders
But you have you have to have followers. Yeah
That's like, you know, but it's like already if they're following they're following that they're not like a
I don't know the following they're not a position to lead I think I mean it's like if they're just a follower
You know, it's like I think like a leader is basically focused on on their own their own thing
But I I would like you know, I don't think I I would like to create other or help to create other streamers like or help people create
themselves as a streamer or
You know, I would like people to be doing streaming and like doing more panels and I think that it's under under
Use things because I think there's like two billion two billion people on YouTube
And so I think anybody that goes to YouTube is gonna have like a lot of people that would be
Interested in finding their channel like and like what they have to say and things like that
They just have to find their audience and that's what I'm trying to do is just slowly find my audience and then it slowly builds
And it's like then like a web. It's like some people tell people tell people and more people come to the channel and
I build those subscribers and it gets better in the other way
I'm gonna come over here and like completely just unload the way I think on your channel
Because I know a lot of
That's why I try to keep that's why I try to keep these type of talking points on my channel
You know selectively from people on my channel, you know, right? Yeah, that's what you start going to different factors man
You're gonna run into people they're gonna these people these are the same people that don't do that do villages
And do any type of research on anything they won't look anything up a dissident. So that's not true
That's not true any research shit ain't looked up nothing
Don't know a from don't a no no no a through z can count from one to three
Dumbest I'm talking about dumb
Retarded for media slow came out feet first
Well, yeah, we do have like
That's what I'm saying, bro
The dumb outweighs the intelligence here, bro. We got more dumb motherfuckers running around here. They're smart
That's why we didn't predict me. We ain't not
Too many shitheads walking around man
I think I think people are very easily compromised. Like, you know, it's just like the whole informant program
You know, I think the criminal justice system works a lot on the informant program where you know, people are snitching and
and you know
taking deals to bring other people down and
and uh you know or they're just being like kind of black black owned by the police basically by
saying okay well you're gonna go to prison and you're or take away your kids and stuff like that if
you don't so you don't you don't do that you don't tell us about this and then and then people so
people will also like you know blame people it's not like but it's the whole informant system
that's what the whole sexiness here is what the whole
criminal justice system and basically circles around right now and so you can't they can't really trust anybody and
Criminals as a criminal. It's like people just stuff will like start talking as soon as they're in trouble, you know
Yeah
You want to come out
Yeah, so you know hi guys trainers you Peter alpha time anyone want to come up for it? We're just having like some
Discussions, I think you know truth on the same page. I think whenever we find like the truth. It's like, you know
Even if it doesn't make sense to everybody. It's like it's like you find it
This is kind of like, you know, you'll find other people that know it and you won't have to argue too much because
You'll you'll know the basic
What's really going on with a lot of things
For me, it's not even the truth. I'm gonna it's just it's basic shit, but it's common sense, bro
It's easy to one two three man
It's just I'm just sometimes it's not that perplexed
People people are more confounded by this type of shit, but it's just somebody like you bro
You look at like what it is man. It is what it is bro. You know, I can't do anything about it
I'm aware of the fact that this she's going on. It's all it is. It's awareness, bro
It's sermon. It's that basic bro. My approach is not
It's not like a scholar or philosopher. It's just a basic approach of understanding that this place has been compromised
Like you said by the few that can the few on the top that's controlling the many on the bottom man
It's all it is bro. And if you want to talk people might be in different clubs together, bro
Yeah
Even over I'm not talking about some spook ism some spooky shit like you had a government of full of reptilians
And you know, we got UFOs and the mother ship is coming to save us and Jesus Christ
He's in the sky watching us. That's spook ism to me, bro
So my come on somebody tell you that Jesus saves but can't tell you not one person to Jesus that say
That's that's crazy. Talk to me
Yeah, it's all man. My god is good. He saves. He loves us all man. He answers my prayers. That's folklore to me
Well, I mean, it's like, yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, that's, I mean, we can be very rational and down, but then earth, there's also a spiritual side and you can recognize the spiritual side, if you like, you know, are looking for it.
It's how much of a miracle it is that we're just like alive today. We're like in human bodies able to like do all the
little kinds of things and write and create and and
be entertained and laugh and and
Talk to people that interact with the world and you know and then we in wake go to sleep wake up and do it again every day
you know and there's you know, we grow we learn we live we learn and
Then uh, then we and then we know we live a life and then you know inevitably everyone passes away
But maybe like we'll like just like we wake up from a dream that the next day after sleeping we wake up into a new life
We so
so you
So like you indulge in like spirituality and stuff like that metaphysics
Yeah, you know, I'm a terror reader and you know, I think I'm very intuitive empathic and
You know, I feel like a connection to the higher power
Yeah
They can believe in like, you know, think they got some there's like a
Think there's like a unity of singularity, which is all God and then it's like we're all in a duality
Which is like I'm for the multiplicity, which is like a billion things
It's like where there's a almost unlimited
Suns and possibilities of galaxies and things like that and there's all these possibilities
But we're all basically part of all the little little little stars are like sparks from like the single
great like fire or you know sun or there's one sun and then it's like it
split off into a billion to suns because I wanted to experience itself as
multiplicity was kind of like it gets too lonely and then what's the experience
everything and so it creates all these planets and possibilities and we live
them out it's like super all part of God too
Yeah, and it's also belief. Yeah, it's belief, but there's also there's belief and which means I want to believe it
Or I think this could be true or there's like faith which is like I know this is true
And then there's just like a knowing which is like, you know, not this is them
Which is like, oh, I know it's true. It's been this it's a parent to me or
It's been exposed and revealed to me and I've seen I've experienced it enough to know that
It's real
How do we how do we know our life is true? How do we know this is not just a dream right now?
Maybe and whatever it is, you know, we like
Our whole life in between was there some place we were before this life? Is there a place we're going after this life?
What are we ball thing is bro? We can't explain the unknown a lot
You know why people for the most the majority of the masses for your death is because
Nobody's ever experienced it and people fear what they don't know. Nobody knows what's on the other side
Yeah, we can do we can we can dive into metaphysics and stuff like that and say yeah energy
Can't be destroyed destroyed
Not created we can say that yeah, but nobody really knows
What death is because because nobody experienced it so I don't know what's on the other side
No, if you go to church if you go to church your pastor's gonna tell you a man you when you leave that flesh, man
You're gonna go to heaven. It's gonna be golden gates golden toilets golden streets
Your massage gonna be on the fucking on the throne with a golden crown on like that's all skip. That's skepticism
That's what the fuck is that that to me that's because nobody really knows because nobody's experienced it yet
Mm-hmm. I don't think we do know is when somebody dies somebody is born with somebody's born somebody somebody's born somebody dies
Yeah, there's a cycle. There's a cycle of life and birth like people were born and people died
It's like, you know, if there wasn't death there wouldn't have there be no need for rebirth
We everyone would just be here. There would be that kind of like
Immortal in a way
Think that's like what yeah, you know, but we are I think our soul
I think I live in a reincarnation where I do believe we can wake up in another body because I believe that our body's bodies are like vehicles
Shit reincarnation
Yeah, I do you know, I do agree with you on that, you know a lot of people my channel
We told you talk about reincarnation a lot. Yeah, I do feel like that we live out, you know multiple lives here
Don't feel like you just dying as that I just that and that I could be wrong
So I'm saying that hasn't been proven but reincarnation hasn't been proven
But they hint at it and even in the Bible. They said if you give your
This if you are submit to Jesus Christ your promise eternal life eternal life means what it's eternal, right?
Infinite right so they hint at the fact that yeah, you we possibly do come back and live another life here, so
What even
Well, even like they have the idea of like the eternal and eternal hell, you know eternal heaven like but uh, you know, I
like the idea of a
Continued rebirth process until our soul is perfected or until our soul feels like it's learned all it needs to learn and then
You know, maybe going to like a realm which is like a little like a kind of like a more of a mix between the spiritual and physical
but this one this one this is a very very physical realm that
We can get hints of like there's like a little hint
I heard a lot of people in the spiritual or echo chambers. They always say that the spiritual supersedes the physical I
You know, I beg to differ. I feel like it goes hand in hand because without left there's no right without without no up
There's no down what I know down. There's no up without night. There's no day without day
There's no light. Yeah, but I don't know my time. So it's polarity. It's
Yeah, that's one of the hermetic principles of polarity. It's like, you know, it's like that. There is it's like we're like the world is
This was a duality where we have the this like the black and white like the black and white checkerboard
That's like the duality and so but there's like, you know
We also have the duality of male female, but you know male it's like in male female the duality is connected
It's like so it's just like, you know hot and cold. They're like the same thing
It's like a measurement of one thing
And they're just like, they're the extremes that, you know, in there, like the, instead of the poles, right?
And, um, and so if we learn how to work with the duality in the world,
But I think that, you know, just like we're born from one woman, like, you know, we're created by man and woman, but we're born from one woman
You know, thank you know God is maybe one and the duality comes out of the oneness or this or even
Zero because the zero is like a hole and everything comes through a hole, you know
So zero one is like the phallus and the vagina
A time I gave the definition on what a theory is bro
A theory is a cost. It's a theoretical concept. It hasn't been proven bro. It's just it's an assumption
The scientists brought to fruition about something bro in particular. It could be a stop sign. They say man stop sign is not red
It's blue
But theory man, that's what I'm trying to tell you man
I'm not trying to like get you like bro. You can go look up what a theory is
But we'll go look up the basic definition of what it did what a theory is bro
And I agree with you when you say there is a science to everything that we do. Yeah, there's a science to walking
There's a science to talking. There's a there's a science to everything that we do bro. Yeah, so
What the problem is with people is mandate when people start talking and thinking different people I say
I this person's on drugs that person's crazy. No, I just think for myself, bro
That's all it is bro. We just don't think alike bro. This is out of allergies classroom one another bro
That's all it is bro. It's not the fact that I'm crazy. I don't do drugs. I don't smoke. I don't drink. I live a sober life. I
Live a very sober life
I'm not perfectly not like that, but I use smoking drink, but now I know I live a sober life
I think that way I can think clearly
right
So when people say this person's wrong, he was thinking like that
I just think for myself, bro, and you just don't like the way that I think bro. You probably just caught up in
Somebody else some else's beliefs, bro
You know you somebody like you has never formulated their own hypothesis, bro
By their own way of thinking about anything bro
You took the indoctrination and ran with it me I took that shit through it in the garbage
You took the program in Iran with it I took all the propaganda through it in the trash
That's the difference between me and you
I'm ready to send a summer. I have a bunch of medical stuff. I'm given
You said somebody said no my my ideas. No ideas are original bro. Even your ideas are not original
You talk when you when you parrot the NASA theory that we're spinning on a fucking ball at a thousand miles per hour
Bro, you just regurgitating what somebody else told you at that point to you fucking idiot
You just parroting what they what they told you in the fifth grade
Yeah, dumb fuck I mean
I mean, yeah, they do they do work with like they do you have like programs for kids and stuff like that
You know, NASA, you know space camps and things and that were really
There's nothing new under the sun my brother and there's nothing new under the fucking sun bro at all I
Rather think for myself to regurgitate a bunch of trash pseudo ass information that somebody else told you
Yeah
Yeah, and we want to
We want to like find the truth, but it's like there's a lot we can't know and it's like we know it's like I
Think we have a limited time here
And so especially like these like space travel like we can't really know you don't really show us anything
We're not gonna get anywhere interesting. You know, we can just put more money and try to go further and further in space
Um, but is there anything we're really, really benefiting from it?
So we can take all that money and put it into, you know, you know, programs for our
people from our country, but, um, other things that would help people actually, like, but
there's been a lot of money on things that are not important, let's see.
We
Know if they if they would take the money that they use on one aircraft one missile anything like that
We could stop poverty in the United States. Yeah, I mean, yeah, I mean, that's true. It's like
so because we're selfish, it's like that, you know, we all suffer
because
No, even like, you know, we can have free energy in this thing, but
It was made so like energy has to be paid for it
You know and then you know the fossil fuels use and pollution and everything just
We could make so we get like pay for energy and water we pay for energy water these things are like free on our planet, you know
I'm sending I'm sending summer unicorn poop. Oh
Awesome
They're bath bombs, but they're unicorn poop
Yeah, I love the next bath bomb. Oh, I have I have some really nice ones from Lush
One's a seaweed one. Oh my gosh
I don't do baths that often but the seaweed bath bombs from Lush are like to die for
They're the best
They smell good
They you know, it's it doesn't smell when you put it in but when you get out
The the the scent it leaves on your body
It's hard to describe, but it's a good scent
But you know, it just moisturizes your your body. It's so nice. I love it. Sorry. Sorry didn't mean to get off track
But I'm packing a box up like I'm gonna put a case of unicorn poop in there for her
well
More pleasant than it sounds. Oh, yeah, it's they're really cute
They're it's really cute a little bath bombs and they look like you know the rainbow kind of things and then as they dissolve
They have a little seaweed and stuff inside of it. It's really cute
It's very nice. I have a friend that has a connective connection with lush
So she brings me cases of the bath bombs over all the time
Well, I love a good bath I look forward to my bath tonight. I'm gonna have a nice spiritual bath
I got an Amazon give me
We could the spiritual baths are very important portion because we collect a lot of
Astral gunk and it was really cleared off
But that's as good looking very pain compared to the military hmm. Yeah
Well, you know, it's like the military is a huge budget. That's a huge budget
We are the defense arm of the pretty much the NWO, you know, that's the the religious is Vatican the
military in Washington and
This guy I knew he was pro-nasa I knew time was was pro-nasa
Just you know just by the way he was talking in the chest. So I get it now
What has NASA done that has benefited you and your family on a personal level?
Have you aborted one of these spaceships and have you gone to a place where there's a utopia?
What has NASA done that has been beneficial for anyone?
I feel like that it's been more of a detriment, you know, including the pseudo science that they have propagated
You know via the school curriculum and via these these science fiction or movies and stuff like that and so on
So I'm asking you time. What has NASA done?
You can put it in the chat that has benefited you and your per your family on a personal level
Have you reaped the benefits from NASA being around?
And this is a real question, bro, I'm not trolling the nun. That's what you're asking that simple the simple question, bro
Yeah, I'm listen listen I feel like I feel like the military industrial complex is a detriment to you know
I'm I go again. I go against all these these entities
So I do feel like you know
They spend almost what 800 million dollars a year on the military industrial complex
That's almost a trillion dollars. They spend in yearly in the fiscal year, you know for arms and weapons
Right to drop on other civilizations, so yeah
Yeah
Yeah, we were you said what has Lockheed Martin done for me? I'm look I just I just conveyed to you
But I just conveyed to the chat and to the panel that yes
The military the military industrial complex has been a detriment
To society bro because they're spending almost a trillion dollar a trillion dollars East fiscal year bro
for arms and weapons
So I'm I ask you what has NASA done that has benefited you and your family
And you have yet to answer that question
Well, whether warnings oh, well whether warning so it was on there. Yeah
And as this holds knows on there and
You know room out. We're back like
Hey, Crystal Marie
Christine God is gonna come upon you Mike. What?
He's saying Christine or Crystal
Yeah, you know Chris your crystal Christian
No, open the door. Okay. NASA is not personally benefited me. They have benefited humanity as a whole by pushing human advancement
Well, right, you know, maybe they have
That's a oxy. That's a oxymoron statement because
That's that's that's a contradiction in itself for you to say that they has benefited humanity because has has NASA
Taken large
Populous of people and put them on these goddamn spacecrafts and taken into a fucking utopia boat. No
Only thing they have done is propagated fucking lies bro over the past what 50 60 years, bro
Like I said via the television via the school curriculum
So what have they done that has benefited humanity, bro?
Have they gave out supplies and have they fed the poor have they fed the hungry?
Have they taken anyone has anyone gone on a space a spaceship per se? No
So what bro? That's that's that's that's not like a mainstream narrative, bro
Yeah, so you ask me real questions. They can't answer them. They give you a scripted mainstream answer
Yeah, I agree a lot of the lot of the argument
I mean it's like but it's like a lot of these things to have normal great answers
They could debate about them there. You know, that's why we're debating because there's not a there's not a clear
Clear clear side or there's both points for both sides
Okay, Christine's dropped down.
Yeah, so, but, you know, I've been kind of like,
if you do go down rabbit holes, I mean,
it's like people can start making false connections.
And, you know, just like with, you know, Alex through the night,
Alex was like thinking that people were,
different people were on different accounts
or there were different identities.
That DJ Electra was other woman.
Like a lot of people were confused because you go down rabbit holes and everything connects, right?
So you have to like, you know
Be be aware of what's you know in your mind and what's like actually there because we could make false connections and
You can see patterns where there really are not patterns
Skip over responses to claim victory. Yeah
Some an asset advancements in the household are memories from scratch resist lenses. Oh, yeah, okay
memory foam sketches and lenses fried right free ready to water purification even components of cell phone cameras
Yeah, I guess it's a freeze-dried foods. Who the fuck eats that nasty ass free dry freeze dried ice cream, bro
Yeah, I asked her nice
Yeah, you put some ones houses like and say man give me some of that NASA freeze-dried ice cream, bro
What the hell is this guy talking about?
The memory phone for base. Yeah, some people we have that some people have that memory phone. Yeah, I get that
Yep
Vacation system components found and cell phones cell phone cameras
Or the tools that's like a microcosm
These these answer that these answers that you're giving bro. These are like microcosms, bro
Well, and that these some of these things it's like I think they you know there it could have been invented anyway without NASA
I don't know maybe it's because you know just like it when you put money into the military
You know it there's a lot of technology like military technology advances a lot, but you know, it's like
Some of these household items you're talking about I don't I don't know how difficult it would have been to build them
Who owns a man? Who owns a NASA couch or a NASA bed? Who drives a fucking NASA? Come on, man
What are you saying? I see a bunch of NASA t-shirts, but not like
NASA shirts because that's memorabilia. I'm talking about like a NASA bed a NASA couch
NASA food NASA soap get the come on, bro. What are these people talking about man? Yeah
I know it's a briefies, but it doesn't even like usually say that the technology of NASA
You're out you're out of time. I'm sorry
Yeah
This guy says freeze-dried food who go I haven't I've yet to go to somebody's house and they had not NASA
Freeze-dried ice cream in the refrigerator room are in the storage man stores cabinet room. So what no man?
I
Was like it's like a brief jerky freeze. Try it again. What do we eat anything? That's pretty sure
Did they invent?
Now listen, it's you know what it's best for some of you all to stay in the chat because you if you some of you all did hit this panel man
You always sound ridiculous up here. I
Swear you would this is why some of you all stay in the chat. You're not gonna hit that panel is because if you came up here
It would easily be disseminated. You were you would easily be I would make you look like a fool
Mr.. Pita has NASA allocated any funds
Towards you know people in poverty
Yes or no, it's anybody in the chat and recent memory. I'm asked this question one more time as NASA
allocated any funds
For as people are living it towards people that there's living in poverty. Yes or no
Hmm
He keeps talking about material science, bro. Who has material science science benefited, bro
Well, I think sometimes it makes our lives easier. I mean, if we didn't have science and didn't have NASA
We wouldn't be having all those all these
Internets and have things that are fingertips
Yeah
Right. I mean, it's like, yeah, who has a NASA phone
You realize the satellites that are up there had to get up there somehow
Yeah, I mean that's
You said
Yeah, I get that
But that's that's not what that's not the question that I asked I asked the guy in the chat has NASA
Allocated any funds that has benefited people that's living in poverty
Yes, or no, that's a simplistic question
I don't want to hear about satellites in the sky, and I don't want to hear about them
I asked a simplistic question
But I don't think even NASA tell me the government how they're helping people in poverty or any large
Corporation, they're wanting the same. That's why I'm saying
But here we are today
Chris and Marie I have no clue what your problem is and I'm gonna tell you right now
You leave my family out of it. I have no clue what you're babbling
I'm not mentioned your name. I have not seen you and you're coming here after me like that
Get out of here crystal. No, you're
What did I do, you know what you are doing is a bullying fucking situation guess what's gonna happen to yourself
Wait a minute when you fucking drive down the street and it's fucking motor you leave my son alone
I have no clue what your problem is.
I don't know why you're coming at me. If you would like to give me a specific
statement I have made or done, that's fine. Other than that, I have no clue what you are babbling.
Get your shit together and have a conversation.
Hey, come and let Chris and Marie back away. This is a camera back on Christmas recently. Yes. He is fine though. Damn
Is it has been disrespecting me since day one didn't know a fucking I
Miss your question
Hello, let's have some decor. I'm here. What is your problem with mr. Steve? What has she done to you that they get you
Because she's a troll and she didn't want me to troll her back and she like cuts everybody in chat
And she's like a fucking retard bitch. She can't take the troll, but she does a troll. What have I done?
One thing, please you're about to find out. I'm gonna show you everything bitch one specific thing
Yeah, why not one one specific thing crystal
Tell me one specific space, okay? I'll give you one thing real fucking quick
You know you do a lot as you lie about things you're a big liar. Guess what? I hate what give me one lie
Give me one lie crystal
You lie and said, oh my gosh, you lied to psyche and told them that I called him a pack before I did.
And then that's what I said.
Okay, well, you're going to believe this bit.
I guess I'm going to have to call you a faggot because this bitch is fucking believe in her.
So I guess I'm going to have to do it.
I mean, I'm going to have to know what she wants.
No, would you like?
It's she or did she you should really prove that that's what I'm pissed about you stupid
She stops on a baby's foot every day, that's what kind of
You don't have a baby's foot or something.
You said she does.
That's what that girl is.
I don't have no baby.
Cut your camera back on one more time, Kristen Marie.
You don't look how you sound.
Cut your camera back on one more time.
You don't want a sexy lady.
You don't want a pretty lady.
They say you are a substance abuser.
You are a pretty lady though.
Yeah, I know because she wants to get me
when I was sleeping with my phone
That's what Christine, but no scene looks like she looks like an old dirty whore with a washed up face
With fake everything
She didn't look like nothing and she's judging me. What a long
Why did she care what I look like?
You know what did that old dirty bitch did that to grandmother she put her profile as my picture of my nostril
What are you talking about?
No
I'm gonna start showing your butthole Christine. Okay. Hey truce. Don't look at my picture
Your boyfriend gave it to me
that's what it is.
Ask her what that is.
What is that?
That's a mole?
That's her face.
Your teeth.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
Let me.
I'm going to beat up.
I'm going to get up out of here, man.
I guess you like that.
There you go.
Yeah.
He's lying, dude.
No, not.
Well, I
Know I don't I have
Crystal
So they pop out of my
No, they'll come out. They don't come out. Oh, she got the news. No, they come out
So she ain't got no teeth
There you go see how they're
Was it better now, I mean
Well, that's her. That's her recently with them out.
No, it's not, you stupid retard.
You know, all that for is your stupid retard.
No, it's not.
You're just a dumb whore just a dumb dirty whore. Just like your family. That's why your husband left you dirty whore
I've been married for 41 years sweetheart. I'm still married to my husband. I think your boyfriend just
Yep, your husband. I don't have a boyfriend. I have the same man. I've been with her for 42 years
I know you're husband is and they both want to fuck you
No, you don't. You don't know
Alcohol methamphetamines, and yeah, I'm not yeah
Anything to
Came out of here like a bad out of hell no your retard bitch you keep
Who have I attacked?
You attacked fucking Rachel, you attacked...
Who's Rachel?
Katie, you attacked fucking...
Who's Katie? Who are these people?
Who are these people?
I don't even know who these people are.
They are all Betty.
I don't know who they are.
Hi Nancy.
I have no clue
Rachel is I have no clue who Katie is. I have no clue who any of these people are
Like your tops real tits by the way what we can tell they're hanging low
Yeah
Yeah, you don't even have tits because you're a fucking dude bitch
Okay
Yeah, she had um, um, a fake husband that
The wife fucking had kids and this bitch. He's lying. Yeah, this bitch is a fake fucking bitch
I had the same man, 42 years ago, I guarantee you she has 42 years, we can get her to,
43 years, you don't think that clarity can get you to talk to her husband?
You're forty-two years
Forty-two years crystal same man. Oh, so you don't care if he fucks around with that forty-two years same
Same man forty-two years
I have no clue what she's on about psych sorry
You
Illusions
Well
Man, it's just pretty comedy. I said that man. I don't say how you don't be sort of pretty just laughing at this shit man
Yeah, man, it's your pretty comedy man. God damn
Oh my god, Crystal
is there anything okay, like, um
What do you wake up to the mad at Christina? Is this out of the blue Christina? Have you gotten along before?
I've not seen Chris on. I don't even have a clue who those people are. She's talking about
Yeah, I
Don't know any Rachel. Well, when you're under the influence of metham, methamphetamines and peels and you know alcohol
You know, you can you contend and you know say delusional things outlandish things
There she goes
She don't sound like what you sound like a old motherfucking method, but she got the camera when she looked decent
Oh, thank you, Jamie
I haven't talked to crystal
Nothing, do you know sunshine as she says she's saying that you're a terrible person that you're gonna be exposed
I don't know whose sunshine is either
You'd be probably crystal who knows
I
You too
Listen, listen, this is the embodiment of YouTube streets YouTube beef man. So I'm all for it
The delusions Jamie the chickens are great
Yeah, I'm gonna go fire my shit. Oh, I'm out. Do y'all be easy. Peace. Thanks for having me up. I appreciate the conversation
Thank you
Conversation about what we're talking about earlier, bro. Yeah, let's do it. Let's do some sounds good. All right, cool
Way into stuff. I had no clue what you're talking about. That's why I was
Right, yeah
Yeah, I suppose
Heavens, and I'm gonna be exposed about them. I'd like to be exposed so I can know what's going on too, right?
Yeah, you see right out of all people we're gonna expose me. Okay. I
Kind of Lea boring life
It's built around children and grandchildren and work is yeah
Yeah, I don't hardly drink. I don't do any drugs on you. It's not pot
Yeah, I could be clean
It's an assos fault Jim could be
And thanks sunshine appreciate that whoever you are
we should all be exposed so it's so it's so it's uh so it's fair yeah i don't know what i'd expose but
that's okay right i think that she just released every oh you know all of our she just put a you
know camera on our window and uh expose everybody's everybody's private life
there you go you know apparently chisel the very good imagination she can make everybody's
Um, life very interesting. It seems like right
We have you know, it sounds like a lot more
People with people with people we don't even know running around, you know
Rachel and Rachel and whoever Rachel and Tracy. I'm not Tracy, but
Yeah, let's see. This doesn't mean funds reflect either I should oh that's sunshine
We there you go. That was inappropriate language
Inappropriate
Yeah, so anyway, anyway, anyway
That was funny
I have no clue what just happens like I'm just telling you and as for for making up things
We all remember that day that she was like as nice and even keel as possible and then all of a sudden
She just flipped
And she did call and she did call you a racial slur with the effort
Yeah, I mean I mean she's causing me
I mean even if she like says the word I like don't say the word, you know, but she
You know, I don't I don't I don't think offense to the word is just you know, I don't want to be yeah
I do have a lot of other people other people may other people may take offense and you're trying to make it a good place for everyone
Yeah
And I make a safe place, you know, I've had people I think you know, you know, Jamie Rose would say that
You know and the end word and stuff like that and she doesn't mean
Harm, you know, I say a lot of it people are not even racist
It's just like either for the shock value or it's like they're vernacular or it's like, you know
I have a real
With that, you know, if if you are a
Black person and you use it because it's used as a term of endearment and I'm okay with that
But you always have to look at how is it being used?
And when it's being used in a derogatory or hateful manner, there's the problem
Yeah, and yeah, that's why it's like I say like no
No hate speech, you know as
You know that includes you know for all for all groups, you know, it's like, you know, I don't like racial slurs and
But I don't mind any kind of other language people. Well, we're they're endeavors. Yeah, and that's how you know
Summer's one channel. It's you know, there's no racial slurs allow
There's no doxing and no racial slurs. It's pretty simple easy stuff
You know, she doesn't want to silence people but there has to be rules
I don't care who you are. There are rules and it's not worth risking in terms of service
Yeah, I mean, yeah
You know, who knows this channel might be the only thing I have left one day, but you know
I mean, I probably have to try to keep it try to keep it
Try but she would keep it good. It could be my my lifeline some day
You are 100% correct. It's not your lifetime. It's cheap entertainment
Okay, at least yeah, it puts it. Yeah. Yeah, that's why I support financial people financially sometimes because I couldn't pay 25 bucks for a whole week of the entertainment
Right
If it's what 25 bucks a week for entertainment, what kind of entertainment well like when I come on on panels, you know, you provide that platform
Well, I get to listen to everybody you provide that platform. What else would I be doing sitting at home watching TV?
Hey, thank you
Hi
Are you better?
No, are you better? Are you fucking did you take a fucking medicine pill or whatever the fuck you do?
My gosh, did you take a pill today? Do you need your pills this morning? I took some vitamins this morning
Is that okay with you? How many I'm not the one that's going a little on the on the balloons, you know bar
Please double
Double doser, please
We know when you're done triple watch triple doses for
I could not talk to you when this beautiful baby is in the room.
See, obviously Christine doesn't know anything about that.
A medicine pill, yeah, she's a medicine pill.
She's got a modium.
Double dose herself.
Yeah, Christine, you should triple, a quad triple dose yourself with whatever the fuck you are taking.
Why would you say that?
She's an awful person. It's like, yeah, I'm so sorry for you
But she's but what does she do to you? What were the people you're best made out of it?
It's not necessarily what she does to me. It's what she does to everybody. It's it's kind of like disgraceful. She's like a bully
Mean everybody she's rude. She ruins your chat. She makes really bad
Accusations calling me a drug person and when she's a drug person and
Fucking and then she says you need to make your chat nicer
Yeah, I
Can't even I can't even comment badly because I know this bitch is gonna block everything I say
Band me. So what does it matter if I have to comment back of a bitch that says bad things about me a day in and day out?
When do I
Bad right when is the last time I've mentioned my comment ad, but you know what?
Could be that you don't really matter. It wasn't even about me
The thing is is that you do this to people day in and day out and it's really fresh
Because I don't like a bully. I don't like bullies
And guess what's gonna happen to you?
You're a very big boy. It is gonna fucking kick you in the face today
No
I don't think I
Where'd you come up with that
And then she says I say bizarre stuff, but she's saying bizarre stuff to me. I'm just catching it
What do you catch
I don't it doesn't matter what I'm catching. I'm catching that you're disgusting. You are delusional
Ugly grandmother. You are delusional
You are delusional in my entire life. You're the worst grandma I ever seen in my entire life
Oh, thank you. You're an ugly mother. You're an ugly disgusting grandmother and mother. Thank you. Thank you so much
Thank you for exactly what I didn't want to be at least I just asked for a specific thing
I have said or done and you cannot give me
You keep bringing your son up
And then you I four of them. I have four sons that are not I have four sons and then telling psyche that I said stuff
You know what? Hey, I said one thing you said and you can ask psyche psyche
You call him a slur that began with an F
Good morning
Next time you hit the meth pipe, can you not go off camera like at least entertain us with it?
You should this bitch like you I told you that
Well, I guess you're the bloody for what I say Christie, okay, so I
But nobody cares what I have lied about what?
You calling a racial slur a homophobic slur with it begins with an F to psyche. He just said you said it
This sin
Yeah, why would you disrespect the channel on her crystal?
To him bonkers that day
He provides this space for our voices to be heard. He actually predicts your voice quite a bit. I mean
What's your issue with cycling?
It did happen sunshine ask psyche yourself
Yeah, what's okay, but it's okay crystal. I don't think events to it. I don't mind
Yeah, but we still need to know what her issue is with you so we can resolve them so it doesn't
Oh, she left. Oh my gosh. Well, I think she's
She said that she she thought that I've called her name before I don't think I was calling her those things
But maybe
She's schizophrenic she really is like that last time I was on panel with her
You didn't hear her holding like three different conversations with herself at the same time
I
Hear
No, he said
He was actually describing cake a when he was describing me it's pretty funny who was me or exiles
Exile that okay exiles. You're okay. Yeah
Yeah
You're not the first person that dropped off panel to hit a meth pipe lady. It's not the first time I've experienced your behavior
It's my observations of you. I don't even know this cake paper. You're talking about
I'm observing you. So, if you're mad about anything that I'm saying, then change your own behavior.
And you can't deny the fact that you wasn't talking...
I'm talking about your behavior, what you said about me before you...
Hold on, you can't deny the fact that you were talking to yourself on the panel last time.
You was totally over three conversations with yourself.
I'm mad because...
What's going on, Crystal? Get it out!
Crystal, are you okay?
Our mic's fucking up.
Yeah, you're losing reception over there, Crystal.
By the way, I told you I'm a tornado, and I am...
Oh, so you're in the basement.
Okay, I'm using my phone to lift our brakes.
It's because I'm a fucking tornado, a fucking alleybit.
Okay, understandable. We're just letting you know that you got an audio issue. Just make sure not aware of it
Yeah
Okay, then shame please don't make those accusations in the chat
So crystal do you talk to spirits you you strike me as a type of talk to spirits through your lampshade she she dropped off
Well that time
That time I was claiming her to be somebody else
All right, I'm done. I just can't understand this lady psyche
I mean like literally last time I was up here
We was all holding conversation and she was yelling at two different people inside of her head
Like nobody was saying anything to her, but she was going off about people saying something to her
She's delusional
Like she keeps saying Christine is trolling her
I've never seen Christine in the same vicinity as crystal other than at this channel and I ain't seen no trolling going on
Yeah, I mean some people are just like I'm troll person that I'm friends with some trolls and I say they probably troll me sometimes but
You know, it's not like
Well, hopefully it's not like in a bad way
Don't say you don't know me so yeah, I don't know are you I think sunshine and he mannered is playing around see you block both
Yeah, guys if people say something in the chat, you don't like I probably will be able to get to every comment
But you can like always block the person and you don't have to see them
Priscilla's trying to come back. I don't know if it's not working yet. Let me see
Yeah, her camera is not on her or sounds long or something
I'm glad to see the chat wasn't distracted by crystal and they were doing their own thing
Yeah, the chat is having fun
Yeah, every nice chat 41 people in the chat. Hey scum. How are you?
That's a great idea
Yeah, we're having a good morning. I got another coffee left
So, Christian, I've been here for the beginning of this saga, but you seem a little more mentally stable and by a little more, I mean, a whole lot more mentally stable.
When would you say this issue caused with crystal happened and what would possibly be the cause of the issue?
Is Christine even here?
I love Christine's right there.
Yes, I'm here. Sorry.
I have no clue what caused that, and I don't even have a clue who those people are.
Oh
It's like the random stranger on the street that comes up to you to blame you for that and you've never seen him
Yeah, I mean one day last week somebody said something and I and then
Crystal was like just freaking out and I said crystal is upset because you call them homophobic
Slur you called you were nice one moment the next moment you called him an effort. I mean
He had he didn't say you couldn't come back to his chat
She was like totally weird
And I have no clue what the hell these other people are in any way shape or form
Sticking cakes you you want a membership? I don't think you might have gotten it last night
We had some memberships gifted last night and today so congratulations on the membership
Yeah, blog me like psyche said in which oh come on
Sunshine what's going on? All right. Why are you why are you even so mad sunshine?
Yeah
I would have figured it would have stemmed from some kind of debate or something Christine
But apparently she's just that homeless guy who comes up to the car banking for change and blaming you for the homelessness
Even though you never met them
I know I really don't care either but Crystal does Crystal's parents. She does. Yeah, she's
deeply emotionally involved. I have to need a moment. I have to brush teeth.
But I think yesterday was by yesterday was actually like a very calm day
I didn't I don't think I got I think I got poor Bob only one time
Yeah
Yeah, actually I only happens twice actually one one n-word Bob and one for Bob and so I mean that's just a couple and
There's a pretty calm day the crystal effect. Yeah
Yeah, it's on that crystal
It's taking cakes congratulations on your membership
Don't call Harry Harry who's he was Harry. Oh, I know who Harry's the
Harry's that annoying Greek guy with that. Oh, yeah character light
Yeah, I don't think anyone called him a name. He was interesting
Hey, does he pay power does he get to see yeah, it's been a while
Shout out to my fellow Kansas City in
Yep
Quite a few people come in the Kansas lately. Have you noticed that?
Yeah, I remember back in the day. I was the only motherfuck out here solo dollop
Yeah, there was somebody last night, I'm thinking what's going on in Kansas lately
Years there's been a lot more of us online
I think it's because of that whole coup for dill that we had a lot of people started popping up on
I don't know. I don't know.
I've been on media platforms for a long long time like since the Yahoo chat room days. Oh my gosh
I have some really good friends that I still see and talk to you today from the Yahoo chats
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna get to a couple again offline, but shit. I never kept in contact with them
Oh, I do there's probably about 20 of us that still talk all the time
Oh man, it'd be hectic if I still had my old crew with me.
It was calm.
They helped me get through with one of the birth of one of my children
and finished through with my master's degree.
It kept me sane in the insanity world.
Some of us need the background noise. It helps us focus.
Oh my god, I don't know what the hell's going on to y'all. What?
And you know, it's been kind of a wild night apparently when I was sleeping maybe somebody was pretending they were me
I don't know. I fucking missed everything from yesterday. I was on other panels handling shit
Yesterday was a real hectic day. That's why I was asking psyche how it turned out over here. Oh
Yeah, I was real calm over here because you know, I basically I modded everybody and
There's like a little bit less fighting over wrenches and
I don't know but I don't it was pretty quiet and pretty quiet over here lately though
Well, and I think because Alex isn't around and Mr. Badpipes and a few other people, but everybody's been live
Going live recently. I'm not lately. I think that makes a difference too
Don't know man. I'm trying to catch Saints alive again, so I can like try to invite dates over here with bagpipes
Have a ring. Oh, well, well, I I ban bagpipes, but uh, I
Yeah, he's like
I banned him I mean I ban him on stream yard and on the on the chat, so I mean
I don't know maybe I'll unbend him but he I'm not really interested in talking to him anymore. He is he's doing like
digitals and stuff and on his on his avatar
I'll be back. I gotta get dressed
Okay, I'll be christine
I'm staying right here. I'm just waiting for a moment
There were fighting over wrenches. I don't know
Basically, I'm on everybody. I had to I mean I have Jamie's cowboy. She's she was with me from the beginning
I do need a just a few people
Then I really like no one trusts
I had like I don't know to be honest with you. I'm not I'm not a good candidate for that
I don't use my wrench for like authority reasons. I only use it for the go-to channel. So I'd be yeah
Yeah
Well, my chest been pretty calm lately, so
It's all good. Good morning, Sweet Pea. Good to see you.
Good to see everybody. How's everybody doing?
Yon Compos. It's your big pipes.
Is this for magic? Yeah.
What is that? Describe.
Sticking cakes.
Uh-oh.
Good morning at young
How's everyone doing having a good day have another coffee. That's all he got
You got Christine and exiled. I guess walked away
Yeah
And I hope we don't have a big cloning problem. I know there do Heather. I've been some people admitting other people
morning collective card share
No, I'm getting ready for my day psyche. I just got through washing my hair back of my hair. Okay
Okay
No, I was gonna ask you though when I came back who was your favorite youtuber of all time psyche
favorite youtuber
I see at least a Jordana
Yeah
Yeah, and what's her main content about?
She's in Florida and she basically goes to local events in the area and local restaurants
and goes to little events and dances and she takes donations for either playing music or
just comments on the screen and so she has usually interesting people as her assistants.
She just goes to parties and she's a driving eating music. Yeah, and but she also takes you know
She takes phone calls from from the viewers and fans and like, you know, she participates with her chat and
She's very entertaining. She's a I have gotten to talk to her many times
She's a little bit controversial though, she's a little bit controversial, but
Oh, okay. I know this lady. I covered this lady with starlight before this the lady to beat up her boyfriend in a car
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I know exactly who this lady is
Yeah, interesting content a lot of people like watching it
Yeah, I don't I don't think she's I think she's fake. I mean, you know, but it's fake
I mean she has probably a on camera persona and
You know, she's very beautiful and I don't think she's had too much surge
I think she had a nose job. She's just naturally beautiful and maybe her lips done stuff
She she got in trouble for beating up that special needs dude in that car, didn't she?
Uh, yeah, I guess you know what she went to jail for just a night and then
Yeah, domestic violence he was just in jail overnight and then she took a plea deal for like a year probation
And uh, that was it. She's got here. She got a probation in April. What happened to the car?
She ran it about people's opinions of
Of it for a few months there
Well, I'll do a few cards for the this is for this either for the chat to the bill in stack
Okay, okay, we got this chariot card.
Okay, so some plans are moving forward,
but it's like, you know, like correlative bill,
these are kind of some of the dark sides of the cards.
You know, just make sure you're, you know, watch your speed
and you know, but you're heading towards,
toward what you want, which is the chariot,
I'll tell you, oh, I just went right to it.
It says the chariot represents determination,
unrelenting focus and willpower,
much like the formidable fashion-loving
who doesn't let anything stop her from getting what she wants, not even a car chase in the snow.
So it says obstacles won't phase you now. You're in hot pursuit of your goals. Nothing will stand
in your way for long. Don't let yourself get distracted. What you want may seem just out of
reach now, but putting your pedal to the metal will give you the last little boost you need to get
That's that one
Next we have oh if it's two of coins
To a pinnacle this is the two of the coins. I think this is like cough from the snake from a
from a
Right, let's see
Yeah, I think it's the other jungle book, okay well to a pinnacle that's coming together with somebody
You know on a business or something, but it says
And it represents the balance between work and home.
It can be tough to manage responsibilities
while still making time for the things and people
that mean the most to you.
This serves the reminder as important
of maintaining a healthy balance.
Okay, so you want to stay balancing.
And watch, you know, stay with the tide that's going.
Okay, we have the hyenas from
From the Lion King right there in the eight coins eight of pentacles
Okay, we got the hyenas
So it's the hyenas represent
Well, it's like you might have abundance, but like you should you should protect it. It says
Eight of coins shows you're working hard to learn new skills
Say dedicated to your goal keep practicing and you'll be successful. Okay, so continue continue practicing you will
You will be successful, but yeah, watch out for hyenas, right? So, um
There you go. Let me see. I'll do one more. Oh, we got this queen of wands. Okay
Who is this queen of wands? Okay, is this a woman in your life? You know this woman it you might have these two personalities
They can be they can be a little jealous, but usually they maintain their jealous, but you know
You have to you remember there's
This is like the mother and the crone a little bit. Yeah, I'll tell you what the book says
Okay, this queen of one says
Says
So who is the fairest of all the queen of wands? Of course
She's a beautiful regal figure who turns heads the moment she walks in a room like the queen
She's graceful stylish and commands the respect and admiration of those around her the cards suggest
It's time to be bold and expressive. Your authenticity is charming. I
Don't know do you know this woman or
You know that might be a woman that you'll that you know men them if you're your wife that you know you look for the Queen's
What cards are my reading these are whose cars nobody's cars at the moment, but if you if anyone was like a
Short free reading or they'd like to get a longer reading
Sure or I have to head out to go to the chiropractor
Okay
I'll do three cards for you
Well, okay, so I see okay, so we have the ace of coins right and the ace of coins is like this, you know
Kind of like you've been thrown a seed or you've been throwing something and if you take care of this
It can grow into something bigger. Okay, it's the beginning of something at the beginning of an enterprise
You know, but also it remembers like the coin is like a seed and the aces are
You know the beginning and you want to grow it into like you can grow seeds into like, you know
Large things like one single seed can create a whole forest, right?
But it says big opportunities are heading your way whether you're given a lucrative new role or
or exciting offer with a lot of potential or
You stumble upon hidden treasure the ace of coins advising to take full advantage of the situation. Okay, then we got the star card for you
And this is like make a wish
Okay, and I always think of that and star card is all always good things and it's like, you know light being poured onto you
Wish is being granted
This is all good things. It says this as the Queen's magic mirror
responds honestly to any question asked the star represents clarity hope power of truth
Star indicates you're coming out of a period of confusion and uncertainty
Which is while the chapter of your life may have been difficult
The stars guiding light here to illuminate the way forward
So you may not have the magic mirror at your disposal. This card encourages you to pursue and embrace the truth
Okay. Nice. Then we have the eight of cups. Okay. Here's the eight of cups.
Aw. I like the eight of cups. You read somebody's the other day with the eight of cups and it was good.
It's like it's like this person it looks like someone's walking away from these eight of cubs like looking for another cup
But I think like you've got like a lot. You've done a lot that you wanted to
Sometimes it got as expected. It says eight of cubs comes forward when a dream
Once achieved isn't quite as fulfilling as you expected you work so hard for this and now that it's in your grasp
You're still not satisfied take some time to think about what it is. You really want okay, and so
Yeah, there's something else. I mean, it's like, you know, you've gotten this ace and you are this
like star power. Um, and you know, you're, and you have a lot, but you just remember you have
a lot and you still want more. There's something else. And so figure it out what it is you really
want because you've got a lot of what you do want. You uh, yeah, I do. June 30th should tell me how
Well, that's often because a lot of people settle and like, you know
When you get to that point where you thought was gonna be your ultimate you realize you have more push
You can go further and then that leaves you wanting to go further
Mm-hmm
Yeah, you got to keep going and I was like there's gonna be
you know a lot of a lot of times in life were
You know, I feel like giving up, but it's like if you keep going, you know, things walk, you know, there's always like ways to improve things and just kind of, you know, we can't give up, you know.
Okay, Chris, I gotta go. I'm gonna go get adjusted. I love my chiropractor. You gotta try it.
Chiropractor is good. Oh my god. Yeah, if you find a good one, they are like it's the best. Oh
That's Rudy Rudy just ran by me. Yeah, I saw that. Okay. See y'all later. I'll be back later. Yeah
Yeah, hi babe
Yeah, so anybody else wants a reading in the chat. I'll do some free readings and
Or if anyone wants to
Get a longer reading today. Oh all my banners have disappeared. Oh, oh, there they are. Okay. I have this
You can go ahead and like there's the information there
Okay
Yeah, I kind of want easy to get another reading hoping that he's gotten out of that era of all those tower cards
Yeah, well, you know
Well, you know, he got a few tower cards in that reading but uh
You know, tower cars aren't necessarily bad.
You know, they can be, but they can be also be,
they can also have a positive meaning,
the spiritual awakening.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, I look so crazy when I do that.
Like, I don't realize what I'm talking about.
Aye aye aye.
Hi, Crystal.
Sorry, hey, I wanted to tell you, Psyche,
that, you know, when I said that
because you were trying to accuse me of things,
then I might as well say it, you know?
It's like, that bitch just kept saying that,
I was saying things that I wasn't, you know?
It's kind of crazy that she manipulates you
as well as she does.
But it's not my game card to play it, you know?
do what you've got to do.
You should really watch your old streams.
I mean, pay more attention, watch your old streams.
They clip what they want.
They want to do what they want.
These people want, people obviously, they don't like me
or like people that bring content,
they want to
Shut off because they don't have content in their own communities
hmm
so they
Like you at with like a fucking real personality
They're like, oh my gosh, this guy's got way too much fucking personality
You know, he's like way too, you know, you're too cool for yeah, you know, too cool for school in a way
Yeah
Well, I want to keep that in mind when these people are thinking because like you were saying things that I didn't I
Said that if you want me to say it
Because I never said that about you
I was saying that about Ziggy, but I was saying if you want me to say it then I'll call you that but
It's just like and I said I didn't even want to call you that like took me like so, you know like
I didn't want to call you that it was not the question is why would you disrespect the community that psyche is a part of
at all
I mean, I know I call non-gay people gay just to offend the non-gay person but when you start going
It wasn't anything to do with that. It was this guy was trying to threaten to murder me. Okay
And so, Psyche didn't understand that he kept leaving, right?
And this guy was saying like, this outrageous stuff,
and I'm not going into every detail, you know?
But this guy was saying outrageous stuff
and that Christine was just applying it
and just saying it was okay.
And like, letting this guy like,
and thinking this when Psyche was gone, dude.
And that's not the kind of people that he needs.
Right. Well, you know, it's the logic. I just don't get offended and
No, it's okay. Hey, listen, we gotta have people that don't hate the hate the hate and like love the hate
You know like me like I
Don't want to be that. That's what I said. I told you that from the beginning. Oh, yeah
I don't I do not get don't give me because they're all gonna fucking say that I did shit
Yeah, well, yeah, I mean people say stuff about everybody. It's like, you know, it's outrageous people can believe what they want to believe
But you know, there's accusations are made every day
That's why I have everyone on the show because it's like I can't I don't know
This there's like, you know, the person's been imprisoned, you know
Even if they've been imprisoned if they're out of prison
Who gets a fuck
Whoo, I was starting to feel nervous there because I've been to prison. Yeah. Oh, well, that's fine. I mean, it's like
Are we gonna like look up your criminal record and find out exactly what you did and
I'm transparent fuck it was aggravated arson would explode sees back in
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so we get so I could say like oh my god
So the way so the people could say this person committed arson you put people's lives in danger
I don't even know if anyone died
Because my real name is Crystal Marie. That's my real actual
Name that I was born with well, it's like your name is the crystal mess
I don't know why people are like saying you think there's some reason I'm a drug actually marry marijuana
Well, if people were to be like, oh my god, he put lies in danger back then that was kind of the ideal
Exactly. Hey, do you see exile? Do you see how he is calling me crystal meth?
I've never done a drug in my entire life. No, I don't I was saying that was
Because you just said and you said people see I'm on drugs with my name is crystal and I said well
You're doing not crystal math and that was like that was a joke
But it's like but you I said it's not you're not they
They call you that I didn't know they call you that but that's what they call me
No, no, you said that you said they call you
You allow that but you don't allow people to say one bad thing about Christine
All right. Well, I can't
Respect people. Yeah, I lost somebody when I when I lost my teeth in an accident in a car
I was not driving and I wasn't drinking and it was no alcohol and there was nothing. Okay
Mm-hmm
Yeah
Hey page
Yep
So hey Rachel hey Rachel something my accident of big, you know, like I know like I was a druggy
No, yeah, I don't think anyone judges you Rachel you I think you were awarded a membership
So well, no everybody doesn't judge me because they know actually because they actually know but you don't I
Don't
Yeah, because you believe Christine
Well, what about what exactly that's right what you said or like I mean I said it doesn't really like you know
I mean, I I
Yeah, yeah, I'm telling you
It's not about Christine. It's not about me. It's not about fucking anybody, dude. It's about you
It is my part
Seemers right
Like listen, you are not you're letting these
Some things are but not everything and that's the shitty part
Yeah
How's everyone doing in chat maybe that's why
That's why I started drinking like I don't I never really drink, you know an allergic to alcohol
You lose alcohol. Yeah
You know as soon as I start drinking it messes with my voice. My voice is so different when I'm not
Have you had any white claws yet, oh, it's too early
No, I have had white I
Know it's like I was looking at it. It's probably one o'clock in the future. I drink I drink sometimes early
You know me. You know me. You know me. You know me. You should have just even said it
You should have said, oh, you're drinking one from last night
Seiji that's one thing that really hurt my feelings dude when she went over to another psyche
Because like community I didn't know she was doing that and I didn't know she was there before you
Or any other state another psyche or those psychic or what are you talking about?
Yeah, psychic
Psychic person
But who is going to one?
Christine
No, be that no beat up. Oh, be that. Oh, be the question of the psychic. Oh, yeah
Well, I think that guy she's like said she dated that guy. Oh
I won't I don't know. She said
She was like you know that Carl guy was like, you know, I didn't know him to be a psychic. I knew him
To like still from people and like try to like he was like a bad person
That's all I know from him. I don't really know too much about him
Yeah, it's all my carl. He grows the weed are y'all I
Don't know
Did he have a second channel?
Is he bald?
Like he peaches hair short?
He fucking threatened.
Well, okay.
Okay, okay.
Maybe this is my opinion.
Can you let me finish it?
Yeah.
In my opinion,
I felt like it was like
She was like threatening you or something or like,
or like saying that she was like a better psyche than you.
And I know that you are the best.
So.
Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
So I know she's just saying that too.
I feel, I feel you.
I feel you.
Like I feel like, I hope you feel me like my,
like not that way, but you know what I mean.
Yeah, like um, like when you ever gave me a rainy reading I've act I
It's been right on point
Mm-hmm. Oh
I'm happy to read the very first day. I met you listen. Okay, I
Want almost $6,000 on bets remember you told me
Mm-hmm. Yep. I said you I said the money you're gonna be coming into some money really soon
And you want to see Calvin, right? Yes, almost. It was like five and
twenty-five and five and then I won 25
I guess I won I had twenty-five dollars like leftover
That they gave me like later on
So I won five hundred and fifty
Mm-hmm
And then I won 20 so I won 500 you know what I mean, but then you know what I'm saying
I was only a $25 buy it
Yeah, so that's a pretty good profit very good, and then maybe like you know get some confidence to bet because
I thought you're gonna win and that's all you needed.
Exactly. You gave me my fucking confidence and I fucking felt it.
That's exactly. Thank you. Thank you, psyche.
Thank you for explaining it better.
Oh, yeah, I just feel, I feel it.
Pretty good. Hey, everybody in chat.
I hope you're doing great. We're talking to Crystal.
Do you want me to read you three cards, Crystal, today or no?
Sure. Sure. Okay.
Okay, I got these villains cards here
Kitty card kitty card
Yeah, it's a key card. You want a key card?
Yeah
Okay
Okay, here you go
So you got the face we got this magician card. Here's the magician
Magician means you have all the tools you you need at your disposal for a full screen
Okay, there's a magician card
Which move is this from okay?
You can use all the elements you can like you know manifest it you can make things happen you can
You know kind of all hack realities the magician is a figure with limitless raw talent and creativity
like the magician smooth talking and doctor
Thauselie is a flashy conjurer and powerful sorcerer who solves it nothing to achieve his goals.
So it says, Imagination is everywhere. You're feeling creative, unstoppable, ready to conjure up your wildest dreams
and brace the creative impulses that come to you with flair because now's your time to shine.
Seize the moment the magician tarot card indicates it's time to harness your potential and put your hidden powers to good use.
Okay, and that goes for everybody. You're a powerful man. You're a powerful man. Oh
Thank you. No, really. No, you were one of the most I always tell people about you
Like I tell my friends like dude. I know this guy and he's not like my
Like I'm not gonna go but you know, he's not
Like undercover he doesn't like act like he's super hard or you know what I mean? He wants to be like
He is like everything you would want from a gay guy. Oh, sorry
It's okay
Well, then we have we have next we have this queen of stores and here's the queen of stores. I believe that's the
She's a stepmother from Cinderella.
Right?
But she's a queen of stores, but you know, she, you know, the queens of stores, sometimes
they're divorced, sometimes they're not, but usually they, at least have a lot of people
out of their life.
This one says, the queen of stores is intelligent, independent, and self-assured.
Like Lady Tremaine, she is a clever, composed person who shouldn't be underestimated.
This tarot card reminds you to trust yourself.
You're more capable than you give yourself credit for.
Okay, and then finally for you we have this justice card. I'm not sure that is either but you know this justice
is about, you know, things becoming made fair.
I've always like, you know, justice in the upright
is always a good sign.
It's like, I mean, something's gonna be made fair.
I'd rather that something is unfair.
And so I'll reach out.
Yeah, chat is always on my side.
Hey, guarantee you Christine, chat is gonna fuck you over.
When they see the fucking truth about you,
they're gonna fuck you over real quick.
Just a-
It says how you-
It says, have you been feeling morally conflicted about a situation in your life?
Are you in a situation or relationship that doesn't feel right to you?
Deep down, you know what's right.
The tarot card justice advises you to follow your moral compass regardless of your personal
feelings on the matter.
It's a clear sign that now is the time to stand boldly for truth and integrity.
It may be hard, but it will lead to peace and stability in the long run.
So there you go, Crystal.
You know, I think
Yeah, you're fucking beautiful. You were beautiful. Oh, thank you. See you've always and you know what?
You always give the best beautiful readings
Imagine wanting anything but a beautiful reading. I mean come on
Oh, thank you so sweet. Yeah, but I don't know but I don't know beat is mad at me
I don't know why she's been mad at me. She was here today. She's not that happy with me still
But you know, I'm gonna I'll try to do better and checking on her show and I know she's
But I like kind of give plenty of people space and like I don't know if they you know
They want to see me and because she was kind of mad at me last time. She talked to me so
Yeah, but Crystal Marie is a tight as a it's right. What's your back? Watch your back boom, okay?
I'm a rider died. I got a song called a ride or die. Okay, they wrote a song about me called right or die. Okay, so I
Know
The links are working, let me see. Oh, I'll post it again
Maybe maybe streamers down unfortunately. Hold on
No, it's rough out here on the streets on the internet streets, it's rough dude
And I feel so far I
I feel like that's what I was like. They're bringing him into a like a fucking like the wolf's dead
You know who are you into you? Oh, me into the wolf's death. Yeah
Why do these people are so ruthless and like they say like and that's what I don't understand about
beta is like beta likes to
put
her thoughts on like I
Don't even know what's going on like that must be something that like I don't know about but
These things of this stuff about like all these bad things like that the fucking is not for me
Okay, I'm not a sacrilegious person. I am a god-willing person and I don't want no sacrilegious
People I mean I am sacrilegious in a way because I said I gotta cross my back
But I gotta cross my back. That's sacrilegious, right?
No, yeah, I don't think well if you know and sometimes it's in the Bible like Judaism says I think no marks in your body
But I uh, I don't know it's like I don't think it's sacrilegious. It was upside down or something or if she was like, you know
Oh, no, it's just a regular cross on my back, but
You know, I always feel like a little bit guilty about it
Mm-hmm as far as like it felt like like maybe I shouldn't have done it
You know, it's like well because my parents were very upset when I got tattoos, so
Yeah, I know a lot of people regret their tattoos late later, but you know, I
Love that. I don't have anything crazy. I have like a heart and a cross
Heart and a cross
Yeah, I have a few tattoos, but
Yeah, well, you know, it's like I'm just like basically I stick to myself here now
I don't bother anybody. I don't go over to any other people's
Anybody there I never had a problem with anybody. I don't know. I just like, you know
That's just treat me like, you know, you'd like to be treated golden rule. You're like, um, I say in my lane though
That's exactly exactly the golden rule. You would like to be treated the way that you are treated
And then when people start disrespecting you and then you see that they don't care you don't care
Yeah
Well, yeah, and that's that's also instead of hating people just being different and just like kind of like
Just try to remove yourself from their presence if they're like, you know bullying you
Or you know, just say bother you, you know, you can you know what? It's not about bullying or bothering. It's about
it's it's about
The way that people should be treated in generally. Yeah. Oh, yeah
And it's like, you know
People say that I'm a big bully, but every single thing of it's pretty much been fucking
you know second
Like as far as like the way that they treated me
Hmm
Didn't remember what we're talking about. Let me see. Yeah, so yeah, so
You know, there's bully. Yeah, and so I don't like bullies and it's like, you know, I like to protect people from being bullied
And why do you like Christine? How do you like Christine though?
I know summer doesn't really do it summer is really great not of doing it, but how does Christine have children?
I don't even know how she has kids
Well, I don't I don't know, but I'm sure she's a great mom and she's you know, very
She's very wise mother. She's a terrible parent
No, she's I you know, but how do you know that because you wouldn't have any access to her parents?
She should have shared that on yeah, so let's not talk about her kid. I
Know
I mean we could see how she treats us like I would imagine that's why I don't have any kids
I would be I mean I would like be the one that would be like don't play at the park
You know what I mean, that's why I was like that's why I didn't have no kids
Don't want to be like oh my gosh. I'm scared that you're gonna get hurt. So I don't want you to play at the park
You know what I mean?
Yeah
How can we get rid of this YouTube addiction anyone I don't know you don't here here's three page
Hi page
Hey, baby. Oh, I love page pages like a breath of like beautiful
I'm a turd, but no your breath of beautiful of everything beautiful
Thanks
Oh my gosh, you look at you look how beautiful you look right now
Can we stop right now in a chat tell page how beautiful she looks this morning gorgeous gorgeous. She's gorgeous
Yeah, is it?
But it's not, you know, at least she's like people are nicer
Yeah
Yep, if they weren't I wouldn't really care because it got thick skin from being on this panel all the time
Yeah, yeah, thank you guys
These people are mean date these people do dirty stuff and mean stuff
Yeah, but hopefully yeah, well, they're not they're not as mean as they used to be I
Know because the laws changed and I I changed the laws. I helped change those laws by the way
You did yeah
If are you are you are in the legislative area, how do you help change the law?
Okay. Yeah, I know
And I know a judge and I was really uh, we're gonna change this shit
And it was from here to three states and it was one of the first
Eight that changed a fucking a crime like you know the online like calling pizza
Now it's in Washington now. They're doing I'm watching they're like, oh we should have liked
took a
fucking
Call into those now. It's in Washington, you know
Yeah, that's in Washington. Okay. Well, that's awesome. Congratulations
Thank you. Thank you so much
Welcome
How are you Paige? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm right. Oh
My gosh page. I'm so sorry
And then I have to do it like
But I have to tell him like facts and then he's like trying to do like a sarcastic thing and I have to give him facts
You do your thing guys you do your thing
No, I
Mean it's a little I want to make you. Huh?
What cards you got out today? I'll pull one for you if you pull one for me
Yeah, I need some I just need I just I got a lot going on
Okay, what did you eat today when I eat today? Yeah
Nothing yet. Why oh
Cuz I was thinking about I want to eat the same bite
Well, how about let's have like a BLT or something. Oh
Okay, we'll do that
BLT in a salad again, uh, I can I got bacon. I got like it
There you go. You're so actually have bacon
Well, okay, I'm perfect. I don't think I have any bacon
Oh shit. Oh my gosh. So you're telling me to make BLT's without bacon and you don't have it. No, no, no
Um, no, okay. So what I'm gonna do is because I actually have to go to
Grace's like little great sixth graduation ceremony a little bit this afternoon
So I think I'm gonna take her for lunch after with some of her friends and I'll get a BLT then
Oh
I got a cookie and you're gonna okay. Maybe I'll order it. I'm gonna cheat. I'm cheating. I'm gonna cheat
But okay, I
Love a bill what we should do a BLT to
Gather up. I was just gonna like
We'll do BLT cook together. So we'll just switch it up. How we don't eat. Oh my god
I made so much food last night page. I made kebabs a
Sauce one sausage a kebab nice
Well, it's like a different, it's like a lot of different and pork chop.
That's baked foods.
Yeah.
Like a pork at Tenderloin with a bacon wrap.
Bacon wrapped.
Bacon wrapped sausages.
Is that what you just said to me?
Tenderloin I was like a lion one tenderloin. I had chicken a
Couple chicken kebabs only just one piece of chicken and then I had
Yeah, well because I was eating it for two days
Oh, hi Randy. Hi, sweet peas and so I don't even remember eating last night. I'm sure it was delicious
Okay, Paige, Paige, you got the tower card, you know, the tower card, you know, so it's
like you've had this like, and this is probably the recent past, you've had a tower moment
and something that like, she kind of shook your foundations and, you know, but has like,
you know, the has the tower with the, and there's the hair, hair coming down.
So maybe like, even like, the hair is kind of beautiful, like, you're beautiful.
My hair falls out when I comb it.
That's fun.
No, you're beautiful.
No, it's not.
You cannot climb this.
You are not falling out of that hair.
Yeah.
Falling out of the tower.
No, you're not.
I heard you take it.
I'm currently in the broken tower.
We're not living in the broken.
You only have the tower of golden locks.
Aww, that's so cute, Crystal. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
It says, when the tower is drawn, it's going to get ready for a big shift in your life, because this card, Herald's, collapsed.
So you may feel blindsided by any revelation that leaves you questioning the very foundation of what you thought was to be true, not assured this is ultimately for the best.
This moment will spree you from your tower embrace the chaos. It'll come out
unscathed
Okay, and then we got like so the back together thingy
And then we have like we have the five of wands and the five of points came out
Okay, so so we have the poison apple and then okay, so then the five of points is like
Five of points is like, you know some conflict temporary conflict and finances maybe or like, you know
Feeling left out in the cold with something and then the five of wands is also conflict in like with a group or something like that
For example, the five of points says
Firmly coins represent instability involving income or the home.
The tarot cards suggest scarcity and the need to conserve resources, rest assured the situation
is only temporary.
If you need help, even through this time, don't be afraid to ask for it.
But also I was like, but I didn't want to have just all these sweet negative cards
So I was like a clarifying or the perfect commoms. Yeah pages perfect
But you got but this is your this is the advice card you got and she's my left assistant, okay?
And so and she's a high priestess, okay?
What else would she be and it says
Let's see, number two. It says,
the High Priestess is a secretive, intuitive figure
whose power comes from deep within her own subconscious.
Like Maleficent, she's sophisticated, calculating, and a magical force to be reckoned with.
And the high priest's paracart is a call to look deeper.
You may not be seeing a situation, friendship,
or relationship in your life for how it really is,
or what it really is.
What is your intuition telling you?
Take inspiration from mysterious maleficent
and embrace solitude to ruminate on this predicament.
Consider it carefully before there is more going on,
for there is more going on than meets the eye.
One more one so one more. Okay. Yeah, let's go. Yeah meets
Gratitude uh before gratitude. I'm always fucking alone man. I'm always in solitude. I know it just sucks
You know, I gotta find a different way wait the judgment card, okay?
And so it's judgment and it's like, you know, the Queen from Alice in Wonderland, but she doesn't look very happy on that card.
But what judgment is called, it's very, I think the next step is justice, you know.
And so judgment has been called, which is like, you know, it says,
Judgment represents cause and effect, consequences,
and through Queen of Hearts,
and though Queen of Hearts may not be familiar
with this concept, forgiveness.
When judgment is drawn in a terror reading,
it indicates you're nearing the end
of a long important journey.
Well, this could refer to the conclusion
of a big project in your life, such as building a house,
or obtaining a dream job.
It usually refers to a more personal inner journey.
Take some time.
to reflect the steps that led you to where you are now.
Appreciate the lessons you've learned along the way
and make peace with any missteps you've taken.
Yeah, and I really like that forgiveness part of that,
you know, it's like, forgive yourself especially
and because we will all make mistakes
and forgive other people as well
so you don't hold on to resentment or anger
or...
and or like reflect our own shadows on other people.
I mean, that's just very, it's very-
I'm not too, but it's really trying to fuck
cause I'm trying not to have a bad day
but a bad day is always trying to have me.
Like it's just not, I'm not going to do, I know, I know.
Thank you, Psych, that was wonderful.
Okay, oh, no problem.
It's hard for us to get readings
cause it's like, it's shit we know,
but it's also nice to hear like, you know, you clarity too.
I don't really talk to anybody just like,
you know, nice to have that.
I'm going to do something different for you today.
We should do, no, this one's like a super long book.
I don't want to do that one.
Let's do the literary, which is one.
Okay.
Hi, baby. Hi, baby.
I guess it's your choice. I shouldn't have just decided for you, but...
It's okay. This will cost you.
Not me, so I'll thanks for you.
Even though you are a little literary witch.
Mm-hmm.
Hi, everybody in chat.
You're doing good.
Four and a half hours, wow.
There's still another copy.
That's the one.
Oh, finish this one.
I don't even know why I bother, I put them all away all the time and then I make a big mess and pull them all out, then I put them all away again, and then they're all over the table. It never ends, man.
What's that money for, 20?
Hey, money.
Yeah, please still have to make some bacon.
I just like the way some cards feel better like the weights the shuffle the like texture
All the things
All right, I don't know the book is for that one
Be smart kids
Mmm
Yeah, let's do the
oh yeah that sounds good I have this we just pulled like a hundred cards for me
so I mean you got to return the favor um oh thank you
dude I lose my head if it was under my phone oh my gosh I lose my head if it wasn't attached to my
shoulders
there and my cards work is a great fun stat we're gonna do this one
and this one. Switching it right up. Let's do the witch's familiars first.
Again, this is what it's called if you're interested in anybody or want to know.
See, it's really cool.
Mm-hmm. I was reading the comments. I'm with the cat
We're your cat
Pritches right here
Hello tricks. Hi, baby. I feel like I haven't seen you in forever and anytime you come up everybody's yelling or something
I audit
All right one more
You're sleeping better see like I see your energy levels they're going up I see and feel
Like there's been something niggling at you though, and you're not sure how to handle it
You're not sure how what to say what you're not sure how to go about it something
You're not sure how to go about something, but you're doing
You're taking the time to think about it and process it so that
You can achieve it in a different way or something like that. I feel if there's some sort of
There's an inner shift in like your mind and the way that you're like connecting certain dots. Does that make sense?
I don't know. I'm picking up a lot. It's hard for us to reach out because we know each other, but really
we don't talk about that kind of stuff a lot unless we're
going through it, so
I do feel like you need to cleanse again. We need to do that. I feel like it'd be good for
Just because you're just you're just on them you need that next little step for that next little push
And it helps when someone does it with you like even if I did it with you that helped me too
It doesn't make sense because it just gives it more empowerment and it's like
You're just ready for a new phase or something. You're just you're plot planning something anyways
I'm gonna leave that at that, but I think that's really cool
Excited to see what this is
You're very creative those sites like there's nothing that you can't do
You know all those people all the people that you look up to and admire just know that like there's a lot of people who look
Up to you and admire you as well. It's the same
And you need that encouragement sometimes because letting people get you down all this time is really really hard on someone's soul
Ooh you got the Raven
Lookie lookie
Okay
Yeah, see it's determination. What did I say when I was touching the cards determination you're determined to do something different
I love it. I love it. You've got like a plan and you're sticking to it
So I actually don't reach for this book ever
It's long so i'll just read the familiar's message
Actually, I'd like to know what a raven means to you. I'm being told to ask to ask you that
What's the question what is a Raven? What does this card mean to you without me reading it for not just to get intuitively for you
What does this mean I?
Think I would think Ravens are like there's really smart and like you know
If they they got in trouble
Well, I think in mythology like they got the term black because they got punished for some reason and they and like they
Got term black and something like that, but I don't sometimes the reason was just because it irritated the wrong person or something
I think like they told Apollo like one of Apollo's Apollo was in love with someone and then they like they gossips about it
Like the Ravens told her something and then she broke up with Apollo and he got mad or I don't know
You kind of similar to punnish them for talking about something they shouldn't have been talking about or something
Well, it's interesting
Okay
So inner conflicts buried so deep magical omen secrets to keep
Determinations goals fly high rise up on the darkened wing and fly I call upon Raven to assist me and harnesses power
So mode it be
That's crazy. I said a bunch of that shit and so did you see what I mean?
I have to do you want to talk about it first because cards don't just say everything. That's what I mean by like
Former person calls me the tarot lady. I'm gonna freak out
They don't mean anything by it, but I'm like, not literally, but other things, but cards
you can read them.
Yes.
So the familiar's message is it's from great void that I have flown with this supernatural
determination that would serve you well as you face your adversaries mystery and magic
of the ancient ones call upon my Mach Mach Mach Macabre or Macabre.
macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre macabre mac
Allow my black wings to support you as we fly above many obstacles.
My piercing call summons the ancestors for protection while they banish actions birthed from black thoughts.
Stand strong as a carrier of raven magic and never let anyone ruffle your feathers as you fearlessly cast light into the darkness with great tenacity.
So you are about to learn a valuable lesson magic's in the air visions of prophecy are gifted to you
Read yourself of interferes use your wits make your voice heard and don't let others make me all of you
Something special is about to happen. I told you I told you that's awesome. Okay. Go spirit. Go cage. Go psych. Go chat
Sorry, I'm trying to hype myself up for the day because it's just trying something different as well
I didn't cry yet today, so that's a win. It's still early
So the job's been really helping me. I'm glad they work me like a dog. I honestly work every single day
So I don't really have time to be sad and then I get home and it's like full force because you held it in all day
Okay, let's do this at a master's for you
These are all so beautiful cards
I don't realize I had so many gilded cards
What are some of your plans today, Syke?
I don't know.
I'm going to have another coffee left,
and then I'll stream until I take a nap.
I don't know.
I'm just going to take a little easy today.
Okay, one more.
Look it's like it's pretty it's pretty cold outside today. It's like, you know, it's a little I think it sounds a little bit
It but it's like it's like very cloudy
It's the same here. It's sunny and it's like overcast a little bit here and there, but it's it's the wind is chilly
Every single time
Lads in the same spot too. Oh
Do you touch from drama boom?
Yeah, all right, so Athena
I'm not reading the whole thing actually do you know who that is like
What does that mean I got us the you know, yeah
What's your interpretation of her to you? Well, she's like a you know, she's a very powerful goddess of wisdom
in Greece and so and you know she was
very powerful goddess but she actually created Medusa and so she was and then
she had Medusa killed and so she was kind of a ruthless goddess too if she
created Medusa then she like then she had Medusa killed so but you know I
think she's wise she's also like you know the owls representing the owl and she
was also a virgin goddess because she was born fully formed as a woman out of
Zeus's head
And so his head opened and he cracked open and she came out so fully formed as a warrior goddess
but she was also
Wise in war she was more about a wise strategy in war rather than a brutal strategy in war
She reminds me of the queen of swords
Yeah, I was gonna say that to you with I saw the sword
The way that she's holding her hand above like this right it just represents kind of the same thing and she has no use for drama
Do you know what I mean? She's very established in her her mind and
Know is what she speaks and and what she hears, right?
Okay
Yeah, so that's cool. Let's check it out. I'll just get a gist for it and then we'll move on to the last one
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do. How's everybody in the chat doing today?
Hi, Gotti. Gotti says hi. Hey, what's up?
I think I'm getting a cold. Hi, Saman. Saman, Sweet Pea. Hi, everybody.
Who the fuck is she? Oh, beat that. That's why.
What a silly context
Hmm, okay
This book makes no sense. Yeah, so you just been kind of drawn into the world of like of human egos by focusing upon drama
Although it's nothing more than a story, the drama feels frightening to you.
This card comes to you as a helping hand in finding your way out of the story by detaching
from the drama.
Don't get pulled into the various plots, twists, turns, and characters of the drama.
Instead, view it as a movie that you know you will be happy, or be a happy, or at least
resolved ending.
Of course, you'll have compassion for everyone involved, yet you don't have to let drama
pull you down in any way.
As you focus upon the poise- er, the poison, holy fuck, the positive, you bring about a
positive resolution.
So additional meanings for this card can be like letting go of attempts to make everyone happy, allowing others to make their own choices in life and not bothered by them.
Don't delay your life's purpose by focusing on other people's issues and or what they need from you. Avoid gossiping or judging about other gossiping about or judging others. Interesting.
YouTube streets and
there's a lot of people trying to
scare people or
You know
Please I'll be very nightmare scenario
They can't into your mind because it's like just thinking about things can be even as bad as really experiencing them
But usually most of the things that we worry about will never happen in like 10 years from now
We'll have a whole difference that are worries probably
Well, that's the thing, you know, just even in like a couple weeks from now
We'll have a whole set of different ways, but exactly this reading is for psych
But I mean him and I know how to share so if anybody
Resonates with this hint hint all of us we can all take it because you know this can resonate for sure
I know with at least 85% of us were or 100 because we're always here, right?
Where's the drama usually around here or one of our other channels? You know what I mean or like just
But in our lives as well, but pertaining to this situation, I suppose, you know what I mean?
It could be YouTube.
But it could be someone's job.
It could be relationships.
It could be anything that you hold value in your life or that doesn't serve you with any value either.
Does that make any sense?
Yeah.
Like you get to choose you can choose. You have the choice. You have the power, right?
Yeah
Hmm
Like if you click you didn't
Communicating with like your past like your grandma or your mom or or like any way someone in your
There's like an older like a feminine energy, I'm not sure if they're passed on I'm trying to figure that out
But I was just gonna say forgiveness. I don't know there's something about something about guilt. There's something
So you're a camera cut out
Well
How's everyone doing?
Well, that's you know, the thing is like if you have any guilt
Then people can like you know guilt is an emotion that people can manipulate you with and like, you know
But if you forgive yourself
Yeah, you know
Maybe if we would give ourselves others can forgive us
We should forgive others that we want people to forgive us
Like I don't think anyone in this world is perfect
Like that's why I I'll have like almost anybody on the show as long as they're respectful in a show
I don't I don't some people say oh this person did this this person did this
But I'll have everybody on and let them tell their side of the story because sometimes you don't know the whole side of the story
Great show. Thank you. Oh
Page comes back in a minute. It was a great a minute of a reading to you. Oh, well, you know
Oh, yeah, so let me see
It was guy it guy was saying like he liked cars his favorite car was the death
Let's see if I can find this part
That says
Do you know the Death Tarot card?
Probably a little lesson about it.
So this is perhaps the card most likely to scare any novice
consulting the tarot.
But according to modern interpretations,
the death trump, like the planet Saturn in astrology,
is really not all as bad as it seems on the surface,
with considerable juggling modern decks
have also managed to keep it in the supposedly unlucky 13th
place in the Trump series.
Although, often the grim title death is tactfully omitted, leaving people to draw their own conclusions about the skeletal reaper.
In most texts, death is depicted as a skeleton carrying in his hands a scythe, before whose sweep fall prelates princes and all, no one is excerpted.
As we have just seen the scythe,
A reaping book is a symbol of the God Saturn, and indeed death is one of the grim, medieval
faces of this deity. Time has become mortality. From this word mortality itself, we can trace
back even more ancient lineage for him, Morse, or Moros, as the Greeks know him. He is one
of the children of Black Primordial Knight. In fact, he is a masculine version of the
three Morets whose weird sisters, the weird sisters, as exploits we examine a few pages back.
Thus, Morose was in effect destiny himself, supremum of all gods, who will not even mighty Zeus.
could gain say. Like that triadic fates, he also possessed two other aspects, Thanatos and Care.
In Greek vase paintings, Thanatos is usually portrayed as a benevolent,
dark-weening genius, often attending upon a sleeper with his brother Hypnos sleep.
The poet Euripides, however, described him as a more terrible guy, as black-robed and striding
among men with a drawn sword. Such a description would perhaps be more appropriate to the third
Closely linked with the three female deities that carries robed in blood and fire accompanied
Aries upon the battlefield splitting off the soul of shareship
I'll read the rest later. Hi page. Sorry. I mean
My phone died if I couldn't a guest
It's okay
In the middle of talking like this and it's just guys and super annoying cells still be talking for a minute. Anyway
forgiveness. I'll be the rest later. Okay. Yeah, that was really quick and then you can continue. Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Yeah, I'll be the rest later. I was saying. Okay, so I'm willing to release old resentment so that I may enjoy my life. So like letting go of some things.
And it says, I am filled with the same beauty, poise, and divine perfection as all of God's other creations.
Inner child, which we know yours is very, very, very nourished and still like present in abundance.
I nurture the child within me through playfulness and self-care.
So like cleaning your fingernails all the time being obsessed with that and being obsessed with your hair and
You're always very playful. Anyways and optimism you expect good things to happen and they do and I do want more for you
Enthusiasm whether I'm most passionate. Whatever. I'm most passionate about is the direction I follow
All I like that for you site. It's perfect
Very nice. Thank you so much
Yeah, it's like I haven't had a reading in a while, so
Well, you can ask everyone every day, and I'll give you one. You know that, right? Oh, oh, thanks
It was same here
Yeah, yeah, so what were you reading? I was reading I was reading about the death tarot card in this book
Yeah, I really love how people always get it misconstrued don't really appreciate the value of the death card
It's like death and rebirth of something or you know, I can mean death
But that's just a spooky name for it that people have a bad idea of but the card's actually a really beautiful card
It has a lot of them
Has a lot of purpose, you know other than just being deaf of
Like a person
There's my box
Well it says, there's two other aspects of this death, of death, this death character
named Morse, like Thanatos and Caer, and it says Caer had these things, these three female
Ares, upon a battlefield, spurting off the souls of the dead, they were in fact southern
versions of the Nordic Dalkyries, the female choosers of the slain, and were thought to
be synonymous with the Moria themselves.
That's become full circle.
Fourth, northern and southern versions of these death goddesses were known as the Hounds
of Hell, and they frequently took the shape of monstrous hunting dogs, whose barks rang
through the darkness when they hunted man's souls.
In Greece, they were known as the Arenis or the Furies, black goddesses with gorgon heads who dogged the steps of those guilty and sacrilegious crimes.
The canine death symbolism also appears in the dog Cerberus, whose image gives rise to the three animal figures on the wheel of fortune and whose task it was to guard the fate of the underworld from intruders.
So what do you think about the death card? What's your view? Do you think of any of that?
Are you there, Paige?
Uh-oh.
Well, I can read more about it, too.
But, yeah, like, a lot of, you know, there's, like, there's...
We all die, you know, it's like...
Some death is, like, very unpleasant.
You know, some, you know, it's sometimes, you know,
we all have to just, you know, pass away in our sleep.
But...
You know some people have pretty gruesome deaths
But no
Eventually the pain the pain ends we would hope
But anyway, I hope uh
Yeah, or everybody will death death and life are together. Hi. Hi, Ilya
Thank you for
Thank you for respecting my stream after I checked out the other night. I appreciate you
Look you want to stream it out porn ball me appreciate you
Appreciate that
Rice and wine
Yeah
Well, we will you know, it's like, you know, it's part of life
It's a part of being alive if we were born through we live forever
Imagine that we were immortal in these human bodies and then like you know
Think things would happen over like the billions of years were alive or the body would be at the other stuff
Hey, what's up, Chris? Oh, sorry. What's up?
Page I page back
No, I was I'm looking at the chat and I thought it's all you okay bring it to you. Hi. I was talking to Ilya
Goddy and
All the other kids names just the same as well
Restore where did you go?
You cookin' up that bacon and make that BLT?
Oh, yeah.
Hi, Gotti, what's up?
Jamie?
Yeah?
Sweet pea?
Trillion years.
A billion, billion years!
Oh, you're so flat today. I should curl it or something. This is just boring. I'm balding. Yeah
Okay, but I shouldn't have done that, but it was like really fried on the ends
Now I'm gonna have to look good. Thank you. I
Just did it myself. How's everyone?
Yeah, but it's like probably super uneven
i was a little drunk like it anybody in chat when i come up with boos let's go
time to cut hair
checks to you
say tricks i love cutlery with tricks he's always cutlery
are you good like the only one who doesn't find the camera hey like
little camera star
I think I'm way too stoned off that joint. Oh my god, I shouldn't smoke that.
Sweet Pea, yes I do.
I'm just really stoned right now, and my head's been up my ass lately,
so I've just not been able to focus on everything, and I'm really sorry guys,
I'm not ever ignoring you or not acknowledging you.
And sometimes I just miss stuff in the chat.
Oh, it's like, Goddy's asking if you can read about the hanged man cart.
Yeah, I'm looking I think it's number 16. It's actually been a while. Where have you been?
Okay, let me see. Hey, man
Dionysus, the ass-eared fool, has reached the end of his Saturnalia.
His time has elapsed.
He must perish in order to be reborn as Yacus, even as the seed must descend into the earth
to grow again the next year.
In Greece, images of Dionysus were frequently hung in trees, as means of securing fertility
for the vines and crops.
This ancient belief persisted in Europe under the guise of such practices as
a stoning an effigy at Lent, known as Jack Olent, Jack, maybe Jariah from Yacus or Jaco.
After the effigy had been taunted and abused, simulating the Titan's treatment of Dionysus,
it was frequently burned, shot, or simply thrown down a chimney.
The Saxons, however, continued to hang it from a tree.
Though he was known as Jaco Lent, some thought of the effigy to be more that of Judas Iscariot.
All of this actually symbolized the entire spirit of the winter carnival over which
the lord of this rule had presided.
The bound, hanging figure shown in the hangman is undoubtedly the Judas Iscariot.
The coins sometimes shown pouring from the twin pouches he clutches in either hand are
the thirty pieces of silver for which he sold Jesus to the Romans.
upon debtors. But lurking behind this orthodox image is that of Jack O'Lent and behind that
is Dionysus embarking upon his descent into the underworld. The myth of the dying god
is a shamanic one. As we have already seen, the hanged man shows us the death itself.
As the Nordic poem, the lay of the high one, on the surface seems to refer to the crucifixion
Deals with the exploits of Odin who as we saw earlier was not only a frosty version of the Greek Hermes
But an arch sorcerer also a prototype shashaman and it says
For all of the nine stormy nights I hung upon the tree, wounded by my own blade, Odin consecrated
to Odin, and offering to myself, bound to that mighty tree, whose roots men know not.
None gave me to eat, none gave me to drink.
Down into the abyss I wandered, and sought out the rooms.
Then I fell into darkness with a great cry, rebirth I attained, and also wisdom, for I
Thus, from one rune, was I led to a second, from one axe to another.
In view of what we know about the shamanic initiation rites, the hangman Trump appears
through his symbolism to hint strongly at this sort of initiation ordeal, ha probably
a self-imposed nature.
The Far East is a characteristically less violent exposition, and Western stories of
Odin and Jesus had the Buddha began his spiritual conquest of death and illusion seated at the
front of an archetypal body tree rather than suspended from it.
He is bound to it in his own view rather than by physical bonds.
The more primitive Shaman, however, following the more ancient practice of shackling the
limbs of corpses before burial in case they decided to return to Pestor the living, would
His actual limbs before entering a magical trance. The practice appears to carry
over into present-day ritual initiation processes.
Freemasons use a cable tow to bind the can at his hand and foot prior to induction.
The Order of the Golden Dawn itself, partially drawn from German
persecution sources, by all accounts, practiced the right, which employed binding and hanging
upon a cross in its first initiation to Adam, the adeptus minor grade, and in its annually
performed Corpus Christi ritual in both the chief
participant was bound to a cross of suffering. In the first instance, this was
prelude to illumination and a second a means of absolution for the Order's
corporate annual karmic debt. Some occultists insist there is a practical
as well symbolic purpose to this bondage on which recent researches into
sensory deprivation might have become the cast light. And then it goes more into
like the astral plane and stuff like that but
Yeah, it's an intense card. Well, but I like to look at the card is like okay like he's not hanging it from his neck
He's any sweet looks like he's still alive. He looks pretty comfortable. He's also enlightened
And, you know, wasn't that what, like, love us are actually seeking in life is enlightenment.
And so, if you achieve enlightenment, then you know that, you know, you're not really
like this human body, really spirit and hopefully, you know, and maybe, you know, but I do think,
you know, Jesus was already a human sacrifice for everybody.
And so it doesn't need to be any more human sacrifice.
You're welcome.
But yeah, if you want to, like, you know, this book is a good book, but it was going
the sensory deprivation and the bonded it's like you know it can put you into the astral plane and
you know was it worse was it worse no because that can be like coming out of feeling stuck you
know that I think that but sometimes you know if you have a different interpretation I would look
at the particular card with the expression on his face and how it looks outside down you know like
Sometimes he's smiling when he's upside down and then sometimes he's frowning when he's right side up. I don't know
But yeah always like go with the feeling you get with it
You know, it's like but I would say you know, he's right side up, but he's still like and he'd be still standing on one foot
So he still has to like, you know
Put his other foot down. So you get to seven six when you get like the seven of seven of sores
Seven of wands or seven of swords?
I'm sorry, seven of wands, seven of wands,
yeah, seven of wands, six.
Yeah, seven of wands, yeah.
Seven fingered in the south of the seat.
Seven is a chariot, so it's like, you know,
say using your power for success, right?
Yeah, that's fair.
Always, always the.
Correspond, you know, there's a lot of firepower. There's also a way down. There's like seven is the I say the numerology to that that relates to the card numbers
You know the the numerology. There's also
Corresponding astrology and corresponding elements to the cards, you know, like the devil is Capricorn, you know
Well, and this is like
the major Akana too
They have the tarot starts like so there's a start and there's
And everything in between is just like either an advancement or a story. It's a story of the
situation that you're going through but it's all like the same card
But it pertains to somebody differently and the story isn't always the same
But yeah, Tara's so cool. I mean, I do love it
There's lots you can fall down a rabbit hole if you learn any kind of divination
I know how to do a lot of different divinating and like I think that palmistry is one of the most like
intricate
Kind of like you just there's so many different ways to do that, too
But there's also just like a structured basis of it where this means this this means that but there's just so much
That you can get into with it with all the different lines
They say it feels like a warning
Does that warning you believe you feel like the hangman is the warning to watch your back?
well
I don't know it's because you know there's some you know
Sometimes I feel like some people feel like they're powerless to do anything in life
And it's like you know, there's no move they can make and they're just stuck and it's time to watch what happens
You know and that's you know
That's that's gonna be true in some reasons because we're gonna have things we have a lot of things
We have no control over like you know and people pass away and
You know like you know what what people do to us and you know people that go after us or
People that help us who's a true friend. There's a lot of stuff to figure out in life, you know
Do they make a tarot protect either dirty pictures or oh dirty pictures? Yeah, I mean most hero decks a lot of them
Yeah, nudity. I have a ton of them like for another I have so many dirty decks
And I also have like like raunchy humor decks and they make all kinds of different ones. Yeah
We use them someday, I don't know if we get in trouble for that can we show to like card nudity on the
No, I don't think I really think I like a lot of caravans will just like cover cover up the nudity on them
You know, it's like just because you know, it's just like they're just being careful. It's like kind of like
Even though it's like
Yeah, and you never know who you're going to offend
Yeah, I mean second. Yeah, your first normal one a few months ago. Oh, if you uh, yeah
Yeah, I would say terror is just a great great tool
to for introspection and
clarity and touch with yourself and yeah
and to get and give and get advice and
you know.
Holy big yon Jesus.
I got a good dinner last night.
I still have a lot of it left to eat
today.
It's right here maybe I'll eat some a little bit.
Copy's okay.
Yeah.
Maybe I will
I saw these big plants like jazz myself up and like do my hair and my makeup and then and then I just don't
Not a girly girl
I had to curl Grace's hair this morning though for her thing because she had to go to school
and then I had to meet her there for the little ceremony thing for the graduation ceremony and she's
she's got like thick wavy kind of hair and like so much of it and it's quite long and
it took me like two hours to curl her hair I'm glad she liked it because she was she's pretty
mean to me when I try to do stuff like that for her she's really picky but I killed it today
I do it with a straightener because it's like it just works better. The girls in the chat will understand that.
Curling your hair with a straightener, doesn't sound crazy.
Sounds fucking nuts.
What do you do with the duck eggs?
Eat them
Go make them like
You meet that like that that that what's it called but Baloo Baloo
Yeah, Baloo
You don't well, I don't know
What country girl don't you do what do you do with duck eggs?
You hatch them I'll burst you
He sits on them
You sit on them until they hatch and then he raises little ducks you fucking would do that Oliver
Bunky needs a card sure
Where's Spunky?
Where did I miss I need to go back and read this. Okay
Spunky got a couple cards
Okay, here's your first card Spunky hold on put up full screen
Spunky you got this
It's a strength. Okay. It's a strength card. Okay?
I don't know. This is like, you know, usually a strength card has like, you know, a woman like,
you know, opening a lion's mouth gently. This one is a little bit more menacing.
But maybe you'll have strength with a partner or something like that.
I'll read the car. It's a little bit of a different strength car. Let me see it
Okay, it says
It says, Brutus and Nero are Madame Medusa's enormous crocodile sidekicks.
Despite their imposing size, might, and muscle, little orphaned penny isn't afraid of them.
The tarot card strength carries the lesson that true power doesn't come from crocodile-like
physical strength, but rather from courage, inner resolve, and compassion.
I guess you're supposed to be looking at it and saying, I'm not afraid of that.
I know I just you know go get little get little orphan pennies like courage
You know says though you may not find yourself
Based with actual crocodiles strength is a positive sign that you have the determination good sense and outright
Gumpion to be any challenge head on and come out on top for best results channel pennies bravery
kindness and perseverance
This card is also assigned to persuade and guide
others gently and a warning against using force or ultimatum to get your way
Okay, that's really good. But then we have I pulled another one for you. We got the devil card. Okay, get the devil, okay?
There's the devil, okay
Well, you're welcome
But with the devil car, you know, the devil car is not necessarily backwards. I'm a capricorn. So it's my
Okay, but says the proud to proud powerful powerful mysterious
turnaboke
Inserts a potent's influence over his dancing minions who are content with their fate and they're thrown into the volcanic fire of Bald Mountain
The devil tarot card represents vise and destructive behaviors,
which reminds you that like Chernobog's minions,
you have a choice whether or not to participate in them.
So the devil also asks you to examine your own behaviors.
Could you be sabotaging your success?
If you're feeling tempted to over-indulge in vise,
the devil is a reminder to consider the potential consequences of your actions,
Turnabog summons his minions with dazzling displays of power, but their allegiance proves
to be their downfall, and he tosses them into fiery mountain.
Learn a lesson from them, be discerning, and don't let yourself be deceived by empty
promises or distracted by instant gratification."
And that's I think see the cards. They're like a little bit, you know, it's just interesting how they did those the villains cards. They're pretty good
Yeah, I do private readings. I'll do private readings. I'll do like, you know an hour on the phone you can
like to you my discord or you can
Double just appear or you or you can uh, you know, so I'll do it on the banner if you want to do it on the show
You can contact me on discord is Instagram
Yeah, I think because you have this strength remember it's like, you know, if you have the strength, you know, it's like, you know, you're already the stronger so it's like, you know, you know, you can like, you know,
And it's like, it's like a lot of like sometimes strong go after the weekend or the weaker
Hey, yeah
Let me know I
Yeah, I had a really good. I did a really good a private reading
We were just like an hour at the time goes really fast and a lot of a lot of information comes out
I just do tons of cars
Don't a few different tax. Hey, here's Lola. They're coming over a little bit. Say hello
Oh, so pretty hi, babe our TV
Mm-hmm
Yeah, well it's like sometimes it's good to like, you know, if you oh, sorry
I love you guys. I'm gonna go. I gotta get ready and go and I'll come okay
Okay, love you
Love you
Okay, you do with this deal with Stanley and not go a shit. Yeah, so it's like, you know, that's the better approach, right?
It's like not just like especially or even like, you know
Sometimes you just need to take you know the sleep on some things and then
Here you feel the next day. I don't know just the
Hey, hey, Jan take an army. Oh, you're welcome. Thank you so much. Thank you so much
They appreciate that
Yeah
Well, yeah
Sometimes
It's always better to deal with it gently because then you know, sometimes we do things we regret when we come at it angrily I
Love you. Thank you so much
Mm-hmm
reading about the fool yesterday but I was gonna read this spell there's an
Yeah, it says,
Boy bishops and burlesque masses aside, the fool himself played a much larger part of medieval life than merely to ape at Cucklust Hill
Ceremonies prior to Lent. In fact, he was often an integral part of every feudal court, attaining considerable fame in later times.
Great lords often
found place for a fool in their households. There, he held an honored position, and his
job apart from merely keeping his master entertained was to remind him that, like Caesar, he too
was only human and open to error. Theoretically, the poor fool was the one person at court,
immune to remretribution for quips at his master's expense. However, all too often,
he became the butt for cruel jokes for, like Dionysus, he was a scapegoat. I think I read
Oh, yeah, okay
Okay, it says the talismans of invisibility in modern times the name for the talisman has been abbreviated as simply lucky hands
It was known as the hand of glory the derivation of the term itself is interesting
stemming from the Greek manager Gordon
Mandragora, it passed on to old medieval folk grimoires as the Monde de Gloré, hand of glory.
However, the talisman described was not this instance of mandrake root, but rather root and
sprouts from the mid-summer fern, triopterous phylics moss. According to alternative medieval
tradition made famous by R.H. Barham in the Ingolbe legend, the talisman was found as an
actual hand severed from the body of a hanged criminal and pickled in zimort, salt peter,
This grizzly trophy was then cured over a fire of fern and vervein.
The grease exuded was retained mixed with sesame oil and twisted with a wick
into a taper which was attached to the knuckles of the hands.
When lit and borne aloft, this bizarre candle was said to cause all doors of the house to come
unlocked in its eerie light and all occupants within to be cast into a deep sleep, the boon
companions of the thief.
The mid-summer fern variety is however the older tradition and needless to say is more
widely adhered to than the other.
As dark of the moon you should trace a circle clockwise around the fern and yourself with
a new knife.
Then pick up the plant carefully using your hands as much as possible for the task.
As you remove the plant you must say ask its permission, carefully stating that you intend
Trim the fern fronds from your knife now, so that only five of them remain sprouting
from the tip-top.
These are the basis of the five fingers.
The stern provides the wrist.
As you whittle away at the hands, trying to make it as lifelike as possible, chance
a traditional invisibility spell such as the following.
Kasudam, Suvantos, Ahelios, Bored, Elameth, Kastumi, Dabuel, by that through which all
things have their being, and by Saturel, Harsheel, Daniel, Beniel, Asi, Monemun, that thou and
thy ministers render me invisible to the eyes that I shall indicate.
Giavules, Arvuron, Ilohai, Elmigith, Hirenobucle, Mete, Baiglis, Kimayul, Trevini, Evie,
Grete, Bachuba, Gouverine, or the Empire which she exerted over us, fulfill this work
that I may pass invisible to whom I wish.
To complete the spell, dry your hand on midsummer's eve, set a fire over a fire on which verbane
or verbonolese have been cast, again repeating the invisibility charm, came to complete a
talisman near earth, at home, until you wish to use it."
I mean, then it goes into like, you know, oh my gosh.
I
Know if anyway, do I need to tell go ahead? Oh, sir
God is God. Thanks guys. Oh my gosh
I don't know I think I don't like this stuff about like you know using animals is disgusting
But I can barely harm a fly
But yeah, there are like weird thing I did this guy named saying I don't know if you've heard of Saint 10
but he's on the show and he's like he like he said this frog and
It's like a dead frog and it's like, you know, he was like if you would like kiss it and stuff
Hi
Crystal oh
My gosh, can you hear me?
Oh, it's like I'm telling you my internet internet is like not working. So
Super weird not working is working out. Hi, you're back
How's it going? Listen, what do you think of self-control?
What do I think of self-control?
What do you think of self-control of other people self-controlling you as far as like, you know, like other people like
You know, you have like a lot of people like kind of controlling you in a way
What are you there?
What do you think how do you think they're controlling me?
Well, because they why do you they deceive you they make you even maybe even ponder
Like a gesture. That's even a lie. You know change
The observation to make it, you know greed whatever they're greeting. I don't even know what they're greeting
What they want from you. I don't know what they want from you
Well
I'm talking about in general
Uh-huh. Yeah, obviously they want something from you. What do they want from you? I
Don't know. How do they want?
You be you or do they want to be
I'm just curious to their observation of their self-control of like their body is like
Oh, they think of you as maybe their son or something or
Because she's so old
Well, I don't I don't know but she is a very late, you know, she's a very mature like a motherly figure
Very like my mama bear types, you know, not really motherly though
My mom would never fucking fuck like my mom would never treat people and my mom is also
My mom's in the nursing field too, but my mom's a doctor natural doctor
And she would never treat a single soul the way that she treats anybody
Yeah
Well, you know
People see people different way to a different relationships, you know, you have to like, you know, we kind of like
Who does she work with did she work with what does she work with?
The nursing field people is hurting walking people
I don't I don't think so. I don't know but it's like I don't know she's like I think she's the
Well, I have a feeling she is and I have a feeling she is and we need to clear that out real quick. She's in Florida
Okay, I'll get that go real quick
Well, you know what you know like the process is okay if she's you know cuz she doesn't seem okay. She seems unseen
Very unkept and well
Okay, there's a way if you're a nursing in the nursing area that you should control yourself with grace
Like, you know that kiss my cheeks
Yeah, you don't kiss my cheeks
Yeah, that's grace. You know Tracy
Mm-hmm grace. That's grace
That's grace
Those are the people, those are the good ones.
Those are the people that we need.
Those are the people that we want to be our nurses.
Do you think we want Christine to be our nurse?
You think I would want that person to be my parents,
fucking, the way that she thinks and her abilities
and the way that she's so nasty to everything now.
Nope.
She does not need a treat. She doesn't need to be around children or adults
unlike elderly
And her nursing felt
Mm-hmm
Yeah, it's well. No, I don't agree. I don't agree with you. I think she's like I think she's a talented nurse
And you know, she's a lot of years of experience
Not talented at all. She's not talented at all. Actually, she's very mediocre. She's seeing I
You know what that is that certified nurse? Yeah, I'll say if I nurse
Okay, that's nothing small. I will say that it's nothing small
But Shane and doctor, okay, and she could get um
She really needs to have a doctor
make sure
Uh-oh you cut out crystal. Oh, yeah, I can hear you
Yeah, you know, but it's anything we have like we're pretty people are pretty judgmental and
We know she's in Florida. We know where she's at
Well, we're out. We'll give her a little boost
confidence
Yeah
This is the firecracker. Yeah
They like to you know, you know confidence with very bad, but you know Armin
I guess it works both ways so we can give her a good boost. She can give me bad
She's not gonna get anything back this time
She might even not qualify this time
She might
might not qualify, can she pass a drug test in two days?
Well, hey, Elia, hey, Armin.
Hey guys, we also got 15 people
got memberships past a couple of days.
Yes, I get to five.
Sorry, bubba.
I've been telling you that we had the tornado thing and then
Like I have no internet
Thank you, thank you. Oh, yeah, I know I did but just when you like after three
Oh, but psyche
Yeah
Hello
I don't hear uh, um ask christine if she doesn't mind
if she can be qualified again at her nursing facility.
Can she be qualified with her actions?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
The way she treats people.
But Tracy never treated anybody like that.
I'm a family member.
See, these are the kind of people
that I have to go off the wall with, you know?
And then when I get disrespected
and then she was lying to you.
And you were believing it. I don't know where to go with that
I'm not gonna fucking fight it
Yeah, you should really take it on yourself and watch back here in videos
Because the things that you said was complete lies. I never called you a I told you that you kept saying that I called you a
Back I'm gonna do it. Yeah, okay. I know it's okay
That's what I said.
I'm not offended, I'm not offended by the word.
And I said that it hurt me.
Do you remember me saying that I didn't want to say it
and it would have hurt me if I said it?
Yeah. Well, it's okay.
I keep saying it.
But you forgot about the whole point
that she kept saying it
and saying that I said a lie
that she keeps lying about.
To you
How do you feel about me lying to you? How it does oh, okay?
You know what there's a god for liars and there's somebody that's in God
That says that if you are a nurse you should never lie
And and she's gonna go hell like right now. She's gonna bit like I hope the fucking chickens eat her head. Oh
Sorry
Okay, I mean I kind of do but I'm just saying I want to be nice
Well just be nice
Lou
Yeah, we can always be nice
Easy
I'm here. Okay, everybody that's gonna try to her see or give them back
To hurt them
Yeah
He would do the scene would be the kind of fuck
Shit all that's bad dude
Yeah, I have here
Like I said, I got like there's a certain health for people like her that pretend to be nice
Well, I mean she's like yeah, she's like yeah, she's been friendly to me, but she's now she's eating dude
It's all a joke dude. She was telling me that she was in a gang and she went to prison. She don't my all kinds of stuff. Oh
my gosh
Well, yeah, you didn't know that
No
There's a prison she was 21 she went to prison because her boyfriend
The game and like he had to go because she got pregnant and she got pregnant in prison
She had a baby and been fucking prison like this bitch is wrong dude
Well, I don't see I don't think she's here to defend herself
So that's like, uh, you don't want to be around prison wars. We don't need to be around prison war
My gosh psyche you are not a prison war
No, I'm not
You deserve better dude, don't you don't you want that? Yeah, yeah
I do
I want the best for myself and for everyone I love.
But you better start recognizing. You really need to start recognizing. You need to start
putting your fucking thinking cap on and just fucking just paying the mother fuck attention.
I'm not gonna tell you again. I mean, I'm not gonna tell you who to choose.
I'm gonna just tell you that this is what I'm feeling.
Uh-huh if you think like there's something going on or something
I'm just telling just
That bitch is like trying to run your channel and
She does it to he does it to a fucking you know, what's so funny about it?
She only does it to be to when she's really wasted she goes in there and starts banning everybody and then blames it on scummy
She's a disgusting whore
If you're off and oh, I didn't you know I
Love saying that though
You know, it's kind of like the F word. I told you that I love that word
I didn't was wasn't saying it towards you. I just love that burn. I
Know it's okay. I really I really do not get it
I don't have no reason to say it.
I mean, I don't have the guys
that are being disrespectful.
That's what I'm saying.
You have never gave me that vibe.
That's what I was saying.
You have, you walk in and out of the room
and think I'm talking,
I've never said that about you.
I'm not offended by it.
Wrong good.
No, it offended me that you thought
that I was talking about you like that,
like against your back.
It's okay.
No, I would never.
No.
I
Would never talk again like behind your back dude
I would tell you and I'm gonna give you a heads up when shit's going down
Even if we're not buddies or not even with with everybody dude
I would tell anybody even my like well, maybe not one but probably almost anybody
That shit's about to happen
You think it is for me?
To anybody
Okay
Well, I mean if you think they are gonna happen me this life life will happen, you know
It'll be life and no
I'm saying like if somebody was to hurt you and I knew about it or they were gonna hurt you too
I mean hurt you as far as like, you know say like porn bombing or
Like trying to come after you in some kind of weird direction
Be like hey, it's like you watch out for these people
Okay, I'm just I wouldn't go in it like just say hey watch out
I don't want people to hurt you is that bad or am I doing it wrong? No, that's no you're right
Yeah, I don't I don't I don't people don't hurt me either, you know, but
You know if there's someone
What to do like Christine like wants to run your entire fucking life dude and
Fucking
He's psyche. Hey when you go poop. Will you like twice once for me and once for you?
What twice
You're funny though. You're funny. Oh, I hope you're doing good today has the weather over there.
What's up?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah, just to lead her all together her and summer just we love summer
But we just delete them all together and then you'll feel so much better
Why are you doing something to me? I
Feel like they're trying to
like this weird game and it's not really working for them so I don't really know
what they're getting off it but I could see Christine because she's like just so
not the normal that she's getting kind of sick rise out of it because I see in
what she was doing to other people you're playing a game yeah
summer, but I think that that lady, that the old lady, Christina's.
I hear you now. Can you see me? Yeah, I hear you. Hello baby. I hear you.
psyche telling you they're fixing my shit, so
Know that they were the neighbors that they were fixing they're fixing at the neighbor's house
Remember I was telling you that
So I have a really bad reception so I miss what you're saying
That's a little bit
We're talking about
You say watch out for some people
Like dude, I don't even know anymore. I mean you have to take your own judgment because you know these people better than I would
Yeah, I mean I just think there's sweet people they
I like to be on my piano sometimes or really orders are there yeah, yeah
Wow
They're very nice ladies
To our mirror
I'm very glad you really should do you should do some backup you should you should uh watch some of these people
Like see what they say because it's not nice and they're lying to you dude
That's really sad for you because how are we gonna fucking prove it to you?
Wait, you can tell you just tell me like what those people are saying this or that like um
Oh
Not dude. No, no, no, no, no, no. That's not how it works, dude
You can say you can say people are saying you can be anonymous about it everybody can say stuff. It doesn't like dude. Yeah
You really have got to start paying attention you need to start putting your name in a block
like where you can see when people comment on your name.
So you can see what you're talking about,
so you know what's going on.
Have you seen comments about my name?
Well, I'm sure somebody with, I know you can do like,
there's a way you can do it, like, no.
Oh my gosh, you guys, you guys know, they will know how to teach you how to do it.
I'm not like on your platform, not really big on StreamYard.
And I'm not even a single say you're you're
Everybody want to talk? Hey guys in the chat. Hey everybody
Well, if anybody does come across you know my name in the forums or chats you can just go ahead give me a heads up
I'm not going to talk about everything.
I haven't seen...
Anybody here? I'm leaving? Sorry.
See, it's like hard times day there.
Chris, are you still there?
Chris's microphone's been messed up.
leaving mangle to Pedia? Okay. Have a good day. Hello? Crystal?
Oh, psyche. Oh my gosh, I tell you I don't the internet not good
We're working we're working trying to work together here, I mean I I I
Yeah, it's working
Yeah, so you have you seen my name like out there or anything or people talking about me another panels or anything
I see like a little bit of it
it sounds okay right now. Say it again, or maybe you should talk. Maybe don't talk.
I can't hear you, Chris. I'm sorry.
What's that? I
Don't know
Appreciate you all being here
Everyone's talking anymore I should get
Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone there? Anyone
I think that was my message.
Yeah, hi.
I'm going to channel messages from the chat.
I can still channel the chat.
I hear you all these weird things.
You're thinking.
I guess I do.
That's low, actually.
Low is my lap, pretty mean.
Well, guys.
because I don't bother you so.
No one wants to talk.
I don't know what to say.
You're washing.
Well, that's who anything the things were watching me
No
It's like
I think there's something called the dick just the despair code I've heard I've heard a yeah
I've heard about this despair code. It's just L is the code
You just program it into somebody so they just like feel so much despair. You know what the point of it is this like
It's still like, you know make them want to like not live anymore
So it's like
kind of a sad kind of thing to do
it's like kind of like a
silent weapon or like a
Silent weapon in a quiet war
something that
But I say, there's always hope.
I think when there's no more hope,
that's one thing, but there's always hope. It's the last thing that was in Pandora's box, so it's one thing we have left.
Just hope that
things will work out as they should.
Everything's going to work out for the best. Everything will be okay.
This too shall pass. Let me ask brother
Count your blessings
10 doors box you tell the story sometime
Because it goes into the creation of man and then the curiosity is actually a jar. You know, she actually had a job
She was very curious. She's actually the first woman, you know
According to the Greek pathology, he was made by Prometheus and Athena. We just got the Athena card religious day
So maybe this is a good time to read this story. Let's see if I was a little quiet on this show
No one knows it's all bad things
All the bad thing I guess we're all not not all the bad things it was all things everything was gonna everything else
Oh, let me see. Let me get it. Good. Good. Let me see.
Okay. It says,
In the Greek myth, Pandora is not born the usual way, but is instead crafted by the gods themselves.
The divine origin sets her apart from other mortals and heightens her significance in the grand scheme of the cosmos.
The creation of Pandora with a collaborative effort among the gods, with each deity contributing
their own special gift or attribute, let's imagine the scene on Mount Olympus.
Hephaestus, the god of craftsmanship, molds Pandora's body out of clay, shaving her into
the form of perfect beauty.
Athena, goddess of wisdom and war, dresses Pandora in a shimmering gown and teaches her
needlework in weaving.
Aphrodite, the goddess of love, bestows upon Pandora irresistible charm and grace.
Hermes, the messenger god, gives her the cunning, deceitful mind, and a seductive voice.
Each god, in turn, adds their blessing or curse to the new creation.
It's almost as if Pandora is the divine project, the showcase of the god's powers and its
estimate to the superiority of mortal beings.
But why would gods go to all the trouble?
What purpose could they have for creating this perfect woman?
To answer that, we need to look at the larger core context of the myth.
In Greek mythology, Pandora's box is not just the first woman, but a key figure in
the story of how suffering and evil came into the world.
Her creation was intricately tied to the actions of Prometheus and his brother Epimetius.
According to the myth, Prometheus, a Titan known for his intelligence, sold fire from
the gods and gave it to humanity.
Angered by the defiance, Zeus, the king of gods, decided to punish both Prometheus and
mankind.
He ordered her festive to God of craftsmanship to create the first woman, Pandora.
Epimetheus, the brother of Prometheus, played a crucial role in the story.
He was tasked by Zeus to distribute various qualities to the animals of the earth.
However, by the time he got to humans, he had already given out all the good qualities
living done for mankind.
This lack of foresight is what allowed Prometheus to trick Zeus to steal fire from humans in
the first place.
When Frometheus was caught and punished for his theft, Zeus turned his attention to Epimetheus.
He offered Pandora as a wife to Epimetheus, who was captivated by her beauty and eagerly
welcomed her.
Pandora, whose name means all gifted, was blessed by the gods with numerous talents
and charms.
She was beautiful, clever, and alluring.
However, she was also given less desirable traits, most notably an insatiable curiosity.
Good morning, J-Dog!
Before sending Pandora to Earth, Zeus gave her a jar in later versions of the box, which
he warned her never to open.
Epimetheus, in his short-sightedness, failed to heed his brother's warnings about accepting
gifts from the gods.
He allowed Pandora into his home, and inevitably her curiosity got the better of her.
When Pandora opened the jar, she unleashed all manner of evils and miseries into the
world.
Sickness, death, sorrow, strife, and many others.
She closed the jar quickly, but it was too late.
Only one thing remained in the jar. Hope. In this way, Pandora, the first woman,
was seen as responsible for bringing suffering to the world. Her creation was a punishment
for the emissaries of Prometheus, and her actions were the result of her flaws given to her by the
gods. Epimetheus and his lack of force and wisdom allowed this to happen.
But why did the gods create such a figure?
Here the story reveals a maturing belief held by the ancient Greeks.
Pandora, the first woman, was created as a punishment for humanity.
This aspect of the myth reflects a view that women were the source of trouble for men.
The ancient Greeks lived in a strongly patriarchal society, and many other myths depicts women
as dangerous temptations or conniving deceivers.
Pandora crafted as an ideal woman ends up unleashing all manner of evil and humanity.
Clear warning about the perils of feminine lure.
It says in this myth, Pandora's box is more than just a container, it's a representation
of the human condition.
The box is filled with the evils and misers of the world, things that make human life
difficult and painful.
When Pandora opens the box, she is essentially unleashing these hardships upon humanity.
Thinking of it this way, before Pandora, humans lived in a world free from suffering.
They had no concept of sickness, death, or sorrow.
These afflictions became an inescapable part of human existence.
In this sense, the box symbolizes knowledge and consequences that come with it.
Just as Pandora's curiosity led her to open the box,
our own desire for knowledge can sometimes lead us to discover things we wish we hadn't.
Once a piece of knowledge is gained, it can't be forgotten,
just as the evils could not be put back in the box.
What were the contents of release from Pandora's box?
The exact contents of the box vary between different versions of the myth, but they generally
represent the many hardships of human life.
Hesiod in his account mentions sickness, death, sorrow, deceit, strife, and other systems
of use.
Imagine each of these evils as a spirit or creature trapped inside the box.
When Pandora opens the lid, they all come flying out, spreading across the world.
suddenly humans who had never experienced pain or loss or deception are overwhelmed by these new
sensations. But there's one more thing in the box, hope. In most versions of the myth, hope is the
one spirit that doesn't escape. It remains trapped under the lid, providing a small comfort to humans
as they endure their new hardships. We'll talk more about the significant of hope app later on.
Or will we?
And with this, in Christian religion, peripandora
is seen as the parallel to Eve, the book of Genesis.
Both women are the first of their kinds,
both are associated with instructing
instruction of sin or suffering in the world,
and both act out of a desire for forbidden knowledge.
The comparison has sometimes been used
to reinforce misadopt misogynistic attitudes
portraying women as inherently disobedient or destructive.
The myth of Vandora is a rich and complex story that has much to teach us about the
human nature and the human condition.
At its core, the myth addresses the theme of curiosity and its double-edged nature.
On one hand, curiosity is driving forth behind human progress, discovery, and growth.
It is what compels us to explore and to learn, to question, to status quo, and push boundaries.
Without curiosity, we would stagnate, never moving back beyond our current understanding
of the world.
However, the myth of Pandora also cautioned against the dangers of unchecked curiosity.
When Pandora opens the jar, driven by a deep-seated desire to know what's inside, she unwittingly
unleashes a multitude of evils and sufferings upon the world.
This suggests that while curiosity is natural and even noble, it must be tempered with wisdom
and restraint and a consideration of potential consequences.
Not all of knowledge is beneficial, and some truth may be better left undisturbed.
This leads to the moral heart of the story, the responsibilities that come with knowledge
and power.
Pandora was entrusted with a great gift, the jar containing blessings and curses, and with
that gift came responsibility to use it wisely and keep the evils contained.
Her failure to do so brought great suffering, but it has brought humanity gifts of hope.
By trapping hope in the jar, Pandora assured that even in the darkest times, humans would
have something to cling to, a reason to persevere.
You're welcome
Yeah, I mean there's a lot more to it like this it's like that's basically the that's basically the
Yeah
The brain able
How are we doing this today? I guess everyone's leaving.
All right, let's, you know, I don't know. It's kind of quiet now. I still do have some possible apps.
I have some, I think I'll take another hit of pod and pass out. Let's take a nap.
I forgot the cat in my lap.
Let's speak now forever, hold you peace.
Oh, love you guys, thank you so much.
If you want more cars, Bunky,
I got more cars, thank you so much.
Yeah, anyone wants a car before I go?
Or you don't want to say anything to me?
Thank you for being here, guys.
Excited, I got a tail going well.
Yeah, let's look more into it. Let's see.
I'll leave you for the second.
Okay, it's funky
Okay, I have this night of hedgehogs. Okay, here's a night of hedgehogs. So this is gonna be a night of pinnacles
It's like the loser guy
This night of pinnacles, you know, he's like kind of this he's kind of the slowest moving night
But he's also like you know, he's out
He's out, kind of, you know, working and stuff and he, but when he, you know, when he comes,
he stays, you know, some nights rush in and out.
Night of Pentacles is going to hang out there for a while.
Let me see Night of Pentacles.
Hedgehog is okay.
The Knight of Hedgehog that says the Knight of Hedgehogs is the industrious and diligent as Bill the Lizard who risks it all
Trying to dutifully save the white rabbit's house after Alice grows the gigantic proportions
The Knight of Hedgehogs reminds you to stick to your routine work hard and focus on the details
Okay, and but he's like a man's coming towards this
This nine night of time. Hold on. I don't finish it. Okay. It's going towards these flowers
This is a nine of nine of flowers. Okay, the flowers are gonna be the wands and
so
So this is like this is like defense like you can see all these are defensive. So and there's like so this is
Defending some kind of idea you have or
Defending yourself somehow nine of flowers advise you to have courage while defending your ideas. You may be feeling like you're alone
In their defense, but that doesn't mean you that you should back down rely on your vision and passion to overcome current
challenges, okay
Because and it's funny because the way he's looking it's like there's this flower growing between the night and its next card
and it's like
It's kind of like the night
the night helps to grow and that the night helped bring this flower or this flower to you
That's protected and you're like and you're very like and you're happy about it
It's because it's a star card right there
You're the star on this card star card make a wish. Also, you're the star of your life and
They could let that mean the star card is like all good things all you know clarity
truth
Star card in this deck says
It says, like the beautiful white rose, soloist Alice meets in the garden, the star represents
serenity, composure, and hope.
The star glows like a glorious beacon of hope, encouraging you to hold onto your dreams no
matter how lofty and out of reach they may seem.
This tarot card reminds you that positivity and hope will help you manifest your most
cherished desires, wishes, and aspirations.
Oh good glad that helps
Yeah, anytime
All right, I'll do an advice card
Okay, your advice the vice card says justice
Okay, that's why I would say you know
Bear this is like the king remember the king was like a really nice though. Oh, this is the king
He was like really like he like calmed the queen down
Okay, he was really nice with the advice.
I think the advice is just to, you know, be fair, justice.
Says, the king of hearts persuades the queen
to control his temper and presides over a courtroom
trial for Alice.
The tarot card justice represents fairness,
morality, ethics, and consequences.
It says, being objective can be difficult when it comes to matters you're passionate
about or personally invested in, but justice encourages you to be fair and rational.
Make sure you really understand the big picture and are seeing things from a healthy, balanced
perspective before making decisions.
That's good advice for everybody.
It's like, you know, sometimes that's what makes me feel injustice.
It's gentle, but firm way. Yeah, and it's like that's why it's good to
When you're pat when you when you're attached to something and passionate to it passionate with it, you know
That that will kind of maybe change temporary or change your emotions about it. So
When you look at it was rationality and logic
But that's the thing some things will make you emotional and
But that's also a way people manipulate people and the population is like with the emotions sometimes.
And also because we're talking earlier today about
not being able to question certain things.
Is there a cat around?
Yeah.
Well...
Sometimes I think the punishment is to fit the crime, and...
You know, populations go through periods where there's a horrific thing that's done to the populations, and...
In today's world they don't even have the death penalty in those states. There's my thanks
Hi be cash
One thing they'll make you go gray
What's up guys
Have I looked at the Romans? Yes, I've studied the Romans.
You know, the Roman society wasn't very different from today because we have these breaded
circuses. And so the breaded circuses of ancient Rome, they were like pretty terrible
because they would be like, it would be like a torture chamber. They would just like,
Even by lions and tortured and they reenact the Greek myths
Like you know, like they'd have like a an eagle come fly down and eat a man's liver like they would do to
Prometheus and I mean some of the stories are a little bit far-fetched, but and then there's these Christian martyrs
I can read this some stories these Christian martyrs sometimes, but they
But they they did yeah, they did crazy stuff for the population and that's why you know, it's like people have they had these big
very horrible like you know
Violent and they would I mean then they would like it. I mean they would like it. They would they would cheer and
They would you know get thumbs up to
Spare some sense. I forgot how they do the thumbs up or something down and they would
Sometimes they could spare the person
Which they would rarely do I bet you know and
And it was a different life than they had, you know, they would train the children to be warriors from like, you know, early age and
So everyone was just pretty savage and
I'm sure the they did agree. Yeah, the world's still crazy, you know, but
I don't know, life is hard, you know.
It's like, I'm surprised I made it this long.
Like...
Okay, bye. Hi, this monkey. Thank you so much. Yeah
He's been smells I only need a little only a little he keys
The mousey
You were new here
20 people still. Well, yeah a little longer. So yeah, welcome everybody. Thank you for still being here
I think some more coffee, maybe
And then your drinks drink and a lot of a cool coffee
Okay, let's examine something
Okay
Okay, you're at home
You're promoting Bayez, okay
That mean
Mm-hmm
Okay, let's see if there's any
I
Like I think some people might be like mad at me or something, but uh
Because no one will stop coming okay, so let me see I'm gonna read about magic
There's a lot of it
Okay
These are kind of long chapters
Read about this
Uh, wow, there's all kinds of stuff there's demons I think this this is like a kind of basic
Magical book, but it's still there's probably two advanced
I can read something from this is called a stone cutter. Hi
Hi, okay
As the as you okay here the Japanese folks feel the most practical thing I find to send you on your way
Once upon a time a stone cutter was working next to a mighty rock
He paused from his labor and noticed a local merchant and his entourage,
past beneath the shade of the trees nearby.
Oh, if only I were a rich merchant, how happy I would be!
A disembodied voice answered him from the mountain,
your wish has been granted.
When the stonecutter returned home, instead of his little hut,
he found a grandam in the magnificent palace.
The man was joyous, and in his new life, the old woman soon forgot him.
One day, while walking through a hot and human market, he saw a fabulously dressed prince,
leaning cockily against his carers, basking in the shave.
I wish I were a prince.
He's got power.
He's got style.
And so he was a prince.
But as a prince, he found the sun still burned his face, gave him wrinkles and made him hold.
I wish I were the Sun itself so the wish was granted as the Sun
He had first felt mightier more powerful than anything on earth, but he burned high above his old township
Oh, here's the up off to finish that later
No, thank you. What you up to man?
Just chillin. How are you?
Just chillin man. Same here. Why you say everybody's upset with you. Why do you feel that way man?
So how?
I have a bad feel how
Oh, oh
You're saying how you feel like people are upset with you like. Oh, I don't know
I think because they go no one's been like no one's been really on the panels like a lot of people like this
Like this disappeared like you got mad at me, you know, it's like then I had mr.
Big Pies being really weird and like and then uh, you know, let's see, but
Um
So you oh my gosh, oh my god, this he looks I was scared on that
Hello, Joanie. That's the next day. I don't know. It's like yeah people you know, there's just like a weird weird vibe
But you know the Beatles mad again. What is she upset about now?
Well, no no she was here today, and then she was like fighting the child's 40 diamonds a little bit and like she was like
Oh, no one. No, she's like
No, I don't let you I think I think we're on good terms with now. She's kind of mad because I'm not like I haven't checked in with her and stuff
but you know
So the tool or for a friend of my mouse you just do it off. Okay. Well, yeah, I don't know
She just seems like she's kind of like not not happy with me
She's been streaming a lot more and like yeah, I wish her the best and stuff
Yeah, I give beatle was like on a big she was like like what 12 hours last night
She was on for a good while man. I don't know how she has the energy for that
Because if I'm drunk, I know I'm gonna pass out. There's no way I'm gonna be able to be on live stream, you know
For that long amount of time. I'll pass out psyche. I know you'll probably pass out too, right?
If you know you're drinking and smoking this pass out and then you know can wake up and do it again and
Yep. Hey, Ilya, these two weren't here. Yeah, so yeah
No, the things are going good. Like, you know, it's been a lot more calmer in chat in certain ways
And there's like a lot less trolley and I think people are people are getting along and stuff. That's pretty good
It's just like it seems like it's quite sometimes and like and like not as many people coming up on panel
But you know, I got 15 memberships the last couple days. That's pretty cool. Like, uh,
You know, I bought five and we had 10 donated and so
of
Exciting and yeah, maybe people start showing up like as far as like oh wait what you what today is what Tuesday?
Yeah, I think maybe everybody's like maybe they're at work, or maybe they're taking kicks to school. Yeah, maybe you know
Yeah, they'll show up and let me know public talk right now. Hello. Oh
Somebody there hello
Those are calling me
All right
Got a knock at the door
Yeah, I hear somebody somebody got his door for sure
You see what chaps
Oh, Jamie's child was in the chat.
What's up, Jamie?
Oh.
Okay.
False alarm?
This is this.
This is what I wore.
Let me see anything out of this.
Oh
They left that on your door. What's the hell? Oh, yeah, they're like Jehovah's Witnesses are like religious people
You know how they go door-to-door kind of pricks the word. That's what they did. So then they left you a flyer
Oh, they put sage what the hell
They left that with that
no
This is for Amazon. I was hoping for a fruit bath. Oh
No, man, hey, there we go
All I got the good state shot. You're gonna light it up right now
Yeah, well, it's not there you go. That's also
Clean the whole aura of everything, huh the whole vibe
You're the Jehovah's Witness Center that crosses the street from my house
they do
Wow
I probably was damn bro, but they probably left the flyer
Man them Jehovah's Witness man. They're like a cult
No
Yeah
Well, there's like a this is very nicely dressed black people I can usually see coming out of it
And they said it's sad to say oh pre-bible study
Basically these pamphlets that were like these carts there like these comics that they're like really
Scary comics that people going to hell and stuff
Shut the TV we got the TV on
So you got any plans today psyche, I don't know I'm you know
Uh, I've
Someone came over and clean the house or this girl came over and clean like my kitchen the other night
And so I just have a little bit more of the house to clean
I have like you know, my bedroom and my other room I have I can know my bad mouse we can order
You're not gonna go to the pier or nothing like that maybe or you don't think so maybe an IRA
Yeah. Oh, it's Tuesdays. It's only noon. Yeah. Well, maybe I don't know. I'll see how I feel. I'm just like, you know
Well, you're gonna take an easy deception here a little bit. I'm trying to stay on as like long as I can but
Yeah, you know, maybe I'll take that bath for sure
I'm looking forward to that
Can you take a bubble bath? Oh
Yeah, well, yeah, I'll take a nice cleansing bath and
You know, I like to take spiritual baths
Usually you see salt coffee and lemon juice, but then the bath
That's what's going on you're asking him say hello asked by who? Yeah, baby. Hey, how are you? How are you?
And that's by you I
Don't know I get a lot of new people here like um, but thank you for coming and welcome to the chat and
We'll see how much longer. I I'm making out kind of out of the cars up. I will go to the liquor store for sure
You know
Yeah, I will
See they
Have a little tobacco left. Actually, I have a couple beers. I haven't drinking these hardly. I've hardly been drinking lately
I just drink a little bit
Yeah, like a couple cans and a couple cans of the harder lemonade
What are you doing? Your little mouse have a little mouse in my room. Yeah
Oh, oh god. Yes, you're doing good. Oh, thank you. I had a feeling thank you for coming today. Hello
You catch what would be in band even now? Oh
Okay, you know what time says you see what he says is this
How come J-Dog is not selling ice cream because I have employees to sell my ice cream time
That's why I don't have to go out there and sell it myself. I have people who do that for me
Well, I wish you well with my channel.
Thank you.
Let's see at an ice cream for free. I only need a little bit. Yeah
Oh, yeah, you can have free ice cream just come over to my house a
Lot of people. Yeah, a lot of people have oh you see look at time. He's calling me a liar time
Such a hater such a hater
Thank You Billy
Now you chatter. Yeah
You got no pot. You got no weed psyche. I do it. I do I have this like I have a vape
But I've been like hitting it. I have like a little bit. There's like a little bit left in it
Oh, yeah, I think a little pie. Yeah. Mm-hmm a little bit
Looking at it. I just I've been taking it. I don't want to like take so many that I like false loose. Oh, yeah
Was it what kind of strain is that an indica or is that a hybrid?
If I need the hybrid it's called unicorn party
Oh, okay. Yeah, that's the hybrid. That's a good string
Bro, have you ever tried on the strain called?
What does it call?
Something donut it has a donut kind of flavor to it and you taste it
You ever have something like that?
Really good
Thank you. Why is people always?
I was about to pee it up. They always what?
No, what do you mean?
I guess the PDF card, what does that mean?
I
Don't know you gay. Oh, I know
Yeah, that's that just flies around the internet
Yeah, everyone calls. Yeah, everyone calls everyone up
You know that's his house location, but there are badly printed black walls and cardboard over the windows
The paint is had pink to make him
That's scary. Oh
Look at time with spreading rumors. He got kicked out. We know that's not his out. Okay time
Whatever you say
Accountants are asking me for no reason calling me creep and but as for true removed
Yeah
What what are you guys talking about Billy wagon?
Billy wagon. I can't read the city Hayden
Yeah, there's no accusations of slander no
No, doxing and
No racial slurs respect the host in the chat. Hey
Oh
I'm sorry, I'm sorry about your name up, but I don't I don't know anything about it
You know what this cat's name is they call her
What don't they what do they call you what's your name?
What do you have a cat oh beautiful cat
She's a baby
Princess
She's going to have babies pretty soon.
Nice.
Saiki, you want some more tax?
Or are you good on tax?
I'm good.
I wish I could give you a cap, but I can't.
I'm going to try it.
You could have some whole litter.
I can give you a whole litter of titties for free.
Oh.
Oh, you know what?
I'll go get them off at Beto's house.
You will?
Yeah, okay a litter of kiddies for me to should get pissed just fuck man. Just have a whole litter of kiddies for no reason
What's the guy's name
Good girl came in the house did you come with the cows?
Yeah, she comes in the house, but she's just chilling right here. She wants to
You go with the house or is she your cat? No, she's mine. Okay. Yeah, no, it's my cat
Then look at
Got the puppy right here. He's killing right now inside because the guys are right now doing the yard work out there
And he gets very very
angsty
When he's out there with the yard
He's relaxed he got his water
Right now when the guys are gonna mow in the yard, we'll let him back out in the yards because
And that's why the cat's in here
Because the cat's in here because she gets scared too
Oh, he's like with his animals animal time. Yep. You got the kiddies. We got the baby
Bushes come back in
Why are you at home with the dog if they're kids?
No, it's gonna take because of uh the yard guys
You know when they come to the yard the guy um when he mows the yard
The dog starts barking really loud
You know what he'll do is he'll bark at the guy and he'll try to bite the guy's ankles.
That's what he'll do.
So you gotta put him in a cage.
They're ankle ladders.
Yes.
So right now when the guy's going low in the yard, we'll let him back out and he'll be able to be back in his yard.
Yeah.
You have a dog psyche. You don't have dogs on psyche. No, I don't have a dog
But they don't we're family loves dogs and you have a lot of everyone has dogs
I don't everybody's I think everyone has a dog because the dog can't hear the lawnmower in a kid. Yeah, okay
Hey, so be careful about you. We'll welcome but yeah, it's just like please
respectful in the chat and
Hang out here welcome into the chat. Yeah, so you know interesting guy. I think I think your balls head
On my head. Oh, yeah. Do you shave that you say that? Oh
What a Noriko, you know, like with that with the electric shavers like they use like for the face and like everything like that
Just with the Noriko shaver
Not like a razor
You look at you a full head of hair though, they give a full head of hair. Yeah, I did. Yeah one more
Yeah, no no more
Okay
Would you ever for like five hundred thousand dollars you shave your head off
No, you won't do it my head see my head my head see my head off
No, no, no like like mine like cut it all off. Oh my oh my hair. Oh, okay. Yeah. No
Not for him. Oh, I want to draw you
Half a million dollars to save my head. Yeah
Maybe um, yeah
Okay, I've hundred thousand dollars half a million dollars. Yeah, I
Think probably yeah, okay
Okay
Where is my
And I'm looking for pens. I want to draw you but I have to find a pen
I shall find you. Okay. Oh
Okay, wait a minute. He wants to say zero water dishes in my dog's bowl, right?
Where is it? Zero water dishes? Look it. There is a water dish
right there, and then he has food right there. He's chilling right there because they're low in the
I didn't look it. You can actually see. Supposedly people are saying I'm living in a tent, which is completely bullshit.
I'll show you.
The tent that they keep seeing in this.
Oh.
This is the patio thing for like the patio.
That's all it is.
No living in tent situation, nothing like that.
Keith, can you sit down and show me so I can draw you real quick?
Just give me like one minute.
Yeah, let me go ahead and put this close.
Okay
Hmm. Okay. What else?
Okay, we got most of them
Hey, that's back. Okay, this is back. Okay, right
There's your pre-book
I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to
Yeah, it's a good one psyche. It's a good one. Oh, yeah, the good one. Okay. Thank you. I tried my best
Yep
Wow, so let's see. Yeah, we'll take a little
On my just charging right now here, so I'm waiting for mine
Mine just
So I'm waiting for my next to charge it
No, sure
Tricks is judging you hard
Well, I'd like to be on my back. He's watching looking see you get tracks DC tricks over my shoulder
Kids the kids has there
They see him
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, I'll say a picture. I drew time. Yeah, we see them pictures. I drew people like time and
Some of my pictures on here. Well, last time I drew Jamie's Cowboys last night. Oh
Oh, yeah, that's her right there. Yeah. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Where's time you have time? Yeah, and I have ghosts. Let's go straight there. Oh, okay
There's time
Man, thank you. So how many people do you have in that book drawn that you have what do you say?
So you have time you have Jamie's Calvary
Sassy Scarlett Sassy Scarlett, okay
Yeah
Who Vita I'm Vita I beat on my other book
Oh, okay. I don't see it. I know where it is right now. There's a dingle. I don't know who that one is. Dingle. Okay. I have a... Do you know who JT?
Yeah, I know who that is. Yeah. Yeah, you saw that one? Yeah. I know who JT is.
Yeah, there's a picture of him drinking out of like some kind of big glass
Rogue numb ad oh
Yeah, what is big arms and he cut off shirt. Yeah
Had you got he
Yep, there's got you right there. Yeah
You see a lecture yeah, DJ
So
Some day on the mouse, maybe I'll sell those also, you know, so
So then maybe I'll be hung in the gallery. We'll see. Oh, yeah
I mean, you know, maybe actually, maybe I will probably I might put them in like
My I write some friends as a show and stuff
You love your
pictures
What do you think of what happened with Mr. Bigpipes?
Did you see Mr. Bigpipes?
Yeah.
I kicked him off the show.
You kicked him up, why? What did he do?
He's just being weird and like he became uncomfortable and like
Then he said he put a curse on me or a hex on he said he put a hex on me six six six
I mean all this kind of stuff. What's wrong with him? Why was that guy acting weird?
I thought he was cool in the beginning. I thought he was you guys were good friends and then he started acting
You're right. He's gonna wish so you're kind of witchcraft on me or something
Mr.. Beep eyes one of your panel once oh once he was coming over all the time
And then like then he would be on like looking for page like he's in my lowest page
He's like page. You know, it's just singing songs to page
He was saying weird things to page time. He was like
Shit like that. Yeah. Yeah, like being a creep. Yeah. Yeah. No, that's no good
What's wrong with him? Is he like mentally ill? Is he slow or is he like just crazy? I
Don't know maybe all three. I don't know. It's like he was like
He's just being weird. I don't know. It's like usual a couple weeks ago
You didn't let people make fun of him now. He's here letting spells on you wishing you nothing, but the worst. Yeah
Yeah, I know it's not weird like I'm so nice to people and
And I was always kind to him, and I was like, I was like,
Hey, everybody, and people in the chat would be me like,
Oh, take him off, take him off.
I'd be like, Hey, he's not, he's a,
actually he's talented and stuff.
And I'd, he talked to him, but he'd just be like,
he'd just be like annoying.
And then like, and then he was just being weird.
And I don't like when I think people just make me fun of me.
Like, and it's like, I'll just keep cutting him off
because I don't have to like be like views on my own,
on my own platform, on my own show.
It's like, you know, so.
Yeah, he was like yeah. Yeah, he was like, oh he's a he's a I want to make out with you
I really didn't make out with you. He's like he's like, oh, but it's it you have to take a shot
He's taking shower first. He's like you your breath smells like fish and then
He's over there, he's yeah
Man, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What about you mini man? So are you guys cool skill or as a mini?
You know, yeah, many man that has come to the show after
Yeah, no, he's just hitting right here because that doesn't have yeah
He pieces of that. Yeah, and then he's like anything. I know he pisses in a bucket
He's telling me that isn't that like, you know, we're like he's been a bucket in the corner of his room
And then he's like telling me that then he had this big like he didn't he I thought his camera was out
But he was just using this like this like let's like
Digital it was like and someone said oh, that's a chaos magic sigil and I and then so then I was like
Oh, that's strange and then the next thing I know like I blocked him and then he's like he starts
He says say I'm a hexed and stuff like a six six six and so it was something like probably
Like some kind of like curse or something. He was trying to do about me or something
Maybe trying to give me maybe trying to get my viewers to him or something like that cuz he was like yeah, I don't know
Yeah, could be like that man. I don't know
But you guys are good now. You guys are okay like like he apologized and looking like that. You guys are cool. I
blocked him
That's like I'm out. Oh
So you but you blocked so you no longer with with with mini Manson mini Manson done. No, no, no, no
I'm talking about I'm not with any man. I'm talking about mr. Big Pipe still. Oh, baby massive. We're fine
You know my show again. Yeah, man. That's all good. I mean, I did this mini massive to the sticker or the
really cool
for me and I'm all going to
it's just like it's just like
like oh here I'll show you.
Did you see the mini Manson art?
Yeah.
There's an envelope.
It's in a couple stickers but
Yeah
There we go. Oh
God, okay, so you will accept my cheese if you okay, there's it out. Okay. Yeah, stop guys. No fighting
Um, yeah, so I don't know what else is going on. What's uh, have you been getting along with everybody and other shows or?
No, yeah, you know, I'm just same old shit fighting with beta as usual, you know
It's kind of like a brother sister kind of you know, sibling rivalry kind of a thing like
You know when you fight with like your sibling and stuff like that
It's kind of like that when you just fight with somebody like you fight in one minute
And then you're cool with them in the accident you fight next minute, you know, it's crazy like that
Yeah, that happens sometimes, but yeah, Vita was like, you know, like trying to like, I don't know, you shot Minimans at 7-10, yeah.
I will. Minimans, oh yeah. But Vita like, was like, you know, really like, really hard on me when she came on the show last time and then like, then she was like saying, like, trying to like...
Tell people like oh like either her or me and stuff like that and I'm able people choose and they say but she doesn't say Madeline
Yes, I think I think we're cool again, but
Yeah, yeah, she's a she's a long time today. It's well ours. Oh, yeah
Dude, I don't know what she I'm not trying to talk shit about beat her nothing like that
But for her to be up for that long on alcohol usually it's two things Adderall or scope
So I don't know which one of the ones she partook in with the alcohol, but
Whatever one it was it had her up for hours and hours and me
I've done coke back in my day not even bad back in the day, but a while back
When I've done coke it kept me drinking for hours and hours and hours on end like really yeah
The Arthur you never had that you were you young coke and you could just keep drinking like Budweiser
You just keep going and not even get hammered. I've never smoked anything in my life, sir
No, not smoke snorted cocaine nothing nothing snort snort snort suck
Not none of that day. Okay. Well, that's usually what it does
For me and my friends will you know, we'll get an eight ball and just do a whole eight ball of
Coke tonight and then we'll just get a whole thing cases of beer and just drink the whole night and just
have fun and just party
Sikey good morning. Good afternoon, sir. I
Think it's watching device
Give them a minute here before I give them a thought
There you go
Is it a couple words of thoughts or whatever? Are you doing there psyche?
Fine. How are you? I'm doing excellent sir. Excellent. I actually have a new name for you
Are you okay? You seem like you're off. Yeah, I'm fine. I'm trying to get this
high post anyone got a new name for you, sir
Yeah, good
site gay
Site gay get it gay like gay gay
Okay
Yeah, I was better than like psycho or sicko
I
Notice you like I have a couple of wrenches now here and there
Yeah, well, no, I just have you know, I have like a I know a few people were at wrench
Okay
Yeah, just like you people have been with me for a long time and I just uh just in case I need something to lead in the chat or
of just to say, you know, Jamie's Cowboys, everyone loves her and, you know, some of them are more, you know, Teresa too, Traveller, just to see.
Is Christine one of them?
Hey, Flirty, is Christine moderated?
Yeah.
No.
Okay, good.
Yes, please.
What is this you follow like a wrench nazi like am I?
Sweet pea why sweet pea talking to me. I don't even know who this sweet pea is the sweet peek of me talking to me in chat
I don't know
No, sweet peas not diamond
It's already diamonds up there sweet pea this person has been talking shit to me in chat all day
I don't know who this fucking sweet pea is
Well, you wanted my attention sweepy you got it come on panel
Yeah, what do you want?
Come talk to me now sweepy. You want to talk come right now though bitch right now
Sake
What's up, dude? How are you?
my man
Christine is the
You pussy the pussy don't even want to come on panel wants to talk shit, but don't come on
My
My mic on you. What's going on here a sweet piece we pee in the chat wants to talk crap on me
And then don't want to come on the panel on you say your face to face
Let's keep getting talked over. What's going on here? Hello?
Hello
I'm glad that Christine doesn't have a wrench and you don't need a wrench Arthur. You don't need it. Trust me
They're overrated anyway. Don't worry about it. You don't need it. No, but I'm glad Christine doesn't have one
Because that bitch she loves to fucking time people out just because they're going at her
She thinks it's okay to time something out and psyche
Channel I can't stand that. Oh, man
Yep
But you know and I know that she causes a lot of problems to you
I've heard Christine and beat us. I've heard her, you know on here
Like like 60 80 years old, I don't know but um, she didn't seem like she had any problems with me
I didn't have any issue with this thing
So I don't know if she does that to people. I don't know how she is with the wrench
Yeah, no, she's a Nazi with the wrench
You can I don't know how she reacts with the ranch because yesterday she was saying how you know
She's a nurse and this on that
And then she said how a patient went off on her and so
She was like, you know, I can't with this patient. So she went to go tell I
Guess the higher up that you know, she's not willing to perform
100% with this patient and they told them well, I mean everybody else has a number of patients over already at the limit
Yeah, I don't I don't I don't know
We don't have to bring that up
Jesus Christ this fucking channels become censored as fuck, bro
You can't talk about this. You can't talk about that.
That's all. Let's just, oh, but we know you, you know, you can talk about panelists.
You can talk about, oh, uh, hey, what do you think about me in the shower with you dropping the soap?
You know, I'm harassing you constantly, but that's appropriate.
You know, for me talking about something that was brought up on the panel,
no, no, don't talk about that. No, you can't do that.
But hey, open your, open your mouth wide open. Here's my dick, right?
Oh, yeah
I think you should come up open your mouth and show us the demonstration. I think you should do that
Like jesus christ this channel it has become
Like you got a lot of and i'm sorry, but you got a lot of retards and i'm talking i'm not talking about you j dog
You got a lot of retards that join the panel. You got the easy's of the world. You got the fucking um
You got the goddies of the world
You got the what's his name a piper piper digging big pipes big piper. Oh my god
Like hey guys, I know how to play an instrument
So I'm going to go ahead and just harass you guys with playing that shit right here
Like good god, dude. You got your own channel go play that shit over there. Oh
My like oh, but no, no
Don't talk about this
don't talk about that don't talk about you know we can't talk about the little hat people I get
that you know it's TOS so we ain't gonna talk about them but you know what how about this
me long how about this foot long you want this foot long there psyche uh is that TOS appropriate
Like good God, you know, I what has happened to you do? What has happened?
No, you can't tell about no, no
And and like oh my goodness you say the four-lettered word country, you know, which I'm talking about
It has two vowels in it
But no, we can talk about this TOS dick here. Yeah, I'm gonna go ahead and put in the shower
and go ahead
Serene
But that's that's TOS appropriate, right? Oh, yeah, you like to see me see myself, right? Oh, yeah, that's TOS appropriate
Yeah, I'm gonna go ahead and leave that up there you
You people subscribe right there, you know?
those people. Yeah, that's that's inappropriate. But go ahead and drop the soap there. And let's
keep talking about what I'm going to do to you. Right? Because that's TOS appropriate.
But what happened to you, dude? What happened? Who's gotten in your ear and like has like
censored the fuck out of you? You have, you know what you, you have become what you love
Say the Howard Stern bitch that you are now.
No, no, no, no, we ain't gonna talk about that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm trying to brand myself into something big.
I'm trying to go into XM Radio Serious FM.
Oh, yeah.
You know what?
Let's go ahead and talk about the TOS dick.
Go ahead and drop it.
That's appropriate. Oh, yeah
Like what has gotten into you psych what happened dude, what happened?
Please tell me look and I'm not saying that we should be free to say the F word that ends with the T
I'm not saying that I want to hear the heart of you are in this channel because I don't I'm not saying let's talk about
You know detailed the mutilations. What's going on? I don't care for that. I don't want to see it here. I get it
but doing like
You're censoring me from saying something that Christine said. I'm not I'm not mentioning where she works
Right. I ain't say what she works. I didn't say none of that
Well good god like no, no, no, no, no, no, maybe I didn't say no, no
I was like let's I like this season not here to depend on it sounds like you're talking about something
You did not say that. I understand had you said you know what?
What you're saying are your thoughts and your thoughts only I am not responsible for your thoughts comments questions concerns on Christine
That I would have been like, you know what I appreciate there
And you know what at the end of the day, this is your chance you can do whatever fuck you want, right?
Say you can take me out of panel right now
As a listener and as as much as you want to hate it, but this is the darn truth as a donator
I think I should be able to at least be vocal about what I support here.
Well, let's talk about something else.
Let's talk about something else, ladies and gentlemen.
You want to talk about dropping the soap?
How about that?
Let's talk about that, right?
Let's talk about...
Oh, yeah.
You don't want to see the country solar guy here.
Swallow it. Swallow it right there. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Go ahead. Yeah, Barry. Oh, yeah.
Like, what? It makes no sense to me. Like, you care about TOS. Oh, but how are you keeping
it? You know, how are you keeping it to 100% true?
Or what should I say? How are you be so truthful about caring TOS about caring for TOS?
When you're here showering on fucking streams
What's the naked?
Okay, well, you know what that in that case all of it's all good. You know what?
There's somebody somebody delete somebody in real life, and if they're not naked, it's okay
You know, if a man beat up a pregnant woman and she's not naked, it's okay, right?
It's all right, psyche, you know, and you're in your way of thinking, that's all right.
You know, some guy was dressed up, and he was fully clothed, and he went to a bank and
he stole all the money.
It's all right.
He was fully clothed, it's all right.
It's all right, it's TLS.
All the psyches at the local bank, and he witnessed what went on.
And he probably knows the person that committed the crime.
He's not going to say anything because the guy was, you know, he was really cold.
It's okay, it's all right.
It's TLS appropriate, right?
Hey, Psych, get this devil out of here. He's a fucking Satanist. You know that, right?
I'm sorry. He's a total Satanist. Yeah
Yeah, I got a positive when he comes up here. He doesn't give any positivity when he steps up here
I never heard him one now
Well, my job is done. Yeah, you have a good one. Psych take care. Thank you. Thank you
Yeah
I think I should take his advice.
Yeah, I told him, all I did was there was no doxing.
I just seemed like that was a huge talking,
personal information, and he just kept arguing,
arguing, arguing, that's what he used to argue.
So, probably not.
Great person, plus he's like seeing these weird things
My god
Yeah, I don't invite them on panel. It's just like
Let's add the boot, come here, there's the other thing.
It's okay, I think, oh, I think it's jokes or something.
Choice foot, legs.
She told me legs.
He's trying to seduce me. He's trying to seduce what I got. Oh no, he's showing me the knee. Oh my god.
He's showing me himself.
He's giving me his finger and he's like making a jerky motion with it. Okay, okay, now he's holding it still.
Going on this like you sorry, that's my evil twin there. How you doing there, buh-bye?
All right
Hi, are you okay? Look, it's uh
It's after the year
June is almost over
I'm gonna ask you a personal question. Is that okay?
Well, I'm not personally good. Okay. Have you met any of the gold that you set yourself?
New years
Yeah, actually, I was just the goal is to get monetized by like April and then I was okay
I was monetized by like early March or or something and
Or like at least I think the banner I kid it took a little bit longer should get approved and stuff
What are you doing as coffee and trying to find a way to trick you for it?
Yeah, and so then, you know, I, you know, I just have, I have membership goals and like,
you know, I just want to, all of my goal and goal is to have fun and like to keep the channel going and
you know, to make sure everything's good on the panel, keep everyone happy and
have fun. Has my book coming out good? I have illustrations for it so far. I'll have some
But yeah, you know, I draw some people and, you know, I'll continue to do that.
Some of my drawings are better than others, but I don't think calling her, yeah, yeah.
And I know, I say that I don't want to call people names.
I want it to be, well, people can like talk to each other and I don't know how some people
talk to each other, but I don't want anybody like attacking each other, but trying to like
change the format of the show that much.
Everything's not changing. I mean it's like it's like all it's like still you know
I just press the go live button and sit here and
Talk and hang out and bring people up
But it's like, you know, I have to ban like people like mr. Big Pipe's who are trying to curse me on my own show
And I have to like, you know
Do it, you know, and there are people that don't support the show or they don't they're just trying to cause trouble
It's like as long as people come up on panel or kinds
I'll uh, I'll have them up, but
Yeah, but did you say big pipes is man? Yeah. Oh my god
He could put a curse on it. He put a curse on me. What?
Yeah
That's weird as fuck
He says like 666 and he says like I put a hex on you a hex
And you've had nothing but his back bro, you see that's what I mean, that's great
Yeah, like, you know
That's weird
I gotta be honest with you, I feel like
It's probably gonna be less than a month. He's gonna be back. You're gonna allow him back. I
Know I helped like go become an alternate account. Thank you for forgiveness
Then like, you know, prove and be nice and chat for a while then I might unbend them on string or two, but
But probably won't well they open the image of a brain
Yeah, okay, yeah, my trust will be fast
Like imagine you right if you and I know you would never do something like that, but
If you were to ever do something like that you must really dislike the person don't you think if you do what?
If you were to do what he did I'm not saying you do or you have
I know you wouldn't but if you were to go down to that level
You would do that to somebody that you just fucking spies like that person
Yeah, actually to that love well here
I guess he didn't like you know ready cuz I was like baby like I don't know but he started putting up that like
It's like chaos magic single digital and then like whenever he was off even though he has his camera was working
He just had the sizzle up and then he would like
then I saw him like backstage and I like banned him one night and then like he was
but he's like because I banned him he was like he put the he said I've
hexed you he said he said I he said you're hexed something like that I yeah
and he's like he's so mad he's like let me in let me in that's weird he said I
was just trying to chill you're so jelly of me that's weird yeah pretty bizarre
On that note, just know this, I know I talk a lot of shit, but I
Would never do something. I think that's
Not only is that weird, but I think that's just
creepy evil definitely evil and
Don't forget you wish any type of farm or bad
had a bad energy towards someone like that like literally wishing a whole spell or
first
That's just gonna come for you man. Fuck that
What's your name psyche
I'm gonna call you Pat
Can I still call you Pat?
Okay, I'm that note
I'll be watching and you take care man stay hydrated dude. I know it's hot over there. Well, how hot is it over there?
Um, it's like, it's like 70 or 80 that's nice
All right, brother take care man. Okay. Have a good day. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you, psyche
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen. I want to know when psyche kind of applause
Bando goes live every single day for our entertainment.
I believe he at least is owed at least $2.99 a day,
at least at the very frickin' least.
Well, at the very least.
Thank you, sir.
Okay, thank you.
Yeah, it's actually $4.99 a month.
So anyway, are there? I mean, Satan, yeah. Well...
I'm scared.
I'll tell you, I'll tell you, like, all kinds of...
Yeah, I don't know. Everyone's got, everyone's got cuckoo for cocoa puffs.
Oh, come on.
What kind of did he pay for I don't know
30 thank you for being a member 24 people in chat we get good numbers here
No
A little bit off lately
Thank you guys for like being here, you know, you guys support me in all kinds of ways like
Just being here chatting I'm on the panel or
Getting readings or just being good reading my friends. Thank you
Well, thank you God
Yeah, we'll keep on fun going on
Like remember like people can say anything it's like it's just like with
It's always like, you know, there's more always more fear people just want to conjure fear in you and it's like that kind of spoils everything
So it's just like, just enjoy life while you have it, because not even life is guaranteed. So,
you know, as you come to, it's, you'll come to like bridges and the off-towers in your life and
things, but you'll always be able to be able to get through anything.
I
You know, I love music because it's a copyright stuff I would like to maybe I don't know but
you know
I like when I keep music off the show just
Avoid any copyright issue. So I know
Yeah, behavior is the better.
All right, I was reading this stone cutter fable
So this guy in Japanese guy he wishes it's kind of reminds me the fisherman's tale
But it's kind of different he wishes he was the merchant then he wishes he was the prince
Then he wishes he was the son
It says as the son he felt mightier and more powerful than anything on earth
But he burnt high above his old township a large cloud moves in front of him obscuring his view
What's this a cloud is mightier than me? Oh, I wish I was the cloud
As a cloud, he floated between the sun and earth.
He blocked the sun's rays, poured rain, and until he flooded the town, overflowed the
rivers and drowned the crops in water.
Everything was washed away and the people fled.
But after all his watery destruction, a great rock remained on the mountainside unmoved.
This rock moved for nothing, how I wish I was a rock.
And a rock he became, crowded and unmovable, unaffected by the heat of the sun, nor the
barrage of rain.
This is the best of all, he thought to himself, however one day he heard a strange noise
below him.
When he looked down, he saw a humble stonecutter, driving tools into his surface.
A trembling feeling ran through his body, and a great block broke off and fell to the
ground at a stonecutter's feet.
Is man mightier than a rock?
Oh, I wish I was the man again.
The mountain spirit answered, your wish has been granted.
The man was content to remain a stone cut of the rest of his life.
Never again did he feel jealousy, covetousness, or painful longing.
Instead, he knew only joy, relishing in his own humble perfection.
Would you like that?
Anyway
She man
How's everybody doing and we can pull some who-do cards
The daughter of baskets and so this sounds it seems like a page of earth. Let me see daughter of baskets
Okay daughter of baskets
Sloan, plant, boneberry, says Tituba was an enslaved teenager who was accused of being
a witch in Salem, Massachusetts, and is depicted here as the daughter of baskets.
She was of Arawak heritage, which automatically made her a suspicious character among the
Puritans.
The daughter of baskets carries a basket full of vein berries and a pot of tea.
Says the daughter of basket is generally the better the bearer of good news on the positive side
She's charming imaginative creative loyal. It has great communication skills on the negative side
She's delusional jealous a pathological liar
Con artist or suppresses her feelings in a reading if she doesn't represent a literal person with these qualities
Then she represents these attributes
Okay
Tishiva, what else do we find?
We have the father of knives, I think he's the king of swords. He's the king of swords,
energy, father of knives. He's not basket with all these things.
Father of Knives says, plant a slippery elm, says the Father of Knives is standing outside
of a circle of cornmeal with a knife stuck in the center. There are broken timepieces in the
circle with the big hands pointing to the numerical value of the person's name. Their time annoying
him is now up.
It says, the father of knives is a consensual dominant male.
On the positive side, he is assertive, intellectual, ethical, analytical, mature, and a just leader.
On the negative side, he is cruel, opinionated, vicious, abusive, stoic, tyrannical, and stubborn,
in a reading if he doesn't represent a literal person with these qualities that he represents
these attributes."
Yeah.
Okay.
So
Yeah, we got a father we got a daughter. Okay, so this is doctor grants doctor grants
Oh
You know, I think I think you know
I've practiced a lot of like the physical things of magic and rituals and things like that
But I find like you can do most you know most of it in your mind. You can you can actually do rituals in your mind
Yeah, so
So this is Dr. Grant, this is number nine, okay?
Number nine, Dr. Grant, okay?
This is Dr. Grant, what did Dr. Grant have to say
to us today?
I think it's one of the elders, let me see.
Dr. Grant, page 50, okay.
Dr. Grant, this is the hermit card. It says, this is from Luke 5.16,
But he, Jesus, would withdraw the desolate places and pray.
Plant, Duckweed says Dr. Grant is shown in solitude picking herbs and roots in the swamps
of Louisiana.
Dr. Grant was a Protestant conjure doctor from New Orleans.
Unfortunately, the details of his life are unknown.
By the time Zora Neale Hurston interviewed Dr. Grant and others in the 30s, many conjure
doctors were using herbs and other supplies from catalogs.
Dr. Grant however was a proud swapper who preferred to do things the old fashioned way
what he needed in the wild. Dr. Grant's reminded Houston of Hurston of a few critical books,
often forgotten lessons.
1. Don't believe in one's limitless power, 2. Petition spirits unequal to man, 3. No more
than one way to get a job done, and 4. Acknowledge that no two people or jobs are alike, because
a remedy that works for one person may not work for another. Dr. Graham was highly sought
out for his abilities, and in some cases was paid more than $100, an exorbitant amount
Meaning, when Dr. Grant appears in a reading, it may indicate the necessity for some alone
time to recharge.
Specifically, it may recommend solitude, in nature, to reflect and listen.
This is more important now than ever, as we are constantly accessible to others via technology.
While this may be convenient, it is also a tremendous burden, and we have little time
to clear our heads and just be without earbuds blasting music in our ears as zillion advertisements
or social media alerts pinging for us to engage with the world again.
They won't stop, so you must make the conscious decision once in a while to make it stop.
Let's be clear, this card is not about sitting in the park for a few minutes looking at pretty
trees, flowers, or a squirrel before you get back online.
You know it's about considering the essence of what that tree, those flowers, and that
squirrel, and how you're connected to them.
and the extraction of power from fundamental reality.
Ford is from the comprehension of source, that knowledge must be accessed and distilled.
Remember, you take something from other nature.
Don't forget to give something biodegradable to her, and her creatures in return.
This card may also indicate you're seeking knowledge and you're ready to make things
tickets to the next level.
It's time to seek guidance from a worthy teacher.
If you received Dr. Grant in the reading, consider the following.
Do you understand the importance of a long time?
Maybe it would be better to stay home tonight?
Silence is golden.
Focus on finding the truth.
Be in the world, not of it.
Pay more attention to your guru or spiritual counselor.
Do you really consider the advice you received about the issue?
It's okay to take a break from him, her, them, or that to reevaluate things.
Meditate more.
Follow your inner voice.
That's it
Okay, well
You guys think I like to suck
Okay guys
Thanks for being here.
I love you. Appreciate you.